Chapter 365: Hu Immortal Blessed Land opens

Back at Shang Liang mountain, Fang Yuan could only be said to have made small name for himself. But after the battle with Tie Ba Xiu, his name spread throughout the Southern Border and truly rose up to fame, becoming a famous demonic path genius.

This news attracted attention from countless people.

Some were experts who had been in closed cultivation for many years while some were Gu Masters who were roaming the world. He faced both righteous path's attention and demonic path's coveting. Fang Yuan had truly charged into their sights.

Some people chose to retreat temporarily like Century Boy. Some like Li Xian and Hu Mei Er were adding fuel to the fire. And some people's battle intent were stimulated and they directly expressed their intent to challenge.

At once, the winds rose and the clouds began to gather, countless waves moved towards Fang Yuan.

San Cha mountain.

In a certain cave.

Fang and Bai were sitting cross-legged. Fang Yuan's palms were placed on Bai Ning Bing's back as he transferred his primeval essence.

In Bai Ning Bing's aperture, essence gold primeval essence fell down into her primeval sea like a waterfall, causing many waves.

The waves surged continuously in the primeval sea and constantly cleansed the aperture walls.

Fang Yuan was rank four middle stage and possessed bright golden primeval essence. But with nine eyes liquor worm, his primeval essence was purified into essence gold primeval essence. Right now, he was pouring his primeval essence into Bai Ning Bing's aperture through bone flesh unity Gu and helped her nourish and strengthen her aperture.

Several hours later, Fang Yuan retracted his palms while Bai Ning Bing slowly opened her eyes.

Her expression was tranquil.

She did not show a trace of gratitude to Fang Yuan for rescuing her, and also did not show a trace of anger for his procrastination.

She was very tranquil as if she had never even been trapped.

However, in the depths of her heart, she felt extremely complicated.

For a long time now, she had been above Fang Yuan in terms of cultivation. But right now, she had instead become the beneficiary of bone flesh unity Gu.

Essence gold primeval essence gave her huge assistance. After all, she was still at rank four initial stage.

"It seems cultivating together with Fang Yuan isn't so bad..." The moment this thought appeared, Bai Ning Bing extinguished it in a flash.

She slowly stood up and spoke with coldness in her voice like she was taking joy in Fang Yuan's misfortune: "Have you heard of the recent rumors? Many people are saying you hold the great secret of three kings inheritance. You did not know any flying methods before but received it from three kings inheritance. Hehe, you need to watch out. Tie clan is furious and has publicly proclaimed you as their enemy, their arrest warrant for you has already spread over the Southern Border."

Fang Yuan indifferently replied while remaining seated: "Hehe, is there anyone who doesn't know about our relationship? Since Tie clan is coming after me, you will also be on the hit list."

"Hmph. Continue your cultivation till midnight, I will stay guard for you. After midnight, we shall switch." Saying so, Bai Ning Bing walked out.

The current situation, compared to when they had just arrived at San Cha mountain, was much more dangerous. Fang and Bai did their best to cultivate at different times.

In the depths of the cave, Fang Yuan remained alone.

He did not hurriedly cultivate but rather sank into contemplation.

Tie clan's response was already within his expectations. He killed an elder of Tie clan and also chased their young master; already ruthlessly infringing their bottomline. Tie clan was a top clan, one of the leaders of righteous path, how could they put up with this? Their retaliation would definitely be extremely fierce!

Besides Tie clan, there were also other problems.

Shang clan, Wu clan and others in the righteous path; Hu Mei Er, Li Xian, Century Boy and others in the demonic path.

This was the price for becoming famous!

Fang Yuan made his name from the battle, but it also pushed him towards the eye of the storm and was now watched by countless people. There were undercurrents and probings from all sides, there were even waves that wanted to submerge him, already having converged into a huge whirlpool.

With his previous life's experience Fang Yuan knew he was facing a test.

If he could escape from this whirlpool, resist the assault of the waves, then he would truly gain a foothold and become a publicly recognized expert of Southern Border.

But if he was swallowed and shredded by this whirlpool, there was no need to mention anything.

"Now, Divine Thief Lu Zuan Feng should have already repeatedly infiltrated Demon Suppression Tower and caused a great havoc, Tie clan should already be under huge pressure. If they want to gather their energy to deal with me, it won't be a matter of a month or two. I can forget about them for now."

"The rumors outside claiming that I hold the great secret should be Li Xian and Hu Mei Er's doing. Hmph, I will deal with these two sooner or later. It is just that Li Xian still has a lot of value currently. And behind Hu Mei Er stands rank six Gu Immortal, I need to plan this carefully."

"Three kings inheritance is a really big cake, I have no way of eating it whole. I can only choose the best parts of it. If I can obtain the essence of the inheritance, like undefeated hundred battles Gu and others, this trip would be a success. My strength will have an enormous boost and it would be extremely helpful in the great battle of Yi Tian mountain."

Thoughts whirled in Fang Yuan's mind before he dispersed them and thought of Central Continent.

"Calculating the time, Hu Immortal Inheritance on Tian Ti mountain should have opened. This is a true Gu Immortal blessed land and is many times more precious than three kings inheritance. That Feng Jin Huang became a Gu Immortal all due to this inheritance and became a figure whose name would shake the world in the future..."

Meanwhile in Central Continent, at the foot of Tian Ti mountain.

The elite disciples that came from the ten great sects of Central Continent gathered together.

In the crowd, the real Gu Yue Fang Zheng softly let out a breath of turbid air, the great competition that lasted for months was finally over.

Several months ago, the ten great sects sent an order at the same time to organize a great competition for these elite disciples to determine the rankings.

Central Continent's ten sects contained the strongest inheritances. This generation of elite disciples were all dragons among men, children of heaven. Even the worst disciples among them had one or two trump cards.

Because of Fairy Bi Xia, Gu Yue Fang Zheng did not have an easy time.

In the great competition, many of his opponents showed deep hostility and made heavy-handed attacks. Fortunately, Fang Zheng had deep foundation, possessing an ironbeak flying crane group and also had the guidance of Lord Sky Crane who was inside the spirit incubating flea; these allowed him to struggle through each round and obtain a rather high ranking.

Right now, in the sky of Tian Ti mountain, ten formless Gu Immortal divine consciousness were quietly communicating.

"This generation of elite disciples are also ordinary in general. But there are finally some excellent juniors."

"Hmm... Spirit Butterfly Valley's Xiao Qi Xing is pretty good. If I am not wrong, he should be the great-grandson of Xiao Bai Hong, right?"

"Myriad Dragon Dock's Ying Sheng Ji is also very outstanding, Long Nǚ has taught him well."

"Hehehe, you are too kind. Your granddaughter Feng Jin Huang is the truly outstanding one, none of her peers can match her attack."

"Are you all going to keep on flattering each other? Let's cooperate and completely open this Hu Immortal Inheritance!"

"Alright, alright."

"Then let's strike together."

"Rise!"

Ten formless powers surged out from the void, majestic and boundless like tsunami or mountain torrent!

The world changed, wind rose and clouds rumbled.

The ten powers revolved around each other before converging together and colliding against a certain place on Tian Ti mountain.

There was no sound, the terrifying formless power vanished like thin air. Golden rays of light blossomed and a vermillion gatehouse slowly rose up.

The gatehouse was a hundred feet tall with a nine colored plaque on it shining brilliantly.

In the air, pink propitious clouds gathered and bright rays of sunlight gathered to become a flight of stairs.

The stairs stretched out from the gatehouse and became a rainbow bridge, landing exactly before the group of elite disciples.

"Enter according to the ranking of the competition." An ethereal voice came from the air and clearly resounded in the ten sects' disciples' ears.

This was the voice of a Gu Immortal.

All kinds of expressions appeared on the ten sects' disciples' faces; awe, reverence, zealotry and so on. Most of their gazes gathered on a girl.

She was wearing a phoenix coronet, had slanted eyes, her golden brows were thin and long and there was was a small red birthmark in the middle of her brows. Her appearance was dignified and graceful, and her beauty was unrivalled.

She was the winner of the first place in this great competition - Feng Jin Huang!

This girl was magnificent and brilliant, her skin was like snow and her eyes were like lightning. Like the phoenix that soared through the skies, she was elegant and pure, arrogantly looking at the world. When compared to her, the elite disciples around her seemed to have turned into ordinary sparrows.

Fang Zheng had fought with her, but was defeated in just six moves.

Hearing the Gu Immortal's voice, Feng Jin Huang gave a clear whistle and turned into a golden light, shooting forward.

The golden light became a phoenix and collided into the gatehouse; the vermillion gatehouse shook and opened a void that swallowed Feng Jin Huang.

After Feng Jin Huang, Xiao Qi Xing, Ying Sheng Ji and others entered Hu Immortal Inheritance one after another.

After twenty to thirty disciples entered, it was Gu Yue Fang Zheng's turn.

Fang Zheng walked through the rainbow bridge and entered the gatehouse. He immediately felt dizzy, colors rotated around to form a whirlpool in front of him, dazzling like the blossoming of all sorts of flowers; he felt like he was drifting in a gorgeous hurricane storm.

"Heeheehee..." A cute and young girl suddenly appeared in his sight.

"You are also another fated person that wants to inherit Hu Immortal Inheritance? In a moment, you will see a mountain. Only the first person that ascends to the peak can obtain me. You need to work hard. Those people that entered before you have already taken a huge lead. Heeheehee..." The girl was wearing rainbow colored clothes, on her back was a snow white fox tail that was moving mischievously, she had large and round eyes that showed her innocence.

"You, who are you?" Fang Zheng was startled and puzzled, he was unable to make sense of this Gu Immortal's place, how could a girl appear here.

"Heehee, so it is a stupid boy." The girl said and mischievously extended her tender and fair little finger, and softly touched Fang Zheng's forehead.

Then, just like how she had appeared, she suddenly disappeared.

From this slight touch, Fang Zheng's body that had been light as a feather recovered its weight and suddenly started falling down.

"Aahhh!" A strong feeling of weightlessness spread over Fang Zheng, and he subconsciously screamed.

He wanted to activate his Gu worms, but to his horror, his whole aperture was locked in by a formless force, making him unable to use the powers of Gu.

"Could it be that I, Gu Yue Fang Zheng, am going to die at this place, dying by falling, having such an absurd death?!"

Chapter 366: Land Spirit

Thud.

A dull sound echoed with dust flying everywhere.

Fang Zheng fell flat on his face on the ground.

Although he fell from a high altitude, it was only for a short time before he landed, thus he survived.

"Spit spit spit!" Fang Zheng sprawled on the ground and spitted grass and mud out of his mouth, a sore pain spreading throughout his body as he felt stifled.

"Where is this?" He took slow, deep breaths and stood up awkwardly before looking at his surroundings.

It was a scenery of green, Fang Zheng felt like he was in a grassland. The grass rustled with the light wind and countless flowers of all colors formed a tapestry that spread to the horizon.

Far away, there was a tall and precipitous crystal mountain.

The crystal mountain was half-translucent and was pink like a scene from dreams.

From his position, Fang Zheng could clearly see human silhouettes climbing the mountain. Compared the the crystal mountain, these figures were very small like ants.

"The first person to ascend to the peak will obtain Hu Immortal Inheritance!" Suddenly, Fang Zheng recalled the mysterious girl's words.

Who was that mysterious little girl?

Could they really inherit Hu Immortal Inheritance by climbing this mountain?

While Fang Zheng was indulging in his doubts, Lord Sky Crane's anxious voice appeared from inside him: "Stupid disciple, what are you still hesitating for? Quickly go climb that Dang Hun mountain!"

"Master!" Fang Zheng was both startled and happy, "Who was that little girl? And, why can't I use any Gu?"

"Get a move on already, grasp every second. I will explain to you, listen properly!" Lord Sky Crane hurriedly explained —

"Hu Immortal Inheritance is not a small matter, it is an intact Gu Immortal Inheritance. There can only be one inheritor, whoever obtains it will soar to the top and will have a huge chance to become an immortal. As for the others, they will obtain no benefits or rewards. The little girl you saw just before is the Hu Immortal Inheritance. As long as you ascend to the peak first, you will become her master and obtain the Gu Immortal Inheritance."

Fang Zheng ran while gazing at the peak.

He had lived in Southern Border and there were many mountains there, he naturally knew the logic of the mountain 'appearing close but was actually very far away'.

"Master, I am very far away from this crystal mountain while they are already climbing it. The gap is too huge. I also cannot use movement Gu, how can I win?"

Lord Sky Crane snorted: "Ignorant! This is Hu Immortal blessed land, this place is not like anything else! Although Hu Immortal has already passed away, her will still exists. Your movement Gu has already been sealed by Hu Immortal's will, naturally you can't use it. Others are also the same, they can't use any Gu. You can only rely on your own physical strength to ascend to the peak and finish this test."

Fang Zheng could not help being dispirited: "I can't use movement Gu and there is such a huge gap, how can I catch up to them? Strange, we entered the gatehouse one after another, how could the gap be so huge?"

Lord Sky Crane laughed: "This is a Gu Immortal blessed land, the time flow here is different. A day in the outside world is five days here. You guys entered the gatehouse one by one and the time difference was short. But once you enter here, the time difference is suddenly pulled apart. Otherwise, why would there be the great competition to decide the ranking? Each rank represents a certain advantage. The last ranked person basically doesn't have any hope to win."

"So it was like that." Fang Zheng only then realized the importance of obtaining a good ranking in the great competition.

Unfortunately, he lacked power and his strength could not compare to others.

The ten great sects were the heads of Central Continent, they had a lot of hidden talents with extremely profound foundations. Even Southern Border's top clans could not compare to them. In this generation of elite disciples, disciples like Fang Zheng, Fairy Bi Xia, Gu Ting and Wei Wu Shang were only second tier.

The first tier were disciples like Feng Jin Huang, Ying Sheng Ji and Xiao Qi Xing. They had powerful background and the support of Gu Immortals. From the very start, they received meticulous nurturing. A huge amount of resources were provided to them, with them never lacking anything, and occasionally, Gu Immortal level existences would personally instruct and guide them in their cultivation.

Comparatively speaking, Fang Zheng was only a countryside boy. Although he had some fortuitous encounters, they could not compare to the support of Gu Immortals.

"My ranking is not high, I can't do anything about. I already given my best in the great competition, almost all of my ironbeak flying cranes have died." Fang Zheng felt regret and also helplessness.

As he kept on thinking, he suddenly felt something amiss.

"Master, since Gu worms cannot be used here, how come you are able to talk to me? Master, you still had this secret, you are really amazing!"

"Hahaha..." Lord Sky Crane could not help but laugh loudly, "Stupid disciple, you finally realized this? But you are overestimating your master. I was only a rank five while alive and after death, my soul is residing in the spirit incubating flea, I have nothing left. The reason I can talk to you is because of our Immortal Crane Sect's Supreme Elder Lord He Feng Yang! Fang Zheng, you need to remember, in this world, only Gu Immortals can contend with Gu Immortals."

"Supreme Elder He Feng Yang?" Fang Zheng was filled with shock, Immortal Crane Sect had many Gu Immortals. Among them was He Feng Yang, to think he would be somewhat involved with him.

Lord Sky Crane meaningfully said: "Fang Zheng, Hu Immortal Inheritance is not a small matter, it has a land spirit. That is to say, this blessed land has its own will! Even a Gu Immortal can't get through force. Land spirits are innocent and stubborn, inheriting their original master's obsession. If a Gu Immortal forcefully attacks, even if the land spirit can't resist it, it could choose to self-destruct and destroy the blessed land. The Gu Master that made the forceful attack would also suffer injuries in vain and would have disastrous losses, and all their efforts would become futile. Thus, they sent you elite disciples."

"In this great competition, Feng Jin Huang from Spirit Affinity House is truly amazing! This girl could be said to be a genius among geniuses, arrogantly looking down at the crowd, a phoenix among people. Your strength is inadequate and it is normal for you to be defeated by her. But our Immortal Crane Sect has not necessarily lost. You are our Immortal Crane Sect's hope for reversal!"

"Me?" Fang Zheng could not help opening his eyes wide as he had never expected there to be such a huge hope entrusted to him.

He suddenly realized.

This contest for Hu Immortal Inheritance looked like a contest among the elite disciples of the ten sects, but actually was the battle between the ten great sects. Disciples like him were the chess pieces while the Gu Immortals of the ten sects were the players; they arranged the pieces from behind the scenes and contested against each other.

And he himself was the ignorant secret weapon chosen by the Immortal Crane Sect.

"Master, isn't the sect having too much expectations for me? I can't use any Gu now, how can I be the winner?"

"Hehehe..." Lord Sky Crane proudly laughed, "Fang Zheng, do you know what this crystal mountain is? This is the Dang Hun mountain in the legends of Ren Zu.

"Dang Hun mountain!" Fang Zheng gave a startled cry.

Legends of Ren Zu had spread over the world, Fang Zheng naturally knew of this famous Dang Hun mountain.

Lord Sky Crane continued: "As long as any living creatures enter the range of Dang Hun mountain, their soul would receive a shock. The closer they get to the peak, the stronger the force of the shock would be. Many living beings don't have strong souls and their soul would often scatter when they reach halfway up the mountain."

"Naturally, this is a righteous path inheritance and isn't as dangerous as a demonic path inheritance. Dang Hun mountain's might has already been suppressed by the land spirit, giving you elite disciples a chance of ascending to the peak. If someone is unable to continue, they would be sent out by the land spirit. That is to say, there is no risk to your lives."

Lord Sky Crane's tone became solemn: "Fang Zheng, the thing I am about to say is very important, listen carefully!"

"You experienced the destruction of your entire clan at a young age and the killer was your own big brother. You are determined to take revenge and your will is firm. Surviving this terrible event had tempered your soul to become stronger than your peers. But there is still a gap when compared to people like Feng Jin Huang and Xiao Qi Xing."

"But you don't need to be dejected, the ingenuity of Lord He Feng Yang's plan lies here. He used secret methods to resuscitate Spirit Incubating Flea. Next, I will use my soul to support you and push you towards the peak of Dang Hun mountain!"

Lord Sky Crane was a rank five Gu Master, he had gone through innumerable difficulties throughout his life and at the same time with his long age, he had gained plentiful experience and the strength of his soul naturally far surpassed the disciples like Feng Jin Huang and Xiao Qi Xing.

These geniuses might be at their prime with limitless future prospects, but right now, the foundation of their soul could not compare to Lord Sky Crane.

Fang Zheng was both happy and worried: "With master's help, I have a chance at winning. But if we cheat like this, won't it be unfair? If other Gu Immortals discover it, what would we do?"

Lord Sky Crane snorted and reprimanded: "Stupid kid, this is not cheating but ability and talent. We are obtaining the Gu Immortal Inheritance with our ability and talent. This is fair! Don't worry, behind you is Immortal Crane Sect, and with Lord He Feng Yang protecting you, other Gu Immortals won't act against you. Moreover, Gu Immortals can't enter the blessed land. If they enter the blessed land, they will suffer the counterattack from the land spirit, thus even if they discover some clues, they can only watch helplessly! Hahaha!"

"The land spirit is so amazing? Even Gu Immortals are not its match?" Fang Yuan felt surprised.

"One side will go all out while the other side has to restrain themselves... Moreover, land spirit has blended in with the blessed land, and in the blessed land, land spirit is an immortal deity able to control the whole blessed land. Controlling the land spirit means controlling the blessed land." Lord Sky Crane laughed.

Realization dawned upon Fang Zheng: "Ah! I understand, that little girl we saw is the land spirit!"

"Hahaha!" Lord Sky Crane laughed, "Disciple, you aren't so stupid after all, finally realizing it. That's right, that little girl is Hu Immortal land spirit. Now charge forward bravely. This Dang Hun mountain is extremely difficult to climb, it would at least take a year or so. Just in case, I won't speak much from now and will only secretly help you. With my help, you have at least eighty percent chance of seizing Hu Immortal Inheritance! As long as you get the Hu Immortal Inheritance, you can rise rapidly, turning from beggar to tycoon and become fat from just one bite. This is ascending to the heavens in one step!"

"I understand, master! I will do my very best and not disappoint you!" Fang Zheng's fierce eyes flashed with a firm and courageous light.

"Go, the whole Immortal Crane Sect is looking at you." Lord Sky Crane spurred Fang Zheng on with one sentence and made his blood boil.

Fang Zheng felt extremely energetic!

Chapter 367: It is not easy to be a godfather these days

Several months later.

Southern Border, San Cha mountain.

In a spacious cave lighted with bright lights, a huge banquet was being held where Gu Masters drank and gambled, and fragrance of various dishes permeated the air.

"Come, come, come, everyone, eat and drink to your fill, no need to feel uncomfortable!" Century Boy was sitting on the main seat; he looked around and greeted everyone with a loud voice.

Century Boy was wearing a black robe and looked like a tender boy but was actually over hundred and eighty years old.

In this world, under normal circumstances, a human's lifespan was only around a hundred years. If one wanted to increase their lifespan, the best method was to find lifespan Gu.

However, lifespan Gu were extremely rare and thus difficult to find.

Humans were the spirit of all living beings, who would mind having a long life? Thus, they thought of many other methods.

Century Boy was one such example, although he did not find lifespan Gu, he possessed return to childhood Gu, which accumulated his lifeforce and slowly released them, gaining the effect of longevity.

The disadvantage of this method was his body and appearance were fixed to have a child's physique.

Century Boy had rank four upper stage cultivation and at the same time possessed over a hundred and eighty years of experience, he was truly a part of the senior generation of demonic path.

He had become astute with age and had visited a lot of places. He liked holding feasts and entertaining all kinds of people. Sometimes, he also gave pointers to some newcomers and imparted some of his experience. In the demonic path, he had the reputation of guiding the younger generation.

Some demonic Gu Masters who received his pointers recognized him as their godfather. As time passed, Century Boy had gathered a whole group of godsons and goddaughters, forming a rather enormous force.

Among those participating in the banquet today, many were his godsons and goddaughters. There were also distinguished guests like Rock Lizard Li Qiang and Fiery Star Bao Tong; they were all famous demonic path figures and could not be underestimated.

"Shang clan's Yi Huo is truly powerful, he suppressed the other four rank four peak stage experts. Currently on San Cha mountain, no one wants to fight him."

"Gu refinement grandmaster Feng Tian Yu has arrived and has agreed to refine Gu for Yi Huo. I am not sure what Gu he is refining but Yi Huo's fighting strength is sure to become more powerful."

In the banquet, the most talked discussion was naturally about the current situation of San Cha mountain.

Yi Huo came from Shang clan and represented the righteous path. His power and influence was huge, suppressing all the demonic Gu Masters on San Cha mountain; they could not even fight properly as they were fearful.

"Yi Huo might be strong, but he is only rank four peak stage. If Tie Ba Xiu was still alive, he could definitely contend with him and Yi Huo would not have been in such a bright limelight like now."

The moment Tie Ba Xiu was mentioned, everyone inevitably thought of Fang Yuan.

"A few days ago, Little Beast King killed Yu Cang; this is the fourth strength path Gu Master he has killed in just this month." Someone whispered.

Yu Cang was a strength path Gu Master and was from Yu clan which was a small-middle sized clan.

Ever since Fang Yuan killed Tie Ba Xiu, his momentum increased tremendously and he looked for trouble again and again, killing both demonic path and righteous path Gu Masters. This awe-inspiring fierce and brutal name shook San Cha mountain.

Century Boy's ears twitched, and his expression turned unsightly when his keen sense heard 'little beast king'.

Fang Yuan killed Sky Tiger Xue San Si who was his goddaughter. He had been proclaiming he would find trouble with Fang Yuan. However, after Fang Yuan killed Tie Ba Xiu, he immediately gave in and did not talk of Fang Yuan again.

"Hmph! Little Beast King might be strong, but it is because of three kings inheritance. He knows many secrets regarding the inheritance and thus every time he enters the inheritance, his gains are much more than ours. Li Xian, you have made deals with him and know much more about his situation. Is this not the case?" Rock Lizard Li Qiang suddenly spoke loudly.

Li Xian nodded: "Indeed it is so. In these few months, Little Beast King has sold some of the secrets of three kings inheritance many times. The information he gave is mostly correct and has been verified. For example, you can disturb hairy men's Gu refinement process in the earlier stages of King Xin Inheritance. There are also some of his experiences regarding King Quan Inheritance."

"Little Beast King definitely knows much more important secrets and is hiding them deep in his heart. His luck has come, he really made it big this time, his strength has been increasing by relying on three kings inheritance. Now, he is one of the most popular candidates to inherit three kings inheritance!" Fiery Star Bao Tong said as he drank wine, his tone filled with admiration and envy.

"Fang Zheng is getting stronger and he has replaced his Gu worms to much better ones as well."

"In these few months, he and Bai Ning Bing has been moving together, they are simply a pair of wretched murderous couple! These two are villains colluding together, who knows how many have suffered from their treacherous attacks."

"Little Beast King has extremely big ambitions, from the time he arrived at San Cha mountain to now, he has repeatedly challenged strength path Gu Masters. Recently, he has again claimed to become the number one in strength path and recover the glory of the ancient strength path."

"Fortunately, I am not a strength path Gu Master...."

Everyone discussed and commented.

Fang Yuan only took the initiative to fight strength path Gu Masters, this caused strength path Gu Masters to be in danger, while Gu Masters of other paths watched on from the side with an attitude of taking joy in others' misfortune.

Although Fang Yuan's actions were unbridled, he did not provoke public anger.

On one hand, he was powerful and could also fly; truly not an easy enemy. On another hand, he took the initiative to reveal many information on three kings inheritance which caused many people to fawn upon him. Finally, he only went against strength path Gu Masters, only dealing with people of the same path, and did not blindly provoke other Gu Masters.

"Century Boy, you need to be careful. From what I remember, you are also a strength path Gu Master, right? Fang Zheng, that brute is mean and devious, and completely unreasonable, cruel and tyrannical." Rock Lizard Li Qiang stared deeply at Century Boy, seemingly persuading him with good intentions.

Century Boy sighed inwardly.

How could he have imagined Fang Yuan to be so violent!

"Sigh, each generation brings forth new geniuses... Nowadays, newcomers are appearing in flocks; a few years ago, there was Mo Wu Tian and now Little Beast King has appeared. This world is becoming increasingly tough, it is not easy to even be a godfather."

Century Boy thought like that inwardly, but on the surface he was still tough: "Hmph! When heavens want someone dead, it will first make them mad and violent. This Little Beast King is become madder and more violent, he is not far from reaching death's door. He killed my goddaughter Xue San Si, I will take revenge sooner or later. But there is no need to hurry, wait till three kings inheritance is over and I will slowly settle the scores with him. The important matter is three kings inheritance."

Saying so, he reminded his godsons and goddaughters present in the banquet: "You guys also need to understand the logic of important things first. Three kings inheritance is an opportunity that seldom appears in a hundred years. You need to grasp it as much as possible or else you will regret it for your lifetime."

What he meant was: You guys better avoid any conflicts with Little Beast King.

"Godfather is right."

"Godfather's words are reasonable and thought-provoking. Revenge is a dish best served cold!"

"This Little Beast King won't be able to keep bouncing for long, he killed Tie Ba Xue and chased Tie clan's young master. We will talk after he is hunted down by Tie clan."

"I heard people saying Tie clansmen have already secretly arrived at San Cha mountain..."

"Godfather, wait till my cultivation reaches rank four, there won't be a need for godfather to make a move, I will be able to deal with Little Beast King!"

"Little Beast King won't remain proud for long, under my thunderclap Gu, there won't even be a corpse left of him!"

...

These goddaughters and godsons talked one after another; some expressed great loyalty and said they would go through any difficulties for Century Boy. Some even fawned saying it was not worth for Century Boy to deal with Fang Yuan. Some judged the situation and bluntly said Fang Yuan's joy would not last long.

"Alright, alright, you are my godchildren. It was not in vain for me to have guided you!" Century Boy laughed loudly.

Right at this time, a voice suddenly came in from outside the cave.

"Century Boy, I am Fang Zheng, get out!"

The merrymaking just before, the clamorous banquet suddenly turned into deathly quietness.

Little Beast King!

How could he come find trouble here?!

Everyone's eyes opened wide and looked at each other in shock.

This was especially the case with Century Boy and his godsons and goddaughters; they were all stupefied and did not know what to do, not daring to utter a word.

"Right, this is Little Beast King's voice, it seems he really came." Li Xian held back his smile and broke the silence.

Rock Lizard Li Qiang, Fiery Star Bao Tong and others all put their wine cups down with grave expressions.

Crash! Century Boy smashed his wine cup on the table, then he gritted his teeth and shouted to the outside: "Little Beast King, I am here, what can I do for you?"

Fang Yuan's voice immediately came from outside the cave: "Hmph, Century Boy, you held such a huge banquet and invited all the heroes, but you actually didn't invite me? Are you looking down on me? You don't need to apologize, it is already too late for apologies. Since you are also a strength path Gu Master, then come out and exchange moves with me."

When Century Boy heard this, he was startled, indignant and furious.

Fang Yuan's appearance made him startled. Fang Yuan's brashness made him indignant. And Fang Yuan's such words that made it seem like Century Boy was really going to apologize made him angry.

However, Century Boy did not want to fight to the death with Fang Yuan. He looked around and shouted with a furious tone: "Little Beast King, don't be too insolent! You came here to find trouble and have no consideration for anyone, you are simply looking down on all the numerous heroes here. I will tell you honestly, Lord Rock Lizard Li Qiang is here, there is also Lord Fiery Star Bao Tong and also young master Li Xian who is an emerging talent of the demonic path. Are you here to court death?"

With these words, everyone in the banquet had different expressions, inwardly cursing this treacherous Century Boy who wanted to pull them down with him.

However, Fang Yuan said: "Century Boy, you coward, the people you have invited are all heroes, but I can clearly tell you that I came to find trouble. But not with others, I came to find trouble especially with you! I want to recover the glory and the radiance of the ancient strength path. You are a puny coward who is damaging the name of the strength path, come out and accept your death."

Li Qiang's grave expression immediately relaxed at these words.

Fang Yuan explained his purpose for coming clearly, it was directed at Century Boy and this let his mind slightly relax.

"I did not think Lord Little Beast King knew our names." Bao Tong stroked his beard with a satisfied expression.

Li Xian laughed darkly and looked at Century Boy with every intention to watch indifferently from the sidelines.

Century Boy had become astute with age, his expression immediately sunk when he saw everyone's expressions.

Chapter 368: Tearing the boy apart

As Fang Yuan scolded over there, Century Boy's chest was burning with anger, thinking: "Although little beast king is strong, the reason he killed Tie Ba Xiu was due to the flying ability's advantage. He is so young, I have eaten more salt than he has eaten rice, as long as I focus on defense, and not act recklessly, I will not be in any mortal danger."

Being in public, Century Boy could only forcefully keep up a facade. If he avoided battle here, the reputation and fame he worked hard to earn for many years would be ruined at once.

"But if I really cannot take it, I can still escape back to the cave. There are so many people here at the banquet, Fang Zheng would not dare to barge in. But what truly angers me is, what these people said earlier were nice words, but at the crucial moment, none of them are dependable!"

Century Boy stared at his godson and goddaughters, feeling upset and disappointed.

Speaking of which, among these godsons and daughters of his, only Xue San Si had the highest cultivation, and was the most outstanding among them, but Fang Yuan killed her already.

"Little beast king, you are too arrogant and overbearing, today I will let you learn that older people are wiser!" Century Boy walked out of the cave, screaming furiously at Fang Yuan.

He looked like a child, but his tone was old and experienced, it was a weird sight.

"Cut the crap, receive my move!" Fang Yuan saw Century Boy walk out and laughed coldly, taking a huge step forward, like a tiger descending the mountain, charging forward with a burst of wind.

All-out effort Gu!

At once, beast phantoms appeared and caused Fang Yuan's strength to increase sharply.

Bam bam bam...

Sounds of punches and kicks were heavy and continuously.

Outside the cave, two strength path Gu Masters tangled together. They were close range fighters, every attack hit the target as they competed with brute force.

After a while, they had battled over a hundred steps away, everywhere they rampaged through, mountain rocks broke, trees toppled, dust and twigs flew in the air.

The Gu Masters in the banquet had left the cave, watching the battle.

Bitter strength Gu!

Fang Yuan gave up on defending, the more injured he got, the more strength he could exert.

Moo!

Suddenly, there was the sound of a bullcry as a large green bull phantom appeared above his head.

This green bull has a huge body, twice the size of an elephant, its back was raised highly, thick and solid, and full of green moss.

This was the mutated beast kunlun[1] bull, having the same status as Biao, dragon-elephant, thunder boar and rock crocodile!

Fang Yuan exerted the strength of a kunlun bull!

This strike was heavy, as the air exploded, emitting a thunderous roar.

Century Boy was unable to guard in time, sent flying as his tiny body was like a ball, crashing through more than ten trees before stopping.

He coughed out a mouthful of blood, staring fiercely at Fang Yuan.

To think it is the kunlun bull strength, little beast king's strength rose again!

"Century Boy, I killed your goddaughter Xue San Si, didn't you want revenge? Today, I will give you the chance." Fang Yuan smiled mockingly, charging again.

"Little beast king, you are too arrogant, watch this!" Century Boy was red with anger, white smoke coming out of his eyebrows.

He received Fang Yuan's attack but did not counterattack.

Century Boy was a demonic figure who had lived for over two hundred years, he had his abilities, and many trump cards.

When he truly unleashed his strength, Fang Yuan started to feel pressured, on the verge of falling into a disadvantage.

Strength Qi Gu!

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's shoulder shrugged, and a trace of strength qi shot out.

Thunder boar phantom entered the strength qi and turned solid, charging towards Century Boy.

Century Boy could only avoid the attack, as Fang Yuan starting attacking furiously behind the thunder boar. Century Boy's counterattack vanished like smoke.

Fang Yuan's battle experience became more and more rich, and his mastery of this set of Gu worm rose.

Before, he could not use strength qi Gu while attacking at close range, but now after tens of matches, he could coordinate his own body and his beast phantoms perfectly.

Thunder boar charged bravely, smashing rocks and mounds along the way. Rock crocodile was tough, using its tail like a steel whip, and its teeth like razors, it was a ferocious beast. Kunlun bull had brute force and horn attacks, its back was like tough mountain rocks. These three beast phantoms, once activated, caused Century Boy to feel extremely outpaced as he hurriedly defended himself.

Solid beast phantoms were the biggest threat to Century Boy. But after the beast phantom was destroyed, it turned back into a trace of strength qi.

When Fang Yuan activates the strength qi Gu again, the beast phantom would appear good as new.

"Thankfully, little beast king's three beast phantoms can only be unleashed through luck. His all-out effort Gu is still rank three, it cannot summon these beast phantoms!"

Century Boy was suppressed by Fang Yuan, but he felt glad secretly.

Although Fang Yuan swapped his boar, crocodile, and green bull phantoms to thunder boar, rock crocodile, and kunlun bull phantoms, it caused his overall strength to rise but there was weaknesses.

His all-out effort Gu was only rank three, it could not summon these three rank four phantoms at will.

That is, unless Fang Yuan gets the undefeated hundred battles Gu from King Xin's inheritance, and raise the all-out effort Gu to rank four.

"Godfather's situation is getting worse. Do we strike?"

"Do you want to die? They are fighting so intensely, before we even join in, we will be turned into meat paste!"

"Strong, way too strong. Among us, only Sky Tiger can contest, but she was killed by Fang Zheng long ago."

"Do we just watch like this?"

"What are you scared of? Is godfather so easy to deal with? He has his trump cards left!"

Outside the cave, Century Boy's godsons and daughters saw the intense battle and were trembling with fear, their limbs turning cold.

Century Boy had a tiny body, his fighting style was to find loopholes and dodge everywhere, he liked to aim at crucial areas, when he punches and kicks, it forms an impact.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan attacked directly, punching and kicking, his arms like long spears while his legs were like large poles. At times, he caused explosive sounds when he attacked, giving off a dominating aura.

Century Boy was suppressed gradually, and his moving space shrunk.

These few months, Fang Yuan had improved in terms of Gu worms.

Not only did he turn green bull into kunlun bull phantom, he also finished using essence iron bones Gu, and raised the toughness of his bones again, to about twice or thrice of before.

Other than these, he also used the golden steel tendon Gu, turning his body tendons into the hardness of golden steel.

Ancient bronze skin, essence iron bones, golden steel tendons...

The three defenses molded into one, complementing each other as Fang Yuan's defense rose sharply. Combined with the golden shield Gu, it was enough to handle the full strength of a rank four peak stage Gu Master!

Century Boy was getting more frightened as he fought: "This little beast king, why is he so experienced?! I had the lower-hand at the start, and I tried to reverse the situation, but I did not succeed once! Is he still a young man? How can such a person be around twenty years old?"

Century Boy thought about himself when he was twenty, compared to Fang Yuan, he felt that he had lived a dog's life all these years!

"No, I must retreat, this little beast king cannot be assessed by human standards. No wonder Tie Ba Xiu died in his hands, up till now, he has not used the bone wings Gu yet!

Century Boy was suppressed by Fang Yuan, not even able to catch a breath. After thinking about it, he wanted to retreat.

He turned his body, towards the cave.

"Century Boy, are you afraid?" Fang Yuan activated charging crash Gu, chasing relentlessly.

"Century Boy, with me here, where do you think you can go?" Bai Ning Bing suddenly jumped into the battlefield, blocking Century Boy's path.

"You!" Century Boy's attention was on Fang Yuan, how would he expect Bai Ning Bing to appear right beside him, and strike an underhanded move? Caught off guard, he was hit by Bai Ning Bing's attack head-on and lost his bearings.

Fang Yuan did not give up such a good chance, unleashing a flurry of attacks.

And his luck was finally shining, as thunder boar, rock crocodile, and kunlun bull, the three great phantoms all appeared at once.

The great strength surged like a wave, flooding Century Boy like the attack of the sea.

Century Boy did not even manage to scream out before Fang Yuan grabbed both his legs and tore him in half.

"AHHH!"

"Godfather, you died a pitiful death..."

"Lord Century Boy!!"

At once, everyone screamed in shock, as blood spewed, bones broke, and organs fell on the ground.

"Hahah, so much for Century Boy, you are nothing much." Fang Yuan laughed as he raised his head, showing off an extreme arrogance.

Blood poured on his face as he stared at the people in front of him, shouting unhappily: "Why are you being so noisy, Century Boy ran away at the last moment, timid like a rat, he is a disgrace to the strength path, he deserved death!"

Suddenly, his expression eased, laughing: "Everyone here is a smart person and did not help this shameless rat. Come, let's go in and drink. Li Xian, do you want the information regarding the three kings inheritance? I still have a deal with you."

Everyone was shocked, worried, and also curious.

Shock was because Fang Yuan was like a demonic god incarnate, killing another famous person and showing off a greater strength.

Worry was because Fang Yuan killed people like cutting grass, he had just killed a person, but the next moment he started laughing, talking about life, he did not care about human lives at all. Being with such a person, anyone would feel intense pressure.

Curious was because Fang Yuan knew the three kings inheritance's secret, and wanted to deal with Li Xian. Could they get some information regarding the three kings inheritance from him?

Everyone had a complex thought and could not decide.

Fang Yuan walked briskly side by side with Bai Ning Bing into the cave.

The people blocking the cave subconsciously gave way to them.

Fang Yuan stepped into the banquet, and sat at the host's seat, this was originally Century Boy's seat.

"All of you sit down, no need to be polite. Whoever dares to leave, is not giving me, Little Beast King, face!" Fang Yuan looked at everyone as he threatened fiercely.

Rock Lizard Li Qiang, Fiery Star Bao Tong, and others were only rank four upper stage, they did not dare to speak although enraged, sitting down.

Under the cold silence, everyone looked at each other, worried that Fang Yuan would start killing again, they could only sit down.

Fang Yuan squinted as he showed a smile: "Since everyone respects me, I shall give you some benefits."

Immediately after, he casually gave an information, regarding the life-saving token in the three kings inheritance.

Everyone heard it and their eyes shone, memorising this information to heart.

[1] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kunlun_(mythology) Back

Chapter 369: Understanding of the Demonic Path

"So there was such a chance at retreating in the three kings inheritance. If I obtain the token, I can move without restraint and wouldn't have to retreat early," Bao Tong lamented.

Li Qiang took the initiative to raise his wine cup and toasted Fang Yuan, "Lord Little Beast King's words are truly worth a thousand gold. I raise this wine cup to congratulate sire for killing Century Boy, this scum of the strength path!"

Tea cools down as soon as the person is gone; Li Qiang had been talking so closely with Century Boy just before, but now the person had been changed to Fang Yuan, he immediately changed his words and called Century Boy the scum.

"Hahaha, you flatter me." Fang Yuan, however, did not raise his wine cup, but looked at the godchildren of Century Boy and impatiently waved, "Today, I have exterminated the source of evil and my mood is also good, so I will give you guys a way out. If you don't want to stay, then get lost. Get lost, get lost, don't block my view!"

With Century Boy's death, these godsons and goddaughters were already feeling anxious and frightened, and could not help looking at each other when they heard Fang Yuan.

"What? You want to stay and try to kill me?" Fang Yuan indifferently smiled.

Immediately, there was an uproar, many people left awkwardly and the cave was instantly empty by half.

However, among the godchildren of Century Boy, some still remained.

"Lord Fang Zheng, you are my benefactor!" A godson suddenly kneeled and yelled with tears and snot falling down, "I was forced by that bastard Century Boy to take him as father, Lord Little Beast King, your dominance shakes the world and your aura overwhelms the lands, you have rescued me, you are my great savior!"

"Lord Little Beast King, your power has thoroughly subdued my heart, please let me stay and serve you." A beautiful goddaughter pleaded alluringly.

"Lord Little Beast King, you have rescued me from a disaster, I will never forget your great kindness. You have given me new life, please let me call you godfather!" An old man in his seventies kneeled on the ground and passionately shouted.

Thump thump thump.

Immediately, in front of Fang Yuan was a scene of kneeling people.

With Century Boy, the head of this group's, death, his force immediately collapsed. Many escaped while a portion looked for an alternative way out and wanted to rely on Fang Yuan.

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan laughed loudly, "Your words are really pleasant to the ears, good, good."

The group of godchildren immediately showed a joyous expression.

However, Fang Yuan's smile suddenly stopped as he turned grim, he shouted: "A group of bootlickers! Killing is killing, crime is crime, why are you speaking of great kindness! I scorn this type of hypocritical praise. I like killing people, I like commiting crimes, listen, how direct is this, how pure is it. Screw off you lot, if you want to take revenge, then accumulate your strength, I will wait for you to challenge me!"

The godchildren were shocked, frightened and stupefied.

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan snorted and with a shift of his mind, a beast phantom charged forward, killing one person on the spot.

The rest seemed to have startled awake; screams could be heard as they hurried to escape from the cave in a pathetic state and even pissed themselves.

The remaining Gu Masters all had unsightly looks.

Fang Yuan was very temperamental and easily killed people, causing the people around him to feel great pressure. Although Century Boy was hateful, he was many times more lovable when compared to Fang Yuan.

Only Bai Ning Bing's expression was tranquil as water; she was sitting on the left of Fang Yuan with her blue eyes half closed.

Li Qiang had been raising his wine cup and still had not placed it down; right now, he forgot his embarrassment and forcefully smiled: "Lord Little Beast King, when cutting grass, you need to pull out the roots. You have let these people go, what if one day they make it big? Just to be safe, it is better to kill them all. Lord Little Beast King, it doesn't matter if you don't remember these people, I have memorized their faces. I will kill them in place of you as my thanks for the information you gave."

"No need, no need." Fang Yuan leaned back on his chair and indifferently smiled.

He had his own reasons for letting these people go, but it could not be said out loud.

Thinking for a while, Fang Yuan said: "Since I started walking on the demonic path, I have never feared offending others. As long as I continue to get stronger, what is revenge? If ten people wants revenge, I will kill ten; if a hundred people wants revenge, I will kill a hundred. If the whole world wants revenge, I will exterminate the whole world! If someone succeeds in taking revenge against me, that will mean that I am not strong enough, that I didn't try hard enough and that I neglected my cultivation; I deserve to die then!"

A terrifying light flickered in Fang Yuan's eyes as he said this, and when he swept his gaze around, he was like an evil ferocious beast that no one dared to match his gaze.

"Little Beast King is ruthless to others, but is even more ruthless to himself!"

"This Fang Zheng's demonic nature is too strong! Not fearing revenge, not fearing death, placing his own life and death out of his considerations..."

"Fang Zheng is crazy, his mind is not normal. Making an enemy out of him will be a nightmare!"

Everyone that heard Fang Yuan felt their hearts go cold.

Fang Yuan succeeded in intimidating everyone and did not take it too far, and smiled: "Let's drink."

Everyone raised their wine cups with trembling hands, they felt like they were accompanying a man-eating tiger and were in danger; the originally fine wine felt tasteless.

But following immediately, Fang Yuan again talked of three kings inheritance and revealed many secrets.

Everyone was engrossed, their breathing started becoming rough in excitement as they listened to the secrets.

Only Li Xian was worried and bewildered: "What is this Little Beast King planning? He is actually revealing such precious information, what is he after?"

The banquet lasted over two hours.

Fang Yuan killed Century Boy and occupied his cave, even taking charge of the banquet. While others wanted more secrets, they felt their trip was not in vain.

When they got out of the cave, they even felt reluctant to leave and wanted to listen to even more news from the cave entrance.

As for the original host of the banquet, Century Boy, his torn corpse was still on the ground and its blood had already seeped into the ground. The deathly white bones gave a cold shine under the moonlight.

Everyone chatted and laughed, and as they walked past the corpse, no one threw a glance at this loser.

This was the ending of the defeated in the demonic path.

Losers are always in the wrong.

All demonic Gu Masters, more or less, had such a common understanding.

...

Light rain fell from the sky and made pitter-patter sounds.

The sky was gloomy and the wind blew coldly.

The light rain fell on a young girl's hair, shoulders, back and finally, her whole body.

"Young master Ruo Nan, the dead cannot be brought back, my condolences to you." The head of Tie clan's four old-timers stood behind the girl and persuaded her with a concerned voice.

But the girl did not speak, the eyes that were as bright as stars before lost its spirit and looked hollow, there was no longer a resolute and sharp gaze.

Tie Ruo Nan looked at the tombstones in front of her in a daze.

These tombstones were cut from the mountain stones and the names of the ones that slept under were carved on them.

Tie Mu, Tie Dao Ku, Tie Xian Hua, Tie Ao Kai, Tie Ba Xiu...

Each of these names could relate to the brightest and most profound memories in the depths of Tie Ruo Nan's heart.

However, the companions who walked alongside her and fought side by side had become cold corpses within the ground. Similar to Tie Ruo Nan's heart, they would never have a trace of warmth.

"It is I who harmed you, I didn't fulfill the duty of a leader!"

"You all died, but I am alive by myself. I am a coward..."

"This is all a nightmare, father, I have blemished your name."

Tie Ruo Nan fell into deep self-blame, besides this, there were also regret and bewilderment.

This genius worked hard to climb up after experiencing her father's death, and was like a slowly ascending star of the righteous path who received blessings and attention of countless people.

But in the battle several months ago, Fang Yuan personally dropped this star into the abyss; she became a meteorite that smashed into a gloomy corner and was full of cracks.

"Sigh...." The head of the Tie clan's four old-timers, Tie Xuan Zhi, looked at the thin and weak figure of the young girl in the rain, and heaved out a long sigh.

However right at this time, an aged voice suddenly came from behind him: "It has been several months already, this child Ruo Nan is still like this?"

Tie Xuan Zhi was startled and frightened!

Who was it, they got so near but he did not sense it at all!

At that instant, the hair on his body stood up and he turned around quickly and subconsciously tried to attack.

However, a wizened hand softly touched his shoulder and a voice followed at the same time: "Xuan Zhi, compose yourself."

Tie Xuan Zhi immediately felt his whole body turn stiff, the surging primeval sea in his aperture was suppressed by a formidable and formless force.

It was like a high mountain had suddenly been suppressed.

The grand head of the Tie clan's four old-timers, the rank four upper stage Tie Xuan Zhi, could not budge even a bit at this moment, his whole body seemed to be confined like an insect trapped within amber!

But when he saw the appearance of the person, Tie Xuan Zhi's terror and despair immediately turned into ecstasy.

"Ah, old clan leader!" Tie Xuan Zhi blurted out.

The wizened old man who was standing in front of him was Tie clan's previous generation clan leader, Tie Mu Bai!

"I have already abdicated as clan leader. Now I am also not an elder, Xuan Zhi, you can just call me Mu Bai." The old man gently waved his hand and smiled.

"Impossible, how could junior dare to call your great name!" Tie Xuan Zhi bowed his back deeply and greeted the old man respectfully.

Towards the old man in front of him, Tie Xuan Zhi was filled with reverence and admiration.

"Name is only a name, the name Tie Mu Bai was meant to be used. There is nothing inappropriate." The old man spoke calmly, vicissitudes of life were reflected in his eyes and he had already seen through fame and fortune.

Tie Xuan Zhi wanted to speak but the old man slightly waved his hand and walked forward slowly toward Tie Ruo Nan.

He stood in front of the tombstones with his back facing Tie Ruo Nan. He then gently caressed the stele and sighed: "Tie clansmen are buried at the place they die. This is the rule of Tie clan since it was established. Do you know why?"

Tie Ruo Nan was still kneeling on the ground and showed no expression as if she did not hear anything.

The old man continued: "Because to Tie clansmen, dying in the battlefield is the greatest honor! Tie Ba Xiu, Tie Mu, Tie Dao Ku, Tie Xian Hua, Tie Ao Kai, these people were the same, your father Tie Xue Leng was also the same. In the future when I die, it will also be the same. And when you die, it will still be the same."

Chapter 370: The Glory of Tie clan

Tie Ruo Nan's eyes twitched and she slowly raised her head to look at this unacquainted but very familiar old man.

"Our Tie clan, since it was established, had been world-renowned for our bravery, unswerving determination and our iron-cold justice. For many generations, Tie clansmen had been upholding justice and striking down on criminals, in this course, countless people have shed blood and sacrificed their lives. The youths that have died here won't be the first and also won't be the last. Do you understand?" The old man continued.

Tie Ruo Nan slightly opened her mouth as if to say something but could not speak anything.

"I am gratified because these people did not die in vain. But I also feel disappointed because you are living in vain. Tie Ruo Nan, do you know the criminal is still out there, getting away with his crimes, and still harming people. That little beast king Fang Zheng..."

Tie Mu Bai paused here and then turned around and looked at Tie Ruo Nan, indifferently asking: "Do you want to uphold justice?"

Tie Ruo Nan looked at this old man and finally recognized his identity.

Tie Mu Bai, rank five peak stage! Tie clan's previous generation clan leader, he moved unhindered in Southern Border and had dominated a region. When he was reigning, Tie clan was like an iron bucket that pressed down on Wu clan, Shang clan and other great clans, and became one of the heads of the righteous path, causing terror to the demonic path!

Tie Ruo Nan's deathly-still eyes suddenly twinkled with a spark, and she squeezed out a word with her hoarse voice: "Yes."

"Good." The old man nodded, his gaze gentle and his tone as calm as before, "Starting now, I will impart the metal path to you, the Gu path that our Tie clan's Gu Masters use to stand on top of Southern Border."

Eight days later...

Three kings inheritance opened once again; red, yellow and blue, three enormous light pillars pierced through the clouds and were visible even from thousands of miles away.

However, San Cha mountain was a scene of stillness with no sound.

Regardless of righteous path or demonic path, countless people looked at the peak - there, a seemingly ordinary wizened old man with grizzled hair and wrinkles all over his face was standing calmly with his hands behind his back.

Not far from him, Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian, Long Qing Tian, Yi Chong and Wu Shen Tong had dark expressions.

Just a moment ago, this old man suppressed the combined power of these five. He defeated them with no difficulty.

"Powerful, truly powerful!"

"Tie Mu Bai, Tie clan's previous generation clan leader, was actually still alive!!"

"Too fearsome, is this the power of rank five peak stage? Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian and others simply cannot compare. It would be as easy as crushing ants for him to kill us!"

"Who could have expected Tie clan to actually send their old clan leader. With this, Shang clan, Wu clan and every other clans are not Tie clan's match!"

"This is an expert of the old generation, little beast king is not worthy to even carry his shoes. In those days, when he moved unhindered in Southern Border, under his command, Tie clan gained powerful momentum and even suppressed Wu clan and almost became the sole head of righteous path!"

"He is one of the most powerful clan leaders in Tie clan history. He is the glory of Tie clan, a role model of the righteous path and the symbol of justice. His battle accomplishments shines brilliantly and hasn't lost its color even today!"

After a short moment of silence, there was an uproar on San Cha mountain; sounds of admiration, cheers and terror.

With Tie Mu Bai's appearance, the power structure on San Cha mountain completely changed.

Three days later, news made its way out.

Originally, Divine Thief Lu Zuan Feng caused havoc in Tie clan and secretly infiltrated Demonic Suppression Tower multiple times, in the end disturbing Tie Mu Bai who had closed himself in cultivation.

Tie Mu Bai personally struck and even though Lu Zuan Feng was a famous divine thief and also a rank five Gu Master, he received serious injuries and had a very narrow escape.

After Tie clan settled this, their gaze gathered at San Cha mountain.

Tie Ba Xiu's death angered all Tie clan higher-ups. And just as they were about to send an expert over to reinforce the four old-timers, Tie Mu Bai said he was going to personally make a visit.

He came to San Cha mountain and with his absolute strength, he easily prevailed over the experts of both righteous and demonic path. Even experts at the level of Yi Huo and Kong Ri Tian had to concede defeat.

"From this day onwards, no demonic Gu Master may enter three kings inheritance." Tie Mu Bai stood at the peak of the mountain and after winning over the five rank four peak stage Gu Masters, he immediately made the announcement.

With just himself, he swept up all the demonic Gu Masters on San Cha mountain!

Demonic Gu Masters were very angry, however even though they were thousands in number, they did not dare to rebel against the rank five peak stage Tie Mu Bai, this supreme expert who stood at the peak of the mortal world.

On that day, Kong Ri Tian and Long Qing Tian directly left the mountain with dark expressions.

Then, Li Xian, Hu Mei Er and others also left sadly.

"The laws of the heaven are vast, justice will prevail. Even if three kings inheritance is a demonic path inheritance, it will contribute its strength to our righteous path. Everyone, as long as we unite, sparks will gather little by little into a bright light that will cover the whole San Cha mountain. And no longer will there be dark places."

Tie Mu Bai spoke sincerely, then slowly stepped into the three kings inheritance.

There were huge cheers all around San Cha mountain, righteous path's morale was boosted to the top; the congratulatory sounds continued endlessly like waves after wave.

This time, the opening of the three kings inheritance lasted for more than half a month.

Tie Mu Bai changed the power structure of San Cha mountain by himself, uniting the righteous path and banishing the demonic path, causing the situation to have a violent change. The aged body seemed to manifest the domineering aura of the former clan leader of Tie clan.

Demonic path figures were all banished; they were still not resigned and thus stayed at the surroundings of San Cha mountain and watched as the three light pillars became thinner and thinner.

After the inheritance closed, Tie Mu Bai held a banquet and invited all righteous path Gu Masters.

The banquet was held in the outdoors and was spread over a vast area in the middle of the mountain. The Gu Masters used mountain rocks as tables and chairs, the aroma of wine and food spread everywhere, and they cheered and laughed.

"Junior Yi Huo proposes a toast to senior." Yi Huo stood up with a wine cup in his hands and bowed deeply towards Tie Mu Bai who was sitting on the main seat.

"In the few great clans, Shang clan always had talents appearing in large numbers. I heard Shang Yan Fei has already become the clan leader now? He had outstanding talent since young, you are also not bad. Take a seat." Tie Mu Bai said with a bit of recollection.

With his seniority, Shang Yan Fei was also a junior.

With his rank five peak stage cultivation, even though Shang Yan Fei had astonishing talent, he was still inferior.

Yi Huo could only nod his head and slowly sit down, heaving a sigh inwardly.

With Tie Mu Bai's arrival, his plan to rule San Cha mountain was already cut at its root. He was unable to catch up to this expert of the old generation and simply did not have any chance of contending with him.

"Old clan leader Tie, on behalf of Yi clan, I congratulate you on coming out of seclusion." Yi clan's elder Yi chong had a fiery temperament, but he behaved like an obedient grandson in front of Tie Mu Bai.

Gu Immortals always stayed in the background and their traces were rarely seen. To most of the people, rank four Gu Masters were feudal lords while rank five Gu Masters were the emperors that occupied the peak of the mortal world.

Tie Mu Bai coming here was an emperor going on an inspection tour; these feudal lords could only bend their backs and visit the emperor for an audience.

"Old clan leader Tie, you are the glory of our Southern Border's righteous path and are still awe-inspiring as ever! With one sentence, you made all the demonic bastards retreat helplessly, making us juniors prostrate in admiration. Unfortunately, that little bastard Fang Zheng escaped pretty fast, escaping San Cha mountain few days before you came." Wu Shen Tong said darkly.

"You are talking about little beast king, right?" Tie Mu Bai indifferently smiled without a hint of anger.

"This little kid is outstanding, I heard his accomplishments are rather amazing. He worked hard alone and started from nothing to become a rising star of the demonic path at a rapid speed. He seems impulsive and unreasonable, but actually makes his moves after meticulous planning and is very good at scheming. It was not groundless for the several youths of Tie clan to die by his hands." Tie Mu Bai continued.

His words shocked everyone present. As the victim's family, the old Tie clan leader whose dignity was offended was actually praising his enemy in front of everyone.

"This old clan leader Tie was rumored to have a fiery temperament with extreme abhorrence of evil. How come he seems to be different from the rumors, and instead is so cultured and indifferent to humiliation?" Wu Shen Tong was inwardly surprised and was just about to speak when he met with Tie Mu Bai's gaze.

The gaze contained the vicissitude of time and had unfathomable depth, a wisdom that had seen through and experienced all of the mortal world.

Wu Shen Tong immediately felt his schemes had been seen through by this gaze; cold sweat dripped out of his body and he found it difficult to speak.

"Do you find it strange?" Tie Mu Bai looked around and slowly spoke with a smile, "Why am I, who is called the glory of Tie clan, openly praising the mortal enemy of Tie clan?"

"Hehehe, praising one's enemy is increasing the enemy's prestige and diminishing one's morale. But in truth, how could the will of those resolute people be destroyed by these few words? By admiring your enemies, you can find their strong points and warn yourself of your weak points, and treat your enemy more seriously. Don't let your wisdom be deceived by hatred."

Tie Ruo Nan, who was standing behind Tie Mu Bai, shivered as she heard these words.

She knew old clan leader Tie Mu Bai was saying this mostly to her.

After Tie Mu Bai came out of inheritance, he had been guiding her all the time. He gave her metal path Gu worms and taught her his experiences in using them and also gave her knowledge on the outside world.

Don't let your wisdom be deceived by hatred... admire your enemies...

Tie Ruo Nan thought over these words and pondered.

"Ruo Nan, what do you think of Fang Zheng?" Tie Mu Bai suddenly called her.

"Yes." Tie Ruo Nan took a step forward and reported, "Although I hate him very much, I have no choice but to admit Fang Zheng is very outstanding. He has the courage to take risks and also moves after scheming. Although he is a strength path Gu Master, he definitely has a formidable and extraordinary investigative method. This point can be seen from how he was able to intercept us."

"The path elder Tie Ba Xiu and I chose was a very hidden path. We were able to deceive everyone else but only Fang Zheng was able to sense it and accurately intercept us. Old clan leader, you secretly arrived at San Cha mountain and no one knew of it, but only Fang Zheng sensed it and escaped early. Little beast king might be at the front of the limelight, but he conceals himself very deep and is absolutely not a person to be underestimated."

"Good, good analysis." Tie Mu Bai nodded, his eyes revealing his praise.

He continued: "In this world, there is a thing that is more precious than life. That is glory. Eons ago, Ren Zu's eldest son Verdant Great Sun gave up his life while chasing for glory."

"Ruo Nan, this Fang Zheng is a mission for you. Arrest him or kill him, wash away your humiliation and make it a glory that belongs to you. Many people call me the glory of Tie clan, but I will tell you Tie clan's glory is not just me alone, but you guys, generations of people who stand for what's right."

Tie Mu Bai's gaze looked at everyone present when he said this, his voice showing the grandeur of past.

"Similarly, the glory of righteous path should be upheld by every one of us. Come, drink this cup to shine the glory of righteousness onto the world, let the radiance of this sun dispel the darkness and let the demonic path cease to exist!"

"Dispel the darkness!"

"Let the demonic path cease to exist!"

All the righteous path Gu Masters raised their wine cups and shouted together. Their voices were powerful and spread a long distance; countless demonic paths figures' expressions changed.

"Damn it, this Tie Mu Bai..."

"The glory of Tie clan, time has not been able to wash away his brilliance. Really a terrifying character."

"He is dazzling like the sun... sigh, him coming out of seclusion is the bad luck of our demonic path!"

Chapter 371: Just let him fly a bit higher

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> Chapter Two, Section Three —

The sunlight of the immemorial antiquity era shone on all living beings.

Cicadas made noises, giving off the clamor of life. Dense green trees formed a large area of shade, as they swayed with the wind.

A large vat of delicious wine was in front of Verdant Great Sun, but he frowned, having no desire to drink.

"Divine travel Gu, oh divine travel Gu, you have harmed me so deeply. Right now, I do not even dare to drink wine. I am afraid of getting drunk, and end up transported to a dangerous land by you." Verdant Great Sun sighed in anguish.

The previous two times, he was sent into the ordinary abyss by divine travel Gu, as well as the cauldron of the hairy men. Thankfully he was lucky, and made it out of both the incidents alive.

Divine travel Gu said: "Prince of humans, I was not intentionally harming you. In fact, every time you got drunk, you were the one who used my power. I am innocent, in fact, I even saved your life once, didn't I?"

Divine travel Gu had in fact, saved Verdant Great Sun's life from the tiger-striped honey bees before.

Verdant Great Sun's expression was dejected: "Sigh... don't mention the past, now because of you, I do not dare to drink wine. My life has become meaningless and boring."

Hearing this, divine travel Gu felt ashamed: "In that case, let me teach you a method. Go up into the sky, and in the azure heaven among the nine heavens, there is a bamboo forest. Inside the bamboo forest, pluck a jade bamboo that is jade sky in color. Next, go to blue heaven and during the night time, collect the eight-sided diamonds inside the star fragments. Next, when it is dawn, fly into the sky and use the light of glory of the rising sun to turn me into fixed immortal travel Gu. Once I become that Gu, I will no longer send you to random places when you are drunk.

Verdant Great Sun heard this and he was overjoyed.

But he thought about it, and felt that hope was slim: "Oh Gu, I have stepped on the earth since I was born, I am not as light as clouds, nor do I have wings like birds. How can I fly into the azure heaven and pluck the jade bamboo. How can I collect the eight-sided diamonds in the star fragments? Not to mention flying towards the rising sun."

Divine travel Gu said: "That is right, humans cannot fly. But it is not a problem, we can ask wisdom Gu. It has the greatest wisdom in this world, there has to be a way."

Verdant Great Sun and wisdom Gu were old acquaintances, the reason Verdant Great Sun started drinking was because of wisdom Gu's teachings.

But wisdom Gu taught him to drink merely because it did not want to be disturbed. Sensing that Verdant Great Sun was going to find it again, wisdom Gu quickly went into hiding.

Verdant Great Sun did not find wisdom Gu, and felt dejected.

But divine travel Gu said again: "If we can't find wisdom Gu, we can find cognition Gu, it is the mother of wisdom Gu."

Verdant Great Sun quickly found cognition Gu, and requested for the methods of flying.

Cognition Gu answered: "You found the right person, because cognition is the wings of freedom. But everyone's thoughts are different, what wings you have depends on yourself."

Saying so, cognition Gu turned into a warm light and shone on Verdant Great Sun.

In the light, a pair of white pure feathered wings appeared behind Verdant Great Sun's back.

This pair of wings was very beautiful, white and pure like snow, without a trace of impurity, it was like the wings of a white crane.

Cognition Gu took a look and said: "Mm, this pair of wings is called 'self', everyone has their own 'self-cognition', this pair of wings has a high degree of flexibility and freedom. But you must be careful, do not overly bask in sunlight, otherwise, your sense of 'self' will either expand or shrink."

"Young man, you must remember my words. The higher you fly, the harder you fall." Cognition Gu thought and said the last sentence with deep meaning.

Obtaining the cognition wings named 'self', Verdant Great Sun was very happy, and flew into the sky.

He flew and flew, going higher and higher.

Humans were not born to fly, like birds soaring in the sky. This brought Verdant Great Sun great curiosity.

He played around freely in the sky, extremely happy. At the same time, he remembered cognition Gu's warning, and did not overly expose himself to sunlight.

When it was sunny, he would hide in the clouds.

Like this, Verdant Great Sun flew higher and higher, finally reaching the limits of heaven, the end of azure heaven.

There, jade bamboos grew in the air, having lustrous green leaves.

These jade bamboos were rooted in the void, and their tips also extended into the unknown void. Looking from outside, one could only see their thin long stem.

Verdant Great Sun retrieved one segment of the bamboo casually.

This dark green bamboo stem was like jade, palm-sized, and hollow in the middle, giving off a cold feeling.

Verdant Great Sun obtained the jade bamboo and was very happy, he continued flying upwards.

The sky of the immemorial antiquity era had nine levels. White heaven, red heaven, orange heaven, yellow heaven, green heaven, azure heaven, blue heaven, purple heaven, and black heaven.

Verdant Great Sun plucked the jade bamboo in azure heaven, a few days later, he flew to the higher blue heaven.

It was night time, and stars were shining the the sky. The stars flew around happily, raining down stardust. These stardust gathered into a sea, a beautiful river of light made of silver stars, flowing across the entire blue heaven.

Verdant Great Sun willed his wings, and plunged into the star river to swim.

He searched painstakingly in the endless stardust, he did not want those seven-sided or sixteen-sided fragments, he only wanted the eight-sided ones. These star fragments were like diamonds, crystal clear and flawless.

He searched for a long time before finding one.

On the second day, Verdant Great Sun flew towards the rising sun at the break of dawn.

The sunrise was like a large red lantern, emitting a warm light.

This sunlight was not ordinary, it was the light of glory, it could shine on all living beings and penetrate the river of time.

Verdant Great Sun's left hand was holding into the jade bamboo, his right hand was holding the eight-sided diamond, as he flew towards the sun and summoned divine travel Gu.

Basking under the light of glory, divine travel Gu swallowed the star fragment, and entered the jade bamboo.

"Oh Verdant Great Sun, I need time to metamorphosize and become fixed immortal travel Gu. During this period, you have to fly towards the sun, and do not leave the light of glory. But you have to be more careful, cognition Gu had said, pay attention to the 'self' wings on your back. Once my transformation ends, you should fly towards the cloud cover immediately. Do remember, remember." Divine travel Gu reminded.

Verdant Great Sun laughed heartily: "Oh Gu, rest assured. I have even survived the ordinary abyss, and lived after the hairy men, I have the reputation Gu, and have transcended vanity, the light of glory can do nothing to me."

"Then I can stop worrying." Divine travel Gu's voice weakened,as the sunlight turned into threads, forming a cocoon and wrapping the divine travel Gu and the jade bamboo.

Verdant Great Sun moved his pure white wings, flying towards the sun.

During this process, the light cocoon became thicker and heavier.

A moment later, the cocoon was burst open, and a butterfly glowing in green light flew out: "I succeeded, from today onwards, I am not divine travel Gu, but fixed immortal travel Gu. Hahaha."

Fixed immortal travel Gu flew around Verdant Great Sun, happily dancing, but suddenly shouted: "Ah, oh no! Verdant Great Sun, look at your wings!"

Under the light of the sun, Verdant Great Sun's wings had expanded to three times of its original size.

"Do not fluster, I noticed it long ago, but so what? The larger my wings, the stronger they are, and the higher and faster I can fly." Verdant Great Sun laughed loudly.

"Quickly hide in the clouds, stop flying." Fixed immortal travel Gu said worriedly.

"Don't worry, don't worry." Verdant Great Sun was not worried at all.

The 'self' wings on his back grew larger and larger, becoming even larger than his body. Verdant Great Sun's speed also became faster and faster.

"Fixed immortal travel Gu, what do you think is above the nine heavens?" He shot up towards greater altitudes.

"Stop flying, stop flying. If you fall down, I cannot save you." Fixed immortal travel Gu was very worried.

"What's the problem, how could I fall down? Look at my wings, how strong are they, how powerful are they!" Verdant Great Sun was just rebuking, when suddenly, his wings expanded to their limits, and exploded.

Losing his wings, Verdant Great Sun fell towards the ground immediately.

Eventually, he landed on the ground, as an unrecognisable grotesque corpse.

Ren Zu eldest son, met his end.

...

Southern border, Huo Tan mountain.

On the reddish-brown mountain rocks, there were some wine. Using the heat of Huo Tan mountain, the wine was kept at a certain temperature.

Sunlight shone down as Fang Yuan raised his wine cup, drinking it in one shot, sighing comfortably: "Such soothing wine, it is meant to be drank at this temperature."

Beside him, Bai Ning Bing was also sitting, but did not touch the wine, instead, staring at the direction of San Cha mountain.

There, the three light pillars shone up into the sky, shooting through the heavens.

"You are still drinking? It has been months, three kings inheritance has opened twice already. Tie Mu Bai is controlling San Cha mountain now and chased away all the demonic Gu Masters. These few months, we have been lurking on Huo Tan mountain, are we going to continue watching?" Bai Ning Bing said unhappily.

She was not afraid of death, only seeking thrills in life.

Maybe she was spurred on by the four old-timers of Tie clan, or maybe because Fang Yuan's strength had surpassed her, these few months, she had been cultivating non-stop, not caring about her rising aptitude.

"The way I see it, we can still enter the three kings inheritance, as long as he find the opportunity and wait for Tie Mu Bai to enter the inheritance, we can strike. With our strength, no one on San Cha mountain can stop us." Bai Ning Bing's words were very aggressive.

But Fang Yuan was relaxing and had a chill expression: "No worries, no rush. Tie Mu Bai is the glory of Tie clan, he is the previous clan leader, having rank five peak stage cultivation. He is such a high and mighty character. Compared to him, we are just rats under his feet. Let him fly higher, higher and higher."

Saying so, he raised his wine cup, pointing at San Cha mountain, smiling lightly as he muttered: "Come, Lord Senior Tie Mu Bai, this junior offers you a toast."

Bai Ning Bing glanced at Fang Yuan, but only saw that pair of black eyes, dark like the abyss, unfathomable.

Chapter 372: Land spirit — Afterlife of the Gu Immortal

Central continent, Hu Immortal blessed land.

A tall and large crystal mountain and river, was at the center of the blessed land.

Its name is Dang Hun mountain, pink throughout, emitting the colors of dreams and illusions.

At this moment, the elite disciples from the ten sects were like ants, trying hard to ascend the mountain.

Somewhere near the mountain waist, Fang Zheng was full of sweat, his face pale as his fingers gripped the mountain walls, gasping heavily.

As long as any living beings got close to Dang Hun mountain, they souls will have to endure the pain of vibrating shocks. The higher Fang Zheng climbed, the more he felt dizzy, like his soul was being blown away by the wind, he felt like he was about to collapse.

"Tsk tsk, you can't hold on anymore? Then give up. Look how much you've fallen behind the others, how can you possibly win? Why don't you just give up, you have no hope left." Hu Immortal land spirit pouted her tiny pink lips as she appeared before Fang Zheng.

Hu Immortal land spirit was like a little girl, snowy white skin glowing with pinkness. Her shiny large black eyes emitted an innocent gaze. What is most attractive is behind her back, where a snow white and pure fox tail grew, it was furry and fluffy, extremely cute and makes one want to play with it.

At this time, Hu Immortal land spirit was sitting in the air, watching Fang Zheng as she made fun of him.

Fang Zheng was not shocked.

After climbing to this height from the mountain foot, the land spirit had appeared many times, watching their progress every time, and was very playful.

Fang Zheng had found the method to deal with her, that is, to ignore her.

As expected, seeing that Fang Zheng was silent, Hu Immortal land spirit's mouth pouted even more: "You're a stupid lad, so boring. Please don't become my master, otherwise my life would be boring to death. Hehe, the others are more fun."

Saying so, she vanished, going to find the other elite disciples.

After Hu Immortal land spirit left, in Fang Zheng aperture, the spirit incubating flea vibrated, as Lord Sky Crane's voice sounded out.

"Fang Zheng, work hard and hang in there. Now is not the time for me to appear, you have to at least get past the mountain waist, only then can we have a chance of victory. Endure, you have to endure, the strength of the soul can be excavated, you have a lot of potential left to uncover."

Hearing his master's encouragement, Fang Zheng's dazed expression became firm again.

He replied in his heart: "Master, don't worry. I will endure, I am just taking a break, and regulating my breath."

Pausing momentarily, he asked again: "Master, I have a question, what is a land spirit? Earlier that Hu Immortal land spirit was near me, if I catch her, would I be able to skip the climbing?"

Lord Sky Crane was shocked, scolding: "You lad, you have no fear due to cluelessness, even trying to scheme against the land spirit. Do you know how the land spirit is formed? After the Gu Immortal dies, the remaining fragments of their will and soul mixed with the blessed land's powers, thus forming that spiritual body!"

"What, the land spirit was a Gu Immortal?" Fang Zheng was shocked.

"That's right, the Hu Immortal land spirit you saw was formed from the former Gu Immortal Bai Hu. But without her past life's memories, merely her lingering desires remain. Don't think of her as powerless, inside this blessed land, she can manipulate the heavenly power freely, and can directly combat a Gu Immortal! She can seal any rank one to five Gu worm at will. Only rank six Immortal Gu worms can move freely in the blessed land. Fang Zheng, you are too bold. Climb this mountain properly, do not have any unrealistic thoughts." Lord Sky Crane chided.

"Yes master, I will not dare to anymore." Fang Zheng nodded, admitting his fault in his heart.

After scolding Fang Zheng, Lord Sky Crane's tone eased, encouraging: "So now you know? As long as you become the owner of the blessed land, you can get the land spirit's loyalty. Within the blessed land, the land spirit is an existence equal to a Gu Immortal!"

Fang Zheng listened as he was completely stunned.

What sort of strong aid was that! The assistance of a Gu Immortal equivalent!!

Lord Sky Crane continued: "However, the land spirit cannot leave the blessed land. The true essence of the Hu Immortal Inheritance is this wide and rich blessed land. Fang Zheng, you are still too low level, and the things you do not know are simply too many. Wait till you inherit this blessed land, you will slowly understand, what sort of help a blessed land can bring to a Gu Master! You are simply too lucky, encountering a blessed land with a spirit, and also receiving the sect's help. If it is a blessed land without a spirit, that would be greatly inferior."

Fang Zheng asked curiously: "Master, what happens to a blessed land without a spirit?"

Lord Sky Crane answered: "A blessed land without a spirit is destined to be destroyed. Like a slumbering divine dragon, anyone can eat its flesh and drink its blood. Until it dies, it will not awaken. Fang Zheng, after you become the lord of the blessed land, you have to give the resources within the blessed land to the sect. Immortal Crane Sect had nurtured you this far, you have to give back to the sect. When the sect is stronger, the protection towards you will increase as well. You understand this logic right?"

"Mm, I understand. It was Immortal Crane Sect who adopted me. Without the sect's help, I would not have any chance in getting the inheritance. I would not even be able to exact revenge on my brother. If there is a possibility, I not only want to repay the sect, but I also want to revive you master!" Fang Zheng nodded, his vision was clear as he held great gratitude and admiration towards Immortal Crane Sect.

Lord Sky Crane heard this and laughed dryly: "Foolish disciple, how can people revive so easily? I am glad you had the thought."

...

The light of glory of the righteous path shone on San Cha mountain.

Under Tie Mu Bai's influence, three kings inheritance became the righteous path's garden of exploration.

Any demonic Gu Master was chased out and not allowed to step into the mountain.

"Tie Mu Bai is too overbearing, fencing up the area and refusing to let anyone in."

"He is a senior expert, yet his greed knows no bound. Eating the meat and bones, but refusing to let us drink even the soup!"

"Most importantly, three kings inheritance's opening time is shortening, and the three pillars are getting weaker. Just as little beast king said a month ago, this Gu Immortal blessed land is decaying, and will face destruction soon."

...

The demonic Gu Masters were feeling flustered and anxious, such a rare opportunity in front of them, yet they are denied entry, only able to watch in vain.

"Stuff the courageous to death and starve the timid to death, brothers, let's charge up together, no matter how powerful that Tie Mu Bai is, can he kill all of us?!" Someone shouted, encouraging the crowd.

"We can wait for Tie Mu Bai to enter the inheritance, and then go up the mountain. That way, there will be less obstruction." Someone suggested.

"There's a problem with this solution. When we come out of the inheritance, so would Tie Mu bai. Moreover, nobody knows where we would appear in San Chan mountain, we might get slaughtered by the righteous path." Someone rebuked.

"So what? Danger lurks when seeking wealth, how can we get the cub without entering the tiger's den? Wanting to gain something without taking a risk, how can there be such a good thing in this world?!"

Just as the demonic path members were shouting and discussing, they heard the wailings of a hundred ghosts near them, and the bright blue sky suddenly became filled with dark clouds.

Within the dark clouds, a shrill voice said: "Gagaga, Tie Mu Bai, you came out of your cultivation, why did you not say hi to your old friend, hmm?"

The dark clouds moved rapidly, forming a face, having an aquiline nose and deep eye sockets, staring at San Cha mountain.

"This laughter and entrance, it is Lord Wu Gui from our demonic path!"

"I remember now. Lord Wu Gui is also rank five peak stage, an expert from the older generation, he is Tie Mu Bai's lifetime rival!"

"There's nothing amazing about the righteous path, we have experts in the demonic path too! Go, Senior Wu Gui!!"

At once, the demonic path members cheered, their eyes glowing as some shouted while others screamed.

The dark clouds moved closer, shrouding San Cha mountain quickly. Such a grand entrance, like an entire army, at once, even sunlight was covered, causing San Cha mountain to fall into darkness.

The righteous Gu Masters were all fearful.

"He has such an overwhelming aura!"

"This old demon Wu Gui, he is still alive?"

"Old demon Wu Gui, he is over hundreds of years old. Back when he was breaking through to rank six, he was disturbed and ruined by the young and inexperienced Lord Tie Mu Bai unintentionally. Thus, he felt extreme hatred and had slaughtered Tie clansmen many times as revenge."

...

"Wu Gui, have you been hiding under a mountain all these years? Are you here to experience defeat once again?" At the mountain peak, golden light burst out.

In the golden light, Tie Mu Bai stood upright, his hands behind his back, speaking calmly towards the rolling dark clouds.

"Hmph, you won by merely one move a decade ago, you really think you are better. Little bastard, today you will die without a proper corpse!" The dark clouds moved like steam out of boiling water, turning into a large hand and grabbing towards Tie Mu Bai.

This hand, was extremely large, larger than a small-sized mountain. It gave off an impressive aura, stunning people and gave off the feeling of grabbing the moon and stars.

The dark clouds looked slow but were extremely fast, grabbing quickly.

Corrosive smoke rose, as the hand covered an entire mountain peak, causing the trees and rocks it touched to disintegrate.

"Old tricks." Tie Mu Bai snorted, moving his leg and turning into a golden light, tearing apart the dark clouds, flying towards the sky.

The golden light flew like a shooting star, like lightning, as it crashed into the dark clouds.

Almost the next moment, there was a thunder-like explosion, going off like firecrackers.

The dark clouds moved violently, as golden light flickered.

The two rank five peak stage Gu Masters fought inside the clouds. Although the details could not be seen, outsiders could feel how powerful they were just from the aftershocks sent out by them.

"Wu Gui, when I just started by Gu journey, you were already an established expert. Back then, i had to avoid you if I met you. But fifty years later, I could escape from you. Eighty years later, you could do nothing to me. A hundred years later, you lost to me. And now, after another decade, today, you will lose your life."

Tie Mu Bai's voice came from within the dark clouds.

"Huff, huff, huff... Tie. Mu. Bai! You are too arrogant, you were lucky to be born in Tie clan, relying on Tie clan, you can speak so arrogantly. If I had the same resources as you, I would've become a Gu Immortal by now." Wu Gui screamed in an unstable tone.

Evidently, during the intense battle earlier, Tie Mu Bai had the advantage.

"But, did you think I have no backup?" Hahaha!" Wu Gui breathed roughly, but started laughing wildly.

As he laughed, a third rank five peak stage aura burst out.

"Tie Mu Bai, did you miss me all these years?" A gloomy and shrill voice travelled far and wide.

Tie Mu Bai could not hide his shock: "Ku Mo, to think you came!"

Chapter 373: Intense Battle of Rank Fives

The situation at San Cha mountain had a violent change.

After Tie Mu Bai suppressed San Cha mountain for the most part of the year, his old enemy from the demonic path appeared. But Wu Gui who was also rank five peak stage could not beat Tie Mu Bai who made his debut later.

The situation that followed was beyond everyone's expectations.

The similarly rank five peak stage Ku Mo suddenly made his appearance. The battle situation immediately changed to two demonic path's rank five pincering Tie Mu Bai.

Righteous path figures cursed at the demonic path's shamelessness while the demonic path figures continued to rush into San Cha mountain and cheer loudly.

Uncountable gazes fanatically looked at the air.

A battle between rank five peak stage Gu Masters was rarely seen much less the battle between three rank five peak stage Gu Masters.

Tie Mu Bai could suppress Wu Gui, but fighting one against two was far beyond his ability. But Wu Gui and Ku Mo were both demonic Gu Masters and although they had allied, they were similarly guarded against each other.

Like this, the three entered a stalemate.

From the sky covered by the black clouds and fierce wind, an enormous and deafening explosion occurred.

Golden light burst out, a four clawed golden dragon tore the black clouds and moved the wind and rain; its dragon roar spreading over a long distance.

"Hmph, merely a rank four golden dragon Gu, did you take that out to make a fool of yourself?" Ku Mo let out a disdainful snarl, "Look at how I tear you to pieces!"

When his words landed, there was a loud sound; the golden dragon let out a miserable whine and fell down towards the ground.

Just as the golden dragon was about to lose its life, a golden whirlwind blew towards it.

The four clawed golden dragon was surrounded by the whirlwind and its heavy injuries were instantly healed. It raised its head and roared before rising up again.

"This is a rank four golden breeze Gu, its healing ability is extremely powerful and is comparable to rank five Gu!" The spectating Li Xian narrowed his eyes when he recognized this golden whirlwind.

"Don't even think about it!" Wu Gui suddenly gave an unearthly cry.

This unearthly cry was extremely ear-piercing like the cawing of ravens, the spectators be it righteous path or demonic path felt dizzy and nauseous.

Following the unearthly cry, a shining jet-black halo shot out and firmly collided against the four clawed golden dragon.

The four-clawed golden dragon could not resist it and exploded.

Dazzling light burst forth like a small sun, causing all the spectators to close their eyes.

The sound of the explosion was so loud, it seemed to burst everyone's eardrums.

A fierce wind pressure soon followed, blowing towards all directions. The wind blew countless trees and stones, burying many Gu Masters alive.

The berserk wind rose as if in defiance of heaven and even dispersed the dark clouds covering the sky.

The spectators regained their senses after a long while and retreated in fear while looking up.

In the sky, three figures were confronting each other!

Tie Mu Bai was wearing a golden chainmail, it was the rank four golden coat Gu and had exemplary defense. His whole body was covered with a layer of gold-red light. It was the rank four golden aurora Gu and could allow the Gu Master to fly.

Wu Gui was stepping on a dark cloud, his lips were sharply sticking forward like a black beak.

And Ku Mo was slowly flapping a pair of bone wings on his back, his whole body was covered with bone armor and there were all kinds of colorful sharp spikes growing out from his elbows, knees, shoulders and other places. At first look, he looked like a malevolent multi-colored human-shaped hedgehog.

The confrontation only lasted for a short few breaths of time.

The three attacked at the same time as quickly as lightning.

In the sky, a golden-red light shuttled back and forth, breaking the void and was as sharp as a sword. A black light soared, moving at one time and stopping at next, it was strange and cunning. A multi-colored light charged and crashed, and displayed the most valiant manner.

Ordinary naked eyes were already unable to make out the progress of the battle. The absolute majority of people could only hear the unceasing explosions that continued to ravage their eardrums.

Suddenly a golden light fiercely streaked across the sky like a blade, towards an area in the middle of the mountain.

Mountain stones and boulders were crushed into fine powder and there appeared a twenty feet wide and over hundred feet tall gorge.

The nearby unlucky spectators were all chopped into minced meat.

Suddenly a raven's caw echoed like the thunder.

Hundreds of unlucky Gu Masters' head burst immediately.

From time to time, bone spikes rained down freely from the sky.

Many Gu Masters could not evade in time and were pierced through, nailed at the ground and lost their lives.

The battle had reached the climax, the three sides moved without restraint.

"We can't endure even the ripples of a battle between rank five peak stage Gu Masters."

"Too terrifying, too terrifying, we need to leave quickly. If we keep on watching, we might have to pay with our lives!"

Everyone was scared witless and hurried out of San Cha mountain one after another.

Even Li Xian, Hu Mei Er and others also did not dare to stay here.

On San Cha mountain, only the rank four peak stage Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian, Long Qing Tian, Yi Chong and Wu Shen Tong remained.

Even so, their expressions were serious and all their concentration was fixed on the battle with their nerves stretched tight as a bowstring; they were ready to escape the moment there was even a little danger.

Soon, these rank four peak stage Gu Masters also could not continue staying there.

Because the three rank five peak stage Gu Masters used their rank five Gu.

Tie Mu Bai's turn gold Gu flew everywhere. No matter what it shot through, whether they were rocks, grasses, trees, flowers, birds, fishes or beasts, they would turn into golden sculpture, their life force extinguished.

Ku Mo's soft bones Gu made any bones within fifty miles of it, turn soft and become a puddle of bone paste.

And Wu Gui's pitch black Gu spread darkness everywhere, any Gu worms under rank six that touched it would received different degrees of restrictions.

In this world, the higher the rank of the Gu, the stronger and rarer they were. Precious Gu of rank four were already hard to purchase and rank five Gu were practically not circulated in the market. As for rank six Immortal Gu; every one of them were one of its kind.

Fang Yuan had reached rank six Gu Immortal's realm in his previous life, but he could only refine a rank six Spring Autumn Cicada. As for most of the Gu Masters, rank five Gu were already very hard to get.

The most important thing in a battle between rank five Gu Masters was the power of their rank five Gu.

"This is the power of a rank five Gu? Terrifying, rank four defensive Gu can hardly resist it, let alone rank three Gu..." From some far away corner, Bai Ning Bing observed the battle in San Cha mountain intently, her blue pupils flickering with grave light.

This was not the first time she saw a battle between rank five Gu Masters. She had seen it once before at Qing Mao mountain.

But the fighting strength of these three rank five Gu Masters were clearly much more powerful than Lord Sky Crane and first generation Gu Yue.

This was because first gen Gu Yue and Lord Sky Crane were decrepit rank five Gu Masters who were struggling at death's door and used all kinds of ways to prolong their lifespan.

First gen Gu Yue hibernated all year round in blood coffin and changed himself into a zombie; neither human nor ghost.

And Lord Sky Crane was not much better, he came from Central Continent, his battle prowess was suppressed to some extent in Southern Border.

But these three rank five Gu Masters Bai Ning Bing was looking at were all at their peak state. Their intense battle naturally gave her spirit an even stronger impact.

"If I face such rank five Gu Masters, I will not be able to resist one move of theirs and there is no hope of even escaping!" Bai Ning Bing looked at the battle for a long time and subconsciously clenched her fists, deeply realizing the gap between her and these rank five peak stage powers like Tie Mu Bai and the rest.

Rank five peak stage Gu Masters were at the peak of the mortal world, an emperor among Gu Masters.

Especially when they used rank five Gu, the strength they could bring out could destroy mountains if they came across mountains, split apart rivers if they came across rivers; such an enormous power gave a feeling that it could not be stopped.

"This is the show you were waiting for?" Bai Ning Bing retrieved her gaze and looked at Fang Yuan standing beside her with a flash of understanding, "Tie Mu Bai is fighting one against two. It seems after this battle the structure of San Cha mountain will have a complete change. Demonic path will suppress righteous path; you were waiting for this opportunity since several months ago, right?"

Fang Yuan calmly gazed into the distance and shook his head indifferently: "Rank five Gu are very rare, many rank five Gu Masters don't have even one rank five Gu and can only use use four Gu. Thus, a rank five Gu Master's battle strength is determined by the rank five Gu they hold and their amount."

"Demonic Gu Masters have always lacked resources and can mostly only rely on luck or fate. Ku Mo and Wu Gui have one or two rank five Gu with them. But Tie Mu Bai is different, he has a huge background called Tie clan, he should at least have three rank five Gu on him."

Bai Ning Bing's expression moved: "You mean Tie Mu Bai will be the winner of this battle?"

Fang Yuan, however, shook his head: "Gu worms are Gu Master's trump card, the Gu Masters can be targeted against once their Gu are exposed. Tie Mu Bai will not easily reveal all his trump cards. From the start, this battle had neither a winner nor a loser."

Bai Ning Bing was a smart person and immediately understood it after Fang Yuan gave her the clues.

No matter how intense this battle was, it was only a probe.

Why did Tie Mu Bai, Wu Gui and Ku Mo came here?

Was it purely for revenge against each other?

Impossible!

For people like them, their greatest goal is to break away from mortal and charge through to rank six Gu Immortal realm, thereby gaining a longer life.

These three were at the peak, looking down on all mortals, and had rich experiences; gratitude and grudges could not move them. Each of their action held their own deep purpose.

"These three chose San Cha mountain for their battle instead of any other places. So, their purpose is already clear - three kings inheritance!"

Bai Ning Bing's eyes flickered with a pondering light.

"Three kings were rank five Gu Masters, their inheritance contains rank five Gu worms; each one of these rank five Gu can greatly increase their strength. With a treasure in front of them, how could they battle without care? Unless there is an extremely huge imbalance between the battle strength of the two sides. But from the current situation, it clearly is not so. So this battle can only end in a draw."

The confusing battle situation suddenly became extremely clear.

Bai Ning Bing subconsciously looked at Fang Yuan.

When everyone's hearts were throbbing intensely because of the intense battle of rank five Gu Masters, he was still so calm like he was a spectator watching something of no concern.

But was it really a matter of no concern?

Bai Ning Bing rejected this thought inwardly, no one knew clearer than her regarding the thirst Fang Yuan had towards three kings inheritance.

But even under such desire, he could still restrain his impulse.

Facing such an opponent, Bai Ning Bing's heart felt incomparably heavy: "Such unfathomable shrewdness... how will I be able to take the yang Gu that can turn me back to a male from him?"

Chapter 374: Calamity and Tribulation of the Blessed Land

Half a month later.

On a certain peak in San Cha mountain.

A group of ash-grey mountain apes close to a thousand in numbers tightly surrounded Tie Ruo Nan while screeching and screaming.

Tie Ruo Nan took in a deep breath, she suddenly waved her hand and shot a large cloud of golden needle Gu.

Golden needle Gu was not a natural Gu but was a Gu created by Tie clan's Gu Masters. Every golden needle Gu was a rank two Gu, their length was around an index finger and were like thin golden needles.

Golden needle Gu shot through the apes; some stood on the spot without being able to move, some died from poison and some were driven into a frenzy and actually began attacking their nearby companions.

Tie Ruo Nan repeatedly shot out golden needles; there was chaos among the mountain apes and they suffered huge losses. In a sorry figure and while screeching miserably, they made their escape. Soon, the noisy battlefield quietened down.

Large numbers of mountain apes were on the ground; some were dead and some were at their last breaths.

Tie Ruo Nan slowly walked past them and shot out golden needle Gu again.

But this time, these golden needle Gu had healing effects, they shot into the mountain apes and turned into balls of golden light, moving back and forth between their injuries. Many mountain apes recovered their movement ability.

Golden needle Gu by itself was not wondrous. But when matched with poison liquid Gu, it could turn into poison needle. When matched with stiff Gu, it could make the enemies unable to move a single step. When matched with chaotic mind Gu, it could cause chaos among the enemies making them unable to differentiate between their allies and enemies. And when matched with vitality Gu, it had healing properties.

Tie Ruo Nan had spent around seven to eight days to be proficient in the combination of these four types of battle tactics. Thus, she was able to defeat close to a thousand mountain apes by herself.

"Ruo Nan, this child has an outstanding talent with high comprehension and more importantly, her nature is tenacious and resolute, she is indeed someone who will become a pillar of Tie clan." Tie Mu Bai watched this nearby with no expression on his face, but his heart was full of praises.

This old Tie clan leader had seen the rise of countless talents in his life and also witnessed the fall of innumerable geniuses.

He was very clear: In a dangerous and difficult environment, many outstanding geniuses would emerge. But talent was only one aspect, what mattered was the nature of the geniuses.

If a genius could put up with hardships and endure loneliness, they would definitely have great accomplishments in the future.

A genius that had poor disposition could only be a shooting star, shining for only an instant.

Why would Tie Mu Bai teach Tie Ruo Nan? On the one hand, Tie Ruo Nan was blood-related to Tie Xue Leng, who had certain relationship with him; on the other hand, Tie Ruo Nan had been polished like limestone after a series of trials; all traces of impatience had gone leaving behind stability and perseverance.

Tie Ruo Nan was like an unpolished jade that let out dazzling light after being polished slightly.

"Old clan leader." Tie Ruo Nan climbed up the peak towards Tie Mu Bai and cupped her hands in greeting.

The girl was full of admiration and respect towards this old man.

Half a month ago, this old man Tie Mu Bai fought against two rank five experts of the demonic path by himself.

He first used rank five turn gold Gu to contend with the two demons easily. Then, he used rank five liquid metal Gu to make these two experts back out and weakened their fighting spirits; the battle finally ended with both sides relenting.

Tie Mu Bai's strength was like a basin of cold water that poured on the hearts of the demonic Gu Masters, causing their rising flames of angers to weaken in an instant.

The conclusion of the battle was that both righteous and demonic paths could contend for three kings inheritance. But everyone could clearly see how good Tie Mu Bai was and that he had not used his full strength.

"Good. Being able to grasp this flexible battle tactic in such a short time is remarkable." Tie Mu Bai praised indifferently as he casually waved his hand.

Whoosh!

A large cloud of golden needle Gu shot out.

However, different from Tie Ruo Nan's golden needle Gu, the golden needle Gu Tie Mu Bai commanded were extremely small like raindrops.

When they moved in the sky, they were like a cloud of golden fog.

The golden fog moved with the wind and brushed past an area of boulders. Pitter-patter sounds as if thousands of silkworms were eating mulberries came from the giant boulders.

Tie Ruo Nan's pupils shrunk, immediately realizing the amazing aspect of this move.

The golden fog infiltrated and penetrated the boulders, creating countless tiny holes in them. The trees nearby the boulders were also pierced through, all signs of life within them extinguished instantly.

If someone were struck by these Gu, their whole body and insides would be perforated and destroyed; it was a really terrifying killer move!

Tie Mu Bai casually waved his hand and threw out three golden needle Gu.

These three golden needles were, however, different; they were thick and long. Normal golden needle Gu had a finger sized length, but these three golden needles had palm sized length.

The three golden needle Gu flew and pierced into a mountain ape's head.

One shot like a perpendicular lightning, straight into the mountain ape from the top of its head, while the other two entered through the left and right temples; the needles almost completely entering the mountain ape's head with only a small portion remaining on the outside.

This mountain ape had been healed by Tie Ruo Nan and was just making its escape when it was struck by the golden needles.

The mountain ape let out a painful scream and leaped a couple of times, kneeling in front of Tie Mu Bai.

The ape's eyes were wide open with incomparable panic, dread and anger.

The strange thing was it could not control its body and kneeled down reverentially and without making any movements. It was not even able to let out a shout.

Tie Ruo Nan had never expected to see such a peculiar scene and was stupefied for a while.

Tie Mu Bai laughed and looked at the mountain ape at his feet, he indifferently said: "Golden needle Gu combined with create fog Gu can form golden fog. This golden fog looks faint and weak, but is actually extremely powerful and is specialized in breaking through Gu Master's defense. When I was twenty-eight and was roaming Southern Border, I used this move to dominate the region of Luchuan river."

Tie Mu Bai paused for a while and continued: "Golden needle Gu combined with puppet control Gu, can take control of living bodies. When I was forty-two and my cultivation advanced to rank four peak stage, I ended my closed cultivation and began to roam the world to test my skills. When I arrived at Tie Mu mountain, I was attacked by a group of over fifty demonic path mountain bandits. I used this move to make thirty-eight of them defect and finally captured all of them and got rid of these evil beings."

Tie Ruo Nan became more fascinated the more she heard.

Since her early years, she followed her father and travelled everywhere. And she had heard of this old clan leader's heroic deeds.

The old clan leader had A grade aptitude and revealed his talent the moment he started cultivating, becoming the number one youth star of Tie clan at that time. He also lived up to others' expectations, advancing to rank four peak stage before fifty.

He ended his secluded cultivation and roamed Southern Border, crossing mountains and rivers to test his skills, and made a name for himself.

After returning to Tie clan, he became the clan leader and brought Tie clan to new heights. For a while, Tie clan was in such limelight that it made Wu clan, Shang clan and the rest lose their splendor.

His whole life was filled with glory and brilliance. He had countless battle achievements under him, whether it was his lone achievements while roaming the Southern Border or leading a group of heroes to eliminate evil - he had few losses.

The way he did his work was unyielding and domineering, daring to stand directly up to the enemies; many of his enemies would be terror stricken at the mention of him when he was reigning. Even righteous path figures would feel mental pressure when they heard Tie Mu Bai's name.

Right now, as Tie Ruo Nan listened to the old clan leader recall those olden days indifferently, she became overwhelmed with emotions.

She could not help imagining a scene.

A hero at his prime, handsome and graceful, donning a blue robe, moved unhindered around the world. He defeated powerful enemies by himself, no one could block him and countless people watched him.

However, time was ruthless, turning that young man into an elderly.

But Tie Mu Bai was still Tie Mu Bai.

Even if he was more old, it could not hide his glorious deeds.

These battle accomplishments were a dazzling halo that covered his body and even the layers of dust of history could not block its radiance.

"Lord old clan leader, I will not let you down, golden needle Gu will not shame your name in my hands!" Tie Ruo Nan spoke resolutely.

The old man gratefully nodded and patted Tie Ruo Nan's shoulder.

"Child, you have a strong mind and our Tie clan's blood flows in your veins. You have to shoulder the responsibility of our Tie clan's children. I will teach you all that I know, and I hope that one day, you can be capable enough to raise the flag of Tie clan. I am leaving that little beast king Fang Zheng to you as your test, do you have confidence?"

"I have confidence and also have a plan. Old clan leader, you can rest assured, Fang Zheng has already completely fallen into the demonic path, I will definitely retrieve his head!" Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone with resolute light.

"Good, do not be arrogant in victory or discouraged in defeat, you are able to get out of your shock and derive strength from your tribulation, this is something that is impossible for many youngsters. As long as you maintain this, you will definitely become the glory of Tie clan! Now, I shall teach you the principle behind these two tactics along with my insights and experience in them, as well as all the other different combinations that can be derived."

Like this, one taught diligently and another did her best to learn.

After over an hour, Tie Mu Bai finished teaching everything: "Good, you can ask me anything you are unclear about."

Tie Ruo Nan had outstanding comprehension ability and had already engraved all the teachings into her mind.

However, she thought for a while and asked: "These days, I have found that the opening time of three kings inheritance has been getting shorter and the amount of Gu Masters that can enter has also been getting lesser. The three light pillars are no longer as thick and bright as before. Right now, there has been many rumors saying the blessed land is already nearing its end. Is this true?"

Tie Mu Bai nodded: "It is indeed so."

"You are still not ready to learn some things. All living things exist in balance - with darkness, there is light; with water there is fire; with blessing, there is calamity." His gaze turned towards the peak of San Cha mountain and sighed: "Every blessed land will face earthly calamity every ten years and heavenly tribulation every hundred years. This blessed land originated from a mysterious Gu Immortal from ancient times and was later was inherited by the three kings and remodelled into this inheritance site."

"This blessed land is already old, its lifespan is almost at its end. A land spirit could prolong this time, but unfortunately there is no land spirit here."

"A blessed land without a land spirit is an enormous boat that is sinking. Anyone can enter inside and plunder the treasures within. The more they plunder, the bigger the holes in this giant boat and the quicker it would sink. This Gu Immortal blessed land is already nearing its end and will only last for less than ten years before it is destroyed due to the exhaustion of immortal essence."

Chapter 375: Gathering of Experts

"To think that even blessed lands faced destruction..." Tie Ruo Nan heard the secret and sighed lightly.

"How can there be any existence in this world that is indestructible? The cycle of heavenly fate, the competition of all living beings, in this wide universe, we mortals are like a single speck of sand at the bottom of an entire sea, small and insignificant. Only by advancing to a Gu Immortal, can we surpass mortality, and have our own foundation, turning from sand into an island, having the ability to resist the sea waves." Tie Mu Bai's tone was full of lamentation.

"When the blessed land faces destruction, wouldn't the people inside be in great danger?" Tie Ruo Nan asked again.

"That is right." Tie Mu Bai nodded: "The moment the blessed land vanishes, the wind of assimilation will blow, fusing heaven and earth together, as everything inside the blessed land would turn into the most basic primeval essence in this world. This wind's power can sweep away all dust and particle, even Gu Immortals fear it, because even Gu Immortals can be destroyed by it."

"There is such a powerful wind?" Tie Ruo Nan was shocked beyond words, showing great worry in her eyes.

Tie Mu Bai waved his hand: "No worry, I have already stepped into the blessed land many times, I have gained deep understanding of it, and have always been observing and learning about it. The blessed land is indeed weakening, but there is still a long time before it faces destruction. During this period, the heavenly power in the blessed land will weaken, and the restrictions towards us Gu Masters would decrease. Slowly, we would be able to use one or two Gu, and then three or four, five or six... Eventually, the blessed land would be full of loopholes, and form an entrance where we can enter and exit at will."

Tie Mu Bai looked afar, his gaze deep and filled with knowledge, like he could predict the future.

"At the final period, that will be the true decisive battle of three kings inheritance. As the restriction from the blessed land is gone, anyone can use their full power. They can plunder and battle to their heart's extent. By then, San Cha mountain would not only have three rank five Gu Masters, that would truly be the gathering of experts, the rise of snakes and dragons."

Tie Ruo Nan felt a flash of inspiration, and realized.

She finally understood why Tie Mu Bai did not fight to the death with those two demonic Gu Masters.

That is because, his future enemies were not only these two. Fighting with all he had so early on would only benefit others.

Towards the end of the three kings inheritance, the Gu Masters would receive greater and better rewards.

Those who truly understood the blessed land, had already been preparing for the final battle.

...

Central continent.

Tian Ti mountain.

Hu Immortal Blessed Land.

"I am finally at the mountain waist." Fang Zheng breathed roughly, sweat dripping from his forehead.

His arms and legs were numb and sore, they had no energy left. Using his own strength, and climbing to this level, it had squeezed out all the potential he had in his soul.

The mountain winds blew, and a strong feeling of dizziness hit him, causing Fang Zheng to feel like he was going to fall.

His entire vision was spinning, after his soul was expended to the max, he even lost the ability to think.

In his daze, he heard from within his aperture, the incubating flea: "Good, very good, my good disciple, you have endured this far, it was not easy. You have succeeded, now it will be up to your master me!"

Saying so, Fang Zheng felt a formless energy flowing into the deepest part of his soul.

The falling feeling immediately disappeared, like a child who was learning how to walk but was suddenly assisted by an adult.

His vision became clear, and Fang Zheng's dizziness vanished at a rapid speed.

Fang Zheng breathed in deeply several times, he felt fantastic!

Like a traveller in the desert, about to die of thirst, but suddenly drinking fresh water. Or like someone who had worked non-stop all the time, suddenly sleeping seven days and seven nights.

Everything became great, he felt awesome.

"Good disciple, make use of your time, and climb quickly!" Lord Sky Crane urged.

"Yes master!" Fang Zheng's eyes were shining like a tiger's. He raised his head, and saw Feng Jin Huang and others, leading far ahead, but they were getting slower.

Fang Zheng felt an unprecedented sense of confidence.

"I can do it, with master's help, I can definitely defeat these geniuses, and became the sole inheritor of Hu Immortal blessed land! Fang Zheng, hang in there!"

After encouraging himself for a bit, Fang Zheng continued climbing.

His movements became fast and steady, his speed was extremely fast, like he was bursting out his second wind. This performance, attracted people's attention and emphasis.

After Hu Immortal blessed land opened, it was connected to the outside world.

Thus, the ten Gu Immortals outside the blessed land immediately found out Fang Zheng's weird condition.

"Eh? This child, he was at his limit, and was about to be eliminated, how did he suddenly get so energetic?"

"Something's strange, this speed is even faster than Feng Jin Huang and the others!"

"This junior is from Immortal Crane Sect. So that's it, I see..."

The ten Gu Immortals exchanged their thoughts, and someone quickly found out Fang Zheng's trump card.

"He Feng Yang, you sure are generous. Spirit incubating flea is not precious, but to ensure the flea still works, you used one's own way Gu didn't you?

He Feng Yang was one of Immortal Crane Sect's supreme elders, he had a rank six "One's own way Gu", everyone knew that.

One's own way Gu, it allowed other Gu worms to operate in the blessed land.

It was an expenditure Gu, only usable for three times. After three times, it would vanish into thin air.

"He Feng Yang, you had great schemes, using this secret chess piece."

"I'm flattered. Among the youngsters, Myriad Dragon Dock has Ying Sheng Ji, Spirit Affinity House has Feng Jin Huang, Spirit Butterfly Valley has Xiao Qi Xing, we Immortal Crane Sect cannot contend, thus we had to do this." He Feng Yang was very modest and low-key.

The other Gu Immortals could only laugh dryly.

They had their own rank six Gu worms, but they did not have one's own way Gu, they could not provide such assistance.

Rank six Gu worms were Immortal Gu, one in the world. At any point in time, in the whole wide world, only one exists.

Immortal Gu were so much rarer than rank five Gu worms, many rank six Immortals do not even have one Immortal Gu.

Back in Fang Yuan's previous life, he became an immortal. But to refine his first rank six Spring Autumn Cicada, he spent a massive amount of time and effort, the moment he succeeded, the righteous path attacked him, their motive was the Immortal Gu.

The ten Gu Immortals here, because they relied on their sects, they all had their trump cards. But even then, they only had one to two Immortal Gu.

He Feng Yan had the one's own way Gu, that means that other Gu Immortals did not!

The most important thing was, He Feng Yang's act did not exceed their bottomline, nor did he break the rules of the game. The other Gu Immortals could only watch from here, unable to interfere.

"It is a pity my Immortal Gu specializes in attack, if I use it, that would be attacking the Hu Immortal inheritance, it would not work."

"Although I have a defensive Immortal Gu to protect the soul, my disciples do not have the immortal essence needed to activate it. Otherwise, Hu Immortal Inheritance would be ours for sure."

"The results are not determined yet, this disciple from Immortal Crane Sect has the help of the spirit incubating flea and has a huge advantage. But he was lagging behind from the start, we will have to see what happens from now..."

"Eighty years ago, He Feng Yang used the one's own way Gu, this is the second time. That means, the one's own way Gu in his hand can only be used one more time. He paid such a huge price, only to gain an advantage in competing for the inheritance."

The other Gu Immortals assessed, and decided to remain observers, not making their moves yet.

...

On San Cha mountain, three pillars of light shot into the sky.

The three kings inheritance opened again, strongly attracting all the southern border Gu Masters.

Just as Tie Mu Bai said, on San Cha mountain, experts started to gather, and a storm was brewing.

"Did you hear? Just yesterday, Li Fei Le came to San Cha mountain."

"Ah, you mean 'sturdy as a mountain' Li Fei Le?"

Soon, another established expert came to San Cha mountain.

Li Fei Le's cultivation was rank four upper stage, an earth path Gu Master. His title was 'sturdy as a mountain', an expert in defense. He was Li clan's rising star, and was nurtured greatly by the clan. But this person was dedicated towards pursuing strength.

Dedication after losing one's direction, becomes obsession.

To pursue the greatest strength, he killed people to refine Gu, and was not accepted by the righteous path, becoming a demonic path cultivator.

Li Fei Le was only the start, in the month after, more and more established Gu Masters arrived at San Cha mountain.

The enslavement path Gu Master Zhang San San, when he was rank three peak stage, he killed a rank four Gu Master, now that he was rank four middle stage, people called him the enslavement master.

The righteous path expert Tao Zi, he had a famous rank five healing Gu that was renowned in southern border — spirit peach Gu.

There was also Yun Luo Tian, young clan leader of Yun clan, wind path Gu Master, reaching rank three peak stage at age twenty-three. Right now, he was thirty-five, a step away from rank four peak stage.

More and more famous Gu Masters, like sharks smelling blood, stepped into San Cha mountain, competing for the three kings inheritance and trying to get their share of the pie.

These Gu Masters had at least rank three upper stage cultivation, and some were even rank four realm.

A month later, San Cha mountain saw its fourth rank five Gu Master.

Wang Xiao.

He was the owner of Wu mountain, a demonic Gu Master, rank five poison cultivator, a true overlord of his area.

Two months later, Wu clan's Wu Lan Shan arrived.

As the number one clan, Wu clan had always been dominating southern border. The Wu Lan Shan they sent was the younger cousin of Wu clan leader, once she appeared, she held a great battle with Wang Xiao.

Although the battle ended in a draw, her performance showed she exceeded Ku Mo and Wu Gui.

Another eight days later, Chou Jiu who was famous among the demonic cultivators, appeared on San Cha mountain's mountain foot, causing a commotion.

Chou Jiu was also rank five, but had little battle strength. He was a healing Gu Master, the famous killer ghost doctor, one of the four great doctors together with doctor Su Shou, travelling doctor Jiu Zhi, and divine doctor Sheng Shou.

He had a strange personality, having this weird rule, anyone he heals needs to kill a person for him in return.

He saves a live, and takes another. Thus people call him: killer ghost doctor.

He who walks by the river is bound to get his shoes wet. In this cruel world, Gu Masters cannot avoid getting injured and sick, they will have to beg a doctor for help eventually.

The four great doctors healed both demonic and righteous, once the killer ghost doctor ascended San Cha mountain, he was invited by Tie Mu Bai earnestly, and the two drank happily in a banquet.

Time passed by quickly, the three kings inheritance opened and closed, closed and opened.

This day, three kings inheritance opened again.

At the mountain foot, two people appeared.

Soon, people recognised them, screaming in shock: "The black and white twin demons, they are here again!"

Chapter 376: Fang Yuan courts death

On the mountain peak, three light pillars of red, blue, and yellow presented themselves before the people.

Compared to the start, observant people could see that these three pillars had dimmed greatly, at the same time their size had shrunk, less than half of the original.

This Gu Immortal Blessed Land that originated from ancient times, had reached its final moments. After being remodelled by the three kings, it was starting to collapse under the plundering of countless Gu Masters.

It was like a sinking ship, the seawater had submerged more than half of it, only the sail and mast are still floating.

"Old clan leader Tie, you first." After considering for a while, Wu Lan Shan cupped her fists politely at Tie Mu Bai.

Among the rank five Gu Masters present, Tie Mu Bai was still the one with greatest strength.

On this San Cha Mountain, he was the number one person of the rank fives. Even throughout southern border, he was a top-tier rank five Gu Master.

Tie Mu bai's status was publicly recognised.

Even opponents like Ku Mo and Wu Gui had to admit this point.

Tie Mu Bai looked at the three pillars, nodding: "Then I will go first."

His every action was under everyone's observation. The few thousand Gu Masters at the inheritance entrance were all looking at him.

Tie Mu Bai took the lead, entering King Xin Inheritance.

Wu Gui and Ku Mo looked at each other, since Tie Mu Bai chose King Xin Inheritance, they should avoid encountering him.

Between rank five Gu Masters, they tend to avoid such unnecessary competition.

The final battle at the end was the stage for them to unleash their true abilities.

After Tie Mu Bai, Wu Lan Shan, Wang Xiao and the others all chose their respective entrances, entering the inheritance.

Next, Yi Huo was the first rank four peak stage Gu Master to enter, followed by the others.

On San Cha mountain, righteous and demonic Gu Masters were gathered together. Enemies who usually fought on sight became extremely orderly when it came to such huge benefits.

But at this moment, the quiet mountain peak became noisy.

First, it was the Gu Masters standing at the outside area discussing among themselves. Soon, Gu Masters in the inner circle also turned their heads to look.

"It is the black and white twin demons, they are finally back!" Some recognised the source of the commotion, and exclaimed.

"They are the black and white twin demons? The recent rising stars of the demonic path?" Some people saw Fang and Bai for the first time and observed them closely.

"These two youngsters are not simple. One was trapped by the Tie clan old-timers for months without falling. The other is even stronger, fighting seven Tie clansmen single-handedly and even killing Tie Ba Xiu!" Someone introduced.

Fang and Bai had caused a great commotion in San Cha mountain, it left a deep impression on them. Now, many people could still vividly recall the scene.

Tie Ba Xiu... I fought against him before. Fang Zheng is truly not simple, being able to kill him at such a young age." Someone nodded, his expression turning solemn.

"From what I see, his 'present age overlord' is just a overstatement. Letting a junior get famous, he is a disgrace to his generation." A Gu Master scoffed.

"So what if the black and white demons came? Times are different now, on San Cha mountain, there are six rank five Gu Masters! The two of them are rank four Gu Masters, they can't do anything here."

"That's right, especially after Fang Zheng killed some Tie clansmen, Tie Mu Bai would not let him off. But he is really daring, still having the guts to come here."

"Isn't it obvious, he only dared to show up after Tie Mu Bai entered the inheritance."

The people discussed softly, all sorts of gazes were on Fang and Bai; curiosity, inspection, solemn, and frivolous.

There were also many others who did not look at them, but placed their sights on another person.

This person was standing among the rank four Gu Masters, tight clothing with eyes shining like stars, tightly knit eyebrows, it was Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ruo Nan was a rank four Gu Master, she naturally stood with the rank four Gu Masters to enter the inheritance.

Although Tie Mu Bai was the number one person on San Cha mountain, he had to follow the rules, and be an example. Otherwise, he would not be able to control the Gu Masters on San Cha mountain.

This was the conduct of a leader of the righteous path.

"Fang Zheng, it's you!" Tie Ruo Nan stood out from the people, staring fiercely at Fang Yuan, her tone extremely agitated.

Seeing Fang Yuan, the enemy who had so many Tie clansmen's blood on his hands, the young girl's heart was filled with hatred and anger, she wanted to go and kill him immediately.

Her tightly clenched fists slowly loosened.

Tightened and loosened, loosened and tightened. Such a repetitive action showed the struggle in her heart.

Eventually, Tie Ruo Nan opened her palm, breathing out deeply, her eyes regaining clarity: "Little beast king, you do not have to worry about old clan leader's attack. Your life is mine, one day, I will kill you, and offer it to the heroic spirit of my Tie clansmen. Just you wait!"

Saying so, the young girl turned around and entered the light pillar, vanishing.

"Is Tie Ruo Nan afraid? She left without fighting!"

"It seems little beast king's dominance remains, this Tie clan young master did not dare to battle."

"I feel that this young girl was smart. The three kings inheritance is in front of her, such a rare event should be treasured. What is the point of fighting and killing now?"

Fang Yuan frowned deeply.

Tie Ruo Nan's performance surprised him. Being able to control her furious emotions, it was not an easy task. Many famous Gu Masters could not do it.

"Tie Ruo Nan... I cannot let you grow further."

This was rare, Fang Yuan felt threat from someone of the same generation.

The things Tie Mu Bai taught Tie Ruo Nan were not a secret, everyone knew about it. Fang Yuan, of course, knew clearly.

Tie Ruo Nan had talent, aptitude, and her heart was determined. Adding in the nurturing of the clan, she was like a swallow soaring into the heavens, one day, she will rise beyond the clouds, and turn into a phoenix.

Controlling the killing intent in his heart, Fang Yuan walked towards the inheritance entrance.

A large portion of the rank four Gu Masters gave way to them immediately.

"Hold it." Suddenly, a righteous Gu Master walked up and blocked their paths.

This righteous Gu Master wore white clothing, his sleeves were wide and swayed with the wind, and he had a handsome face. It was none other than Yun clan's young clan leader, Yun Luo Tian.

"Little beast king, I heard you killed Tie Ba Xiu." Yun Luo Tian stood before Fang Yuan, after giving him a glance, he started to observe Bai Ning Bing.

"Do you know?" He pointed at Fang Yuan, saying arrogantly: "You won in an unfair way, you used a flying Gu and killed a member my righteous faction, you took the easy way out."

The atmosphere was extremely heavy.

Yun Luo Tian's words were very offensive, and Fang Yuan was an arrogant person, at this rate, they were going to fight.

Many Gu Masters took steps back, getting away from these two.

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan's eyes were eerie as he looked at Yun Luo Tian, nodding, suddenly laughing: "You are right, I used a loophole and killed Tie Ba Xiu, sorry about that."

Yun Luo Tian was stunned, he did not think that this little beast king would reply this way. Isn't this different from the information about him?

These years of closed cultivation, he had trained in the art of flying. He feels that his flying skills were not inferior to the few flying experts of southern border. Thus, he wanted to challenge Fang Yuan, and build his reputation.

But Fang Yuan was so courteous, he could not continue finding problems with him.

Demonic cultivators were evil and ruthless, but he was a righteous member, and the young clan leader of Yun clan, his every action was closely inspected, after all, it represented Yun clan's image.

Yun Luo Tian stood dazed for a moment before calming his mind: "We let young master Tie Ruo Nan go first because we admire old clan leader Tie Mu Bai. Since you know you had an unfair victory, you should stand down now. There are so many heroes and geniuses here, it is not your turn to enter yet."

Yun Luo Tian waved his sleeve at Fang Yuan, speaking plainly.

Although he secretly flattered the people around him, it caused them to become even more nervous, and everyone felt a storm approaching.

Just as everyone was preparing for battle, Fang Yuan took a step back: "Sir makes sense. It was my fault, you guys should go first."

Yun Luo Tian laughed loudly, waving his sleeves and relaxed, walking towards the light pillar, entering after tens of steps.

Although he did not fight with Fang Yuan, he felt the gains were greater.

Not long after, words would spread that he challenged little beast king verbally, and scared this demonic rising star till he retreated.

At that time, his reputation would surge, and Yun clan's reputation in the righteous faction would rise as well.

After Yun Luo Tian entered the inheritance, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing entered King Bao Inheritance together.

Seeing them disappear, the remaining rank four Gu Masters started conversing.

"Is this still little beast king? He is so polite?"

"Did he take the wrong medicine, or did I see wrongly? This world is changing too quickly!"

"Hehe, little beast king gave in, he is such a coward. If it was me, I would've rolled up my sleeves and fought."

"Sigh, his opponent is Yun Luo Tian after all! Although Yun clan is not a super clan, it is still a first-class clan."

...

After his vision of the spinning world calmed down, Fang Yuan assessed his surroundings.

Grey-white sky, light red ground, extended towards the horizons. On the ground, there were pieces of volcanic rocks, hot rising steam, or grey dust cloud.

"Devil again, they descended again!"

"My companions, quickly gather together. As long as we fight together, we can defeat the demon king!"

"Come, our Hong Dan village can only be protected by ourselves!"

The top of volcanic rocks were flipped over, and tiny humans walked out.

These tiny people were the size of babies, they were pink and tender, extremely cute. Most importantly, at the middle of their chests, they had a cute and round red egg.

These were the eggmen.

Similar to the hairy men, they were variant humans.

Fang Yuan gave a glance, and knew these were the red eggmen among the eggmen. The egg on them were red, and they used the large volcanic rocks to build their houses, and lived inside.

At this moment, Fang Yuan could only use one exploding egg Gu.

King Bao Inheritance's aim was to make Fang Yuan use the exploding egg Gu to exterminate these red eggmen. That way, he can advance to the next round.

Facing the assaulting red eggmen, Fang Yuan did not move.

He let them attack him.

These attacks accumulated, quickly injuring him heavily.

Fang Yuan could not breathe properly, he was bathed in blood and the feeling of death was creeping up on him. At this moment, even if he used the exploding egg Gu, it could not change the situation.

Letting himself get into such a dangerous situation, Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile.

"This moment has finally arrived!"

Chapter 377: Refining an Immortal Gu!

A bunch of short red eggmen encircled Fang Yuan, attacking constantly.

"Eh? Is this devil a fool, why is he not moving?"

"If only all devils were such fools, that would be great!"

"Do not let your guard down, devils are extremely crafty, quickly kill him."

Seeing Fang Yuan about to die, the red eggmen cheered victoriously.

But at this moment, a formless energy descended and swept Fang Yuan away!

Falling into encirclement, the dying and unconsciously Fang Yuan vanished without a trace, leaving behind a bunch of shocked red eggmen.

When Fang Yuan woke up from his slumber, the scenery before him was completely different than before.

This was a dark blue colored hall.

The hall was extremely plain, made with large cube bronze blocks. There were a lot of moss on the blocks, showing how long they have already existed.

Fang Yuan laid on the center of the hall, feeling the chill from the bronze block under his back.

"I've already healed your injuries." A large tortoise opened its wrinkled eyes slowly, staring at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan slowly got up from the ground, first touching his own body, his injuries were truly healed.

Next, he looked around the hall in a calm expression.

Lastly, he turned his gaze over towards the huge tortoise before him.

This huge tortoise was large as a house, a thick and hard jade thin shell on its back. Its four legs were like elephant legs, and there were two dragon whiskers growing out of its face.

Fang Yuan looked at this huge tortoise, his lips curling into a smile, as his smile turned into laughter.

"Hahaha..." His laughter echoed in the hall.

He purposely courted death, not even using the Spring Autumn Cicada, it was all because of his previous life's knowledge and information, there was a huge risk involved. It could be said, one wrong move and game over. But a demonic cultivator moved forward relentlessly, they were most skilled at all-in gambles. Right now, Fang Yuan reached the main hall, and his risks had all paid off.

After laughing heartily, Fang Yuan stopped laughing, facing the huge tortoise: "Land spirit Ba Gui, you finally awakened from your slumber."

"You know me?" The huge tortoise's voice created vibrations as there was some suspicion in its eyes.

"That's right, I know you, and I also know the secret of this blessed land." Fang Yuan nodded, walking in the hall with his hands behind his back.

"This blessed land originated from an ancient strength path Gu Immortal. The Gu Immortal protected the blessed land, resisting calamities and tribulations, but eventually, he died in one of the tribulations. His dying wish gathered with this blessed land's heavenly power, formed the land spirit. That is you, Ba Gui. As long as I complete his wish before he died, I can become the new owner of this blessed land, am I right about that?"

Fang Yuan spoke openly, not beating about the bush.

Although the land spirit is formed from the Gu Immortal, it is no longer human, but merely the immortal's will.

Using an explanation from Earth, that would be, a preprogrammed AI[1].

As long as the land spirit's requirement is met, one can gain its recognition and become the new owner of the blessed land.

Thus, when Fang Yuan spoke, there was no need for any schemes or plots.

The huge tortoise nodded: "That's right, his final wish before dying is also the blessed land's test. As long as you can complete it, you can become my master."

"And the contents of this wish, is to refine the second aperture Gu right?" Fang Yuan followed.

During ancient times, strength path flourished, eight out of ten Gu Masters walked the strength path.

This blessed land's original master, was a strength path Gu Immortal, he created the recipe for second aperture Gu. But right before the crucial step, he died in a tribulation.

After he died, this final obsession became the land spirit.

That is, the huge tortoise before Fang Yuan now.

To complete this wish, the huge tortoise had been waiting aimlessly. But time passed, and no one that fulfilled the criteria showed up.

This fated person, had to be a strength path Gu Master, owned beast phantoms, and also strong to a degree.

Next, this strength path Gu Master had to be on the brink of death to receive this opportunity.

This is because, the blessed land's previous owner had a lot of lingering grudge and hatred, refusing to let others gain his fortune so easily.

But he still wanted to refine the second aperture Gu, thus there was such a requirement for the fated person to be as close to death as possible, just like him. Only someone who had shared his emotion could be qualified to gain everything.

But time passed, and the calamities and tribulations continued to occur.

The land spirit Ba Gui could not find a suitable strength path Gu Master.

To preserve its immortal essence, it could only choose to slumber helplessly.

The wide and huge blessed land, after many calamities and tribulations, had shrunk to less than one percent of its original size.

One calamity was enough to puncture a thousand holes in the blessed land.

Thus, there was a hole created, and a path to the outside world was connected to the blessed land.

Three roaming kids came here and relied on the blessed land's resources to cultivate to fruition. These were the three kings of the demonic path.

After the three kings got their revenge, they returned to the blessed land to live.

As time passed, they got more familiar with the blessed land and were a step away from rank six.

But in the end, none of them broke through and before dying, they remodelled the place into the three kings inheritance ground.

The three kings walked on the refinement, fire, and enslavement path, none was a strength path Gu Master.

The moment the remodelling began, the land spirit was woken up.

It watched silently without stopping them. It wanted to use this inheritance to attract qualified strength path Gu Masters as well.

When the three kings inheritance opened, countless Gu Masters entered, and increased the blessed land's immortal essence expenditure. As the blessed land faced the risk of destruction, the huge tortoise awakened from its slumber.

After waking up, the first thing the land spirit did was to find the fated person.

In the entire blessed land, there were many strength path Gu Masters. But those who fulfilled its requirements were none.

In ancient times, strength path was mainstream. But now that times have changed, strength path was eliminated, on the brink of extinction. Those who truly cultivated strength path to a high level, were even rarer.

Hearing Fang Yuan talk about the second aperture Gu, the land spirit Ba Gui was stunned: "You know a lot."

It felt strange, but did not pursue the matter.

To it, the fated person had already been found, now the next target was to refine the second aperture Gu.

However, it was not easy to refine second aperture Gu.

That is because, second aperture Gu was not a mortal Gu, it was a rank six Immortal Gu!

But Fang Yuan was already mentally prepared, directly asking: "Second aperture Gu is a rank six Gu. Rank five is mortal, rank six is immortal! To refine an Immortal Gu, the most basic condition is immortal essence! In the blessed land, how much immortal essence is left?"

The tortoise turned its body, gazing deep within the hall.

The flooring cracked open, as a hole appeared, and a bronze cauldron rose slowly. Eventually, the flooring closed up, leaving the cauldron alone in the hall.

This cauldron had three legs and two handles, it was filled with immortal essence inside.

The immortal essence was a greenish water, crystal clear and giving off a rusty smell.

There was very little immortal essence, only a thin layer left in the cauldron, and as time flowed, it slowly decreased drop by drop.

This is because, after the blessed land opened, countless Gu Masters explored, and entered and left multiple times, expending immortal essence.

"But this is already much better than in my previous life. As long as I ration it properly..." Fang Yuan looked at this layer of immortal essence, thinking deeply, as sparks seemed to be flying above his head.

In his previous life, after the three kings inheritance opened, the land spirit waited but did not meet its fated owner.

Only towards the end of the inheritance did the land spirit find a suitable, dying strength path Gu Master and transported him in.

This lucky person was a demonic path member, surviving the ordeal and benefitting from the crisis.

However, he was very poor at refining Gu worms, when he started the refinement process, he died.

Towards the end, Gu Masters had a great understanding of the three kings inheritance, and knew when to advance and retreat. They all had some trump cards or tokens to preserve their lives, and could easily leave at will.

Towards the end, the blessed land could not sustain it much more, and Gu Masters could freely use their Gu worms, fighting and causing bloodshed.

Where there are battles, there are deaths and injuries.

The land spirit found a chance, and chose a few strength path Gu Masters from among them.

But by then, it was already too late. There was a severe lack of immortal essence, and the land spirit was severely weakened, unable to do anything.

In the end, the blessed land continued to break down, as Gu Masters found this hall. Arriving here, they battled with the land spirit, and killed the strength path Gu Master who was refining the Gu.

Only then did they know, that San Cha mountain's blessed land held such a secret.

But at that time, immortal essence was expended, and the land spirit was dead, the Gu refinement ended in utter failure.

The legendary second aperture Gu, became extinct before the first one was even created.

"Second aperture Gu, allowing a Gu Master to have a second aperture. Even an idiot would know the value of this Gu! I have A grade aptitude now, one aperture holds ninety percent primeval essence. If I have the second aperture Gu, I would have a hundred and eighty percent primeval essence. At the same time, I can have double the primeval essence recovery speed, and even a second set of Gu worms. My battle strength will surge, and create history for myself. Once I succeed, I will definitely be the strongest person among the same rank!"

Fang Yuan was secretly excited.

But to refine this Immortal Gu, the process was really difficult, it would not be an easy task. Even Tie Mu Bai would feel stunned at this.

But to Fang Yuan, it was another situation all together.

Firstly, he was a rank six Gu Immortal in his past life who used the Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth, he also succeeded in refining the Spring Autumn Cicada, he had the precious experience of creating an Immortal Gu.

Secondly, ever since the three kings inheritance opened, he had been plotting.

He challenged strength path Gu Masters everywhere, eliminating his competition. Xue San Si, Century Boy, they were all chosen by the land spirit in his previous life, but now, they died in Fang Yuan's hands.

Lastly, he had the help of the land spirit.

In his previous life, the land spirit was already very weak when he saw the first lucky person. Towards the end, it was so feeble it got killed by a bunch of mortals.

But this life was different!

Fang Yuan approached death purposely, coming here in advance, he would receive great help from the land spirit.

"Back then, that Gu Immortal had made ample preparations to refine this Gu. With such a foundation, I have at least fifty percent chance of succeeding in this refinement.

Back when Fang Yuan refined Spring Autumn Cicada, he had less than twenty percent chance of succeeding. Now that he was refining the second aperture Gu, he had fifty percent, it was extremely high!

[1] Artificial Intelligence Back

Chapter 378: He is dead (Double Chapter)

Soon, Fang Yuan calmed down.

Second aperture Gu was only an opportunity, to make it a reality, it needed planning and effort.

"Whether the refinement of second aperture Gu succeeds or fails, a large amount of immortal essence will be consumed. Without immortal essence, the blessed land cannot contend against the upcoming earthly calamity and heavenly tribulation. That is to say, even if I become the owner of the blessed land, this blessed land can no longer be saved and I will have to give up on it."

"Thus, second aperture Gu will be my greatest reward for this trip."

However, the whole matter was not so easy and simple. The situation Fang Yuan was facing now was extremely complex.

With the start of the refinement of second aperture Gu, the remaining immortal essence would start decreasing sharply; the blessed land would weaken greatly and the assistance the land spirit could give would become lesser and lesser.

At the same time, he also needed to consider the Gu Masters within the blessed land. If they discovered this main hall, they were sure to attack together just like in his previous life and disrupt the process of the Gu refinement.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with sharp light and after pondering for a while, he took the initiative to demand: "Land spirit, tell me the recipe for refining the second aperture Gu."

Land spirit Ba Gui slowly nodded its head and its deep voice entered Fang Yuan's ears: "Then listen properly, this is the full content of the recipe."

"Rotten soil blood powder, treasure flower in the earth. Jade bone turned into petals, ice muscles into stalks and golden relic into the heart of the flower. A bright stellar fire, gather ice and snow into plains. Yang cloud burns with elixir fire below and yin clouds scatter sand like gold above, add beast phantoms in the middle until lightning crackles, creating beast strength placenta, and start collecting apertures... Wild grass grow wildly, the qi of blood like the sea. Three hundred years as spring, five hundred years as autumn. With unlimited divine opportunity, swim and roam in the wilds, adding in third watch, and another third watch, obtaining nine. Nine as extreme, the refinement is complete!"

The recipe content was huge and had close to ten thousand words.

Fang Yuan's expression turned grave as he listened.

There were up to a thousand steps in refining this second aperture Gu. The early stage involved hundreds of types of materials, the middle stage used up large numbers of rank four and rank five Gu, and it continued to become more arduous as it got closer to the last step, until finally, it needed the use of another rank six Immortal Gu!

"This is not good, the difficulty in refining second aperture Gu is many times higher than I estimated. The intel in my previous life only talked of the early stage of the recipe mixed with much misinterpretation from the people involved."

Fang Yuan's heart sank, the fifty percent confidence he had turned to about thirty percent after he heard the recipe.

"You don't need to worry too much, large amounts of materials and Gu worms for refining second aperture Gu had already been stored in this main hall."

With the land spirit's words, the whole main hall was suffused with dark blue light.

The brilliant radiance shone over the main hall; the relief sculptures on the surface of the main hall suddenly protruded out and turned into solid.

Fang Yuan was amazed at this change: "This is clearly a kind of storage method, this is the first time I am seeing it. Sigh, many methods of the ancient era had disappeared along the river of time."

Materials after materials of all kinds dazzled his eyes. There were at least five thousand Gu worms from rank one to rank five; among them, there were over six hundred rank four Gu and no less than eighty rank five Gu!

Rank five Gu which were very rare in the outside world had unexpectedly numbered to almost a hundred at this main hall. And the expensive rank four Gu had apparently become as rare as cabbages here.

"So many top-tier materials! There are so many Gu which I have never seen... these strength path Gu, if I obtain them, my battle strength will definitely rise by over ten-folds! And there are also over ten yellow gold relic Gu along with eight purple crystal relic Gu! If I used them, I will be able to advance to rank five peak stage within moments!"

Fang Yuan looked at these rank four and rank five Gu, and had a thought of giving up the refinement of second aperture Gu and directly taking all these Gu worms.

However, this impulse was immediately extinguished by him.

With the land spirit beside him keeping guard, these Gu worms could only be used to refine second aperture Gu and he was unable to use them for his personal use.

Secondly, second aperture Gu would be a great help in the future if it was refined, and it would provide enormous help even at rank six realm.

Second aperture Gu was a long term investment and its benefits would soar to the sky especially after one reached rank six.

"There is still one extremely crucial Gu worm left." Ba Gui said and opened his eyes, using all his strength to control this main hall.

The blue radiance increased sharply and reached and unbearable intensity.

The immortal essence in the bronze cauldron began deplete bit by bit.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, and within this blue light, he saw a confined Immortal Gu.

It was like a round gem, the gem's whole body was yellow and was hollow inside with a ball of purple smoke in it.

This smoke transformed constantly; suddenly turning into a pegasus or an immortal crane the next moment, or changing into a moving cloud or pure thunderbolt.

Following its appearance, a strong wine fragrance spread through the whole main hall.

Fang Yuan took a few breaths and immediately felt drunk; his eyes turned hazy and his mind became dizzy, he immediately held his breath.

"This is the rank six Immortal Gu — Divine Travel." The land spirit introduced.

Divine travel Gu!

Fang Yuan opened his eyes wide and stared at this Gu without even blinking.

Divine Travel Gu was very mysterious and also legendary. Its earliest appearance was in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> was the first classic of Gu. It appeared to be a story when one first read it but it actually held profound messages, recording the secrets of the ancient times and all kinds of Gu. Some Gu were directly described like wisdom Gu, strength Gu and so on. And some Gu were hidden, their descriptions were very vague, requiring the readers to dig through it and study carefully.

In the legends of Ren Zu, divine travel Gu's earliest appearance was beside Verdant Great Sun.

Verdant Great Sun drank four different top-tier wines in the world; the dense liquor aura in his body congealed into divine travel Gu.

Divine travel Gu had the power to send the Gu Master to any place in the world. But its activation required the Gu Master to be in a drunken state and its destination also could not be controlled.

Verdant Great Sun was transported to many dangerous places and suffered a lot due to divine travel Gu, his life on the line several times.

"Divine travel Gu might be one of the four great movement Gu and is very powerful at that, but its flaw is extremely big, who would dare to use it? Even Verdant Great Sun had no choice but to refine divine travel Gu into fixed immortal travel Gu in the end. No wonder the original master of this blessed land chose this Gu to refine into second aperture Gu."

Fixed immortal travel Gu was also one of the four great movement Gu and could send the Gu Master to any place they wanted to, even if the destination was at the edge of the world. But the prerequisite was that the Gu Master needed to have a concrete impression of their destination. If there was any huge changes to their destination, they would fail in using the fixed immortal travel Gu.

Fang Yuan carefully pondered and understood the intentions of this ancient strength path Gu Immortal.

Divine travel Gu might be at the noble rank six but its every use carried extremely high risk and had low worth in using. Thus, Verdant Great Sun refined it into fixed immortal travel Gu, while this ancient strength path Gu Master thought of using it to refine second aperture Gu.

The land spirit Ba Gui carefully resealed the divine travel Gu and asked: "When do you plan on beginning the refinement?"

"There is no rush, let me first study this recipe properly." Fang Yuan sat cross-legged on the spot and closed his eyes to contemplate.

Humans were the spirit of all living beings and Gu were the essence of the world.

After a Gu Master's cultivation reached a profound level, they would understand a principle; a Gu Master using Gu was not simply using the Gu worms as a tool. But rather, it was a way to understand heaven and earth.

Gu worms were the vessels that carry the law fragments of the Great Dao. Refining Gu was not simply following random steps but was based on the understanding of law fragments.

A recipe not only contained the process of refining Gu, but even more importantly, it contained its creator's comprehension of heaven and earth.

From this recipe, Fang Yuan could study the experimentation and insights of the original owner of this blessed land, the ancient strength path Gu Immortal. And when he compared them with his own experiences, he would gain an even deeper understanding of the Great Dao; this was absolutely a beneficial matter.

"Gu Master can only have one aperture from birth, if there was a second aperture, this would truly be an act of defying heaven. I see why divine travel Gu was chosen."

Fang Yuan opened his eyes after a long while, gaining a deeper understanding of the whole refinement process.

"Land spirit, let's start the refinement!"

"Okay." Land spirit immediately responded and gave two kinds of materials and a Gu worm to Fang Yuan.

First material was green pond rotten soil which originated ten thousand feet deep under a rotten and poisonous marsh, and was extremely toxic. Even Fang Yuan's arm would be rotten within a few breaths if he touched it.

Second material was a blood colored powder which had a rather large origin. The blood of eight kinds of immemorial desolate beasts were mixed, solidified and then grinded to form this powder.

The Gu worm, however, was common and Fang Yuan had come in touch with it at Qing Mao mountain.

It was earth treasury flower.

Earth treasury flower was a storage Gu. Flower wine monk planted it in the depths of the cave to store several Gu worms which were obtained by Fang Yuan in the end.

With the land spirit's assistance, Fang Yuan mixed the green pond rotten soil and eight desolate blood powder.

After the mixture became an evenly distributed soil, he planted the earth treasury flower in it.

Earth treasury flower immediately decayed and died when it entered the soil. Whether it was the toxicity of the green pond rotten soil or the violent nature of the eight desolate blood powder, they both were something the earth treasury flower could not endure easily.

However, Fang Yuan had already anticipated this situation and was not discouraged.

Land spirit took out another earth treasury flower Gu, and Fang Yuan casually planted it.

That ancient strength path Gu Immortal had already foreseen the probability of failure in every step and had thus prepared enough spare material.

After continuously failing several times, Fang Yuan finally succeeded in planting the earth treasury flower in the soil.

Green pool rotten soil's toxicity and the blood power of the eight desolate blood powder formed a kind of subtle balance, causing a strange transformation within the earth treasury flower Gu.

This was the first step of the recipe — rotten soil blood powder, treasure flower in the earth.

Next was 'jade bone turned into petals, ice muscles into stalks and golden relic into the heart of the flower'; it required the use of jade bone Gu, ice muscle Gu and yellow golden relic Gu along with skilled Gu refinement techniques.

Third step 'bright stellar fire, gather ice and snow into plains'; this could easily be misunderstood with stellar fire Gu and snowy plain Gu. But the firepower from that would be inadequate. In fact, the two phrases needed to be combined to be understood, the true answer was to use stellar fire prairie Gu together with snowy plain Gu, only then would there be balance.

Fang Yuan followed the order one by one.

At the fourth step 'Yang cloud burns with elixir fire below and yin clouds scatter sand like gold above'; this tested his multitasking ability.

Fang Yuan first used yang cloud Gu with elixir fire Gu, then activated yin cloud Gu and used golden sand Gu.

The yin and yang clouds mixed with the smoke from previous steps. Spheres of fiery orange elixir fire rose up from the yang cloud. The golden sand fell down from the yin cloud like a light drizzle.

"Yin above and yang below is anti-balance... this is the critical juncture! Go, white elephant beast phantom." Fang Yuan's eyes burst out with divine light as he activated all-out effort Gu and summoned white elephant phantom.

White elephant phantom collided into the center of yin and yang clouds and was grinded down by elixir fire and golden sand.

With a soft explosion, white elephant phantom turned into a ball of white light and revolved in the air.

"Again, black python beast phantom." Fang Yuan pointed and sacrificed another beast strength phantom.

Black python entered the center of the clouds and quickly turned into black ray and spun around the white light; the two were in an endless tangle.

"Stone turtle beast phantom, horse beast phantom." Another two beast phantoms flew out of Fang Yuan's body.

Four beast phantoms tangled against each other and formed a whirlpool of colorful light, but there was still something lacking.

"Strange! Why have they not fused?" Fang Yuan was baffled, this was the first difficulty he had ran into.

The colorful whirlpool was being grinded down by the elixir fire and the golden sand, and was continuously becoming smaller; the multiple auras could not fuse together.

Fang Yuan suddenly had a thought as he looked at the process which was about to end in failure: "Wait a second, could it be..."

He began to control the four beast phantoms.

White elephant beast phantom was steady and simple. Black python phantom was coiling and cold. Stone turtle phantom was still as a mountain. And horse beast phantom ran with the wind.

These four beast phantoms were just carelessly tangling with each other before, but under Fang Yuan's control now, each of them began to display their true disposition and nature.

Boom!

Thunder crackled and a strange transformation began.

Yin and yang clouds moved, yin cloud sank down and yang cloud rose up; the two forming into a whole entity.

The mist surged and mixed ceaselessly with lightning and thunder constantly crackling inside.

"So it was like that. No wonder it needed strength path Gu Master, although those who merely possessed beast phantoms would still not be able to succeed. The Gu Master must understand the true nature of each beast phantom to start the fusion." Fang Yuan let out a breath of relief and comprehended the process.

Rumble...

Lightning crackled and thunder exploded.

The sound was like war drums, becoming more condensed and finally blending into one.

Boom Boom Boom...

Under continuous rumbling sounds, the mist completely fused into one color before suddenly exploding.

A frenzy wind blew, dispersing all the clouds and mist.

Only one Gu remained in the air.

This Gu was rank five Gu and was like a disk. Its surface was rough like an embryo made of grass and soil. In the middle of the disk was a ferocious beast with the head of a horse, tusks of an elephant, body of a turtle and the tail of a snake.

"This is the beast strength placenta Gu." Fang Yuan relaxed his mind when he saw this Gu; the moment he relaxed, he fell down to the ground and fell asleep.

He had used a total of five days and five nights to refine this Gu. He had not rested a moment during this time and had been multitasking the whole time; his mental energy had been used to the limits, and he was extremely exhausted.

This sleep lasted for a day and a night before Fang Yuan woke up.

He touched the beast strength placenta Gu and recalled the recipe: "Yang cloud burns with elixir fire below and yin clouds scatter sand like gold from above, add beast phantoms in the middle till lightning crackles, creating beast strength placenta, and start collecting apertures..."

"Next is gathering apertures!" Thinking of this, he stood up and said to the land spirit: "Ba Gui, it is time."

Ba Gui was also straightforward: "Alright, I can send you to wherever you want to go in the blessed land."

A large map appeared in front of Fang Yuan along with all kinds of scenes, displaying everything in the blessed land.

Everything from Gu Masters, hairy men, dog beasts and so on were clearly shown.

"This place." Fang Yuan searched through the map before his gaze fixed on a place, and pointed at it.

Next moment, Fang Yuan disappeared and appeared in front of Tie Mu Bai.

"You." Tie Mu Bai was exploring the inheritance and was slightly surprised by Fang Yuan's sudden appearance.

But he calmed down soon and was just about to say something when Fang Yuan quickly waved his hand and luckily summoned a rock crocodile phantom.

Bam!

Tie Mu Bai's head was smacked by the rock crocodile's tail, and it exploded like a watermelon —

He, was dead.

Chapter 379: All according to plan

Fang Yuan killed Tie Mu Bai and immediately pounced on his headless corpse, grabbing his arm and letting his mind enter the aperture.

The aperture walls were crystal clear, as the primeval sea ebbed and flowed.

Rank five Gu Masters have purple crystal primeval essence. Initial stage is light purple primeval essence, middle stage is violet purple primeval essence, upper stage is deep purple primeval essence, and peak stage is crystal purple primeval essence.

Tie Mu Bai was a rank five peak stage Gu Master, he had crystal clear primeval essence, like the liquid form of crystals, great power was hidden within its beautiful appearance.

The difference between rank five peak stage and rank four upper stage was very huge. Furthermore, he had ninety-eight percent of such primeval essence, even a hundred Fang Yuan could not compare to him.

In the purple crystal primeval sea, there were Gu worms flying.

A golden small hand, flew randomly above the sea, like a golden light. This was Tie Mu Bai's vital Gu, the rank five Gu worm that he had once used when he battled Ku Mo and Wu Gui on San Cha mountain — turn gold Gu!

Turn gold Gu had great power, any lifeform that was hit by hit would turn into pure gold, losing their life.

Even Ku Mo and Wu Gui did not dare to take the attack head on. As for Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian and the other rank four peak stage cultivators, they did not even dare to observe the battle, taking the initiative to avoid them.

This was Tie Mu Bai's strongest long range attack method.

If Fang Yuan tried to use long range battle, the beast phantoms that possessed the strength qi would turn into golden statues after being hit by the golden light, sacrificing themselves. Fang Yuan would not be able to retrieve them anymore.

Other than turn gold Gu, at the bottom of the purple crystal sea, there was a yellow-gold current.

This current was like melted gold, swimming at the bottom of the sea.

This was the liquid metal Gu, also rank five, once activated, it had great defenses, and allowed a Gu Master to have no worries regarding defense. Most amazingly, it was liquid form, and could change its shape at will, even if it was broken through, it could regather itself like water, and was a tough nut to crack.

If Tie Mu Bai used liquid metal Gu, even if Fang Yuan used all his strength, he would not be able to break this defense.

In the purple crystal sea, there was another eyeball. It seemed inconspicuous, but it gave off a golden light at times, gathering attention and was more alluring than the stars in the sky.

This was the vajra stare Gu.

It was also rank five, but was not an investigative method, rather it was an attack type Gu.

Once activated by a Gu Master, the formless stare gains attacking power, like a giant pole slamming into a person's heart. Once eye contact was made, it could directly attack an opponent's soul.

This Gu was hidden by Tie Mu Bai, even during the battle against Ku Mo and Wu Gui, it was not used.

Once used, it would be a contest of souls between both Gu Masters, and the victor would be decided, it was a trump card that should only be used at the end.

Tie Mu Bai had once used many different Gu to strengthen his soul's foundation. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan walked the strength path, his soul was not strengthened.

If Tie Mu Bai used the vajra stare Gu, he just needed to maintain eye contact with Fang Yuan for a second, and Fang Yuan's soul would be completely destroyed.

To use this vajra stare Gu, golden eyes have to be used.

If one used ordinary eyes for this, they might turn themselves blind. Only by using two golden eye Gu, and turning one's own eyes into golden eyes could they use the vajra stare Gu safely.

Evidently, since Tie Mu Bai had the vajra stare Gu, he naturally had golden eyes.

Just like how Fang Yuan turned his skin into bronze skin, and bones into essence iron bones.

Other than these three rank five Gu, Tie Mu Bai's body also had four rank four Gu worms. Golden dragon Gu, golden breeze Gu, golden coat Gu, golden aurora Gu, all of them were outstanding Gu worms, and were high quality Gu worms within the metal path.

These Gu worms were all excavated by Fang Yuan.

After confirming that Tie Mu Bai did not have any other Gu worms on him, Fang Yuan took out the beast strength placenta Gu, and activated it around Tie Mu Bai's stomach.

After Tie Mu Bai lost his life, his aperture started to shrink. Right now, after being sucked by the beast strength placenta Gu, the aperture flew out of Tie Mu Bai's body, and landed in the placenta, devoured by the wild beast inside the placenta.

After devouring the aperture, the rough and coarse beast strength placenta Gu became lustrous and shiny, the original embryo looked like it was made of soil and had crevices on the surface, but now it looked different, thick and tightly packed, just like a concrete brick.

This beast strength placenta Gu was used like this, according to the blessed land's original owner's peculiar idea. Continuously absorbing Gu Masters aperture, then slowly accumulating and changing qualitatively.

To refine the second aperture Gu, apertures were naturally the main ingredient.

The beast strength placenta Gu that was refined was intended to plunder other people's apertures. Killing lives to attain success, this was a demonic path method, one could easily tell that the ancient strength path Gu Immortal was not a kind person.

This beast strength placenta Gu, if others used it, they might feel guilt, but Fang Yuan was extremely fine with using it, he had no mental pressure at all.

In his previous life, to refine the Spring Autumn Cicada, he killed people in more than ten thousand miles of land, blood flowed into a river as he caused an immense bloodshed in the world, he could not even count how many people he killed. How could killing a single Gu Master now affect him?

"Good, good, good! This beast strength placenta Gu, after absorbing Tie Mu Bai's aperture, it already raised the second aperture Gu's aptitude to forty percent. Great, excellent."

"Using numbers to make up for quality in order to break through, this is the rule of using sheer quantity to trigger a qualitative change. Going beyond the mortal world, and becoming an Immortal Gu, how can there be no price to pay? Back then when I refined the Spring Autumn Cicada, I slaughtered over ten million people, that was also because of this."

"The better the aperture that is absorbed and the larger the numbers, the higher the aptitude of the second aperture Gu that is refined in the future. Next, I have to kill Gu Masters, go on a killing spree and use all their apertures to raise my beast strength placenta Gu. Hahaha, hahahaha..."

Fang Yuan inspected the beast strength placenta Gu carefully, extremely pleased and raised his head up as he laughed.

Why did he kill Tie clan's group? It was to make Tie clan furious and send a rank five Gu Master.

The arrival of one rank five Gu Master would break the balance, causing a chain reaction and attracting even more rank five Gu Masters.

"These rank five, rank four Gu Masters are all my prey! To assist me in refining the second aperture Gu!" Fang Yuan laughed.

All his plots and schemes, these few years of planning, and all the risks he took, it was all for this moment.

How incredibly amazing is this, this is the best feeling!!

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, his black hair flying with the wind, as demonic blaze burned in his eyes.

Looking at actual battle strength, the rank five peak stage Tie Mu Bai was over a hundred times stronger than Fang Yuan!

Just simply the turn gold Gu, if Fang Yuan was hit, he would be dead, there was no way to survive.

Even if Tie Mu Bai only used rank four Gu, his rank five peak stage crystal purple primeval essence was not something Fang Yuan's yellow gold primeval essence could compete with.

But!

In the three kings inheritance, Gu Masters were restricted by the heavenly power, and were unable to use their Gu worms, at the same time, their defenses were all limited, and they became extremely fragile.

But Fang Yuan was different —

He has the land spirit's help.

What was the land spirit? The lord of the blessed land! With its help, Fang Yuan could use his Gu worms inside the three kings inheritance.

Meanwhile, Tie Mu Bai had his rank five peak stage cultivation, but his strong Gu set was unusable.

Standing before Fang Yuan, he was a living target, just a livestock. Stripped of all his defenses, he was fragile as a baby.

He could not even use a single metal path Gu worm, he could not even self-detonate.

He worked hard all his life, accumulating this set of Gu worms, and now it all went to Fang Yuan.

After Fang Yuan killed Tie Mu Bai, he kept all the Gu worms inside his aperture.

The Spring Autumn Cicada's aura could only suppress rank four Gu worms. These three rank five Gu could not be controlled by Fang Yuan, but because of the location, these Gu worms were restricted by the heavenly power, unable to move at all.

As Fang Yuan's primeval essence refined them, they gave up and changed owners.

"Good, you obtained a rank five peak stage aperture, this way, the second aperture Gu's aptitude has risen to forty percent. But you must take note, to transport you earlier, and support your attack, we expended quite a bit of immortal essence." Land spirit's voice came, warning Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stopped laughing, his expression calming down: "I have already considered that."

He sneered, his eyes glowing with brilliance, as his tone was extremely confident and in control of the situation.

He continued: "Ba Gui, you have slept for too long, the blessed land was remodelled by the three kings, you lost too much control of it. Even as the spirit of the blessed land, although you can overwrite these changes, that would use up too much immortal essence. There is little immortal essence left inside the cauldron, if we split these essence into sixteen portions, then the amount we used earlier would be half a portion."

Ba Gui was stunned, praising: "You are absolutely correct. You actually managed to calculate the expenditure of the immortal essence so accurately, your performance has truly amazed me!"

Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal in his past life, he was extremely familiar with the use of immortal essence. It was easy to make such accurate calculations.

"I estimate that among the sixteen portions, at least eight is needed for the refinement of the second aperture Gu. As for the remaining eight, we need four to sustain the blessed land, and to kill Gu Masters, we need a bit more than three portions. The final bit would be kept to deal with emergencies.

But Ba Gui said: "Young man, you are wrong this time. To refine the Immortal Gu, we need ten portions, and to maintain the three kings inheritance, we only need two. After you kill enough people, I will close the blessed land."

"No, I am not wrong." Fang Yuan shook his head: "To refine the second aperture Gu, although we need to expend immortal essence, the expenditure of some steps can be replaced with primeval stones. That way, we can save two portions of immortal essence. Furthermore, you cannot close the inheritance, you have to keep the entrance open the entire time."

"Why?" Land spirit asked.

Fang Yuan replied: "Because once you close the inheritance, the matter of me killing rank five Gu Masters would be exposed. By then, such a situation would attract even stronger foes."

"Even if you close the blessed land, you cannot chase away the Gu Masters who remain in the inheritance. That is because the three kings modified the blessed land, you will need to waste a lot of immortal essence to expel them. Immortal essence is already running low, even portion is important, it is needed for refinement."

"Towards the later stage of the refinement, immortal essence will run low, and the blessed land will be on the brink of collapsing, and have lots of loopholes, connecting to the outside world. It is no use closing the blessed land, when your strength falls drastically, this hall would be discovered. By then, we would be attacked by the Gu Masters, and the refinement would be likely to fail."

After a while of silence, the land spirit said: "You are right, but your method has a fatal flaw. If we use primeval stones to replace the immortal essence, you need at least thirty million primeval stones. Do you have so many?"

Fang Yuan laughed loudly!

"I only have a million primeval stones on me, it is obviously not enough. But it is not a problem, there are other Gu Masters, especially these rank four and five Gu Masters, they are definitely rich, after we kill them, do we have to worry about primeval stones?"

Ba Gui considered it for a bit: "You are right, the help I can give you will shrink. Towards the end of the refinement, that is the most important step, we will act according to your suggestion."

Chapter 380: Slaughtering Rank Five

A battle between dogs ended.

"Steel armor dog group's defense is so strong." The rank five demonic Gu Master Ku Mo had several hundred steel armor dogs around him, feeling extremely pleased.

The steel armor dogs had thick leather armor, black and heavy, like steel. In the King Quan Inheritance, it had the greatest defense among dogs for the first fifty rounds.

Just earlier, Ku Mo controlled the dog groups, and had a victorious battle.

His battle result was outstanding, using the dog enslavement Gu to recruit a jade eye dog king.

This jade eye dog king was not only a hundred beast king, it also had a wild Gu worm that was effective against the Yin dogs.

"Last time, I failed because of the Yin dogs. Ordinary dogs cannot hit these formless bodies, with the jade eye dog king, I have no fear now."

This was only the eighteenth round of the King Quan Inheritance, and Ku Mo already had a dog king, and a large number of steel armor dogs.

He was after all a rank five Gu Master, he had amazing methods.

At the same time, his luck this time was great.

King Quan Inheritance was like this, it was the one which required luck the most among the three inheritances. If you start out well, your advantages will snowball and make it easier to pass the middle and later stages.

"Last time, I only got to the sixty-eighth round, I am too embarrassed to speak of such a result! This time, I got lucky and had such a great start. But I cannot be complacent, Tie Mu Bai chose King Xin Inheritance this time, I heard that previously, he got to over eighty rounds."

Thinking of Tie Mu Bai, Ku Mo's heart became heavy.

He knew that if he fought alone, he was not Tie Mu Bai's match. Thus, when he chose the inheritance, he purposely avoided Tie Mu Bai, and chose the King Quan Inheritance.

The truth is, among the three inheritances, King Xin Inheritance was the easiest to get through for the first few rounds. The Gu Master can disrupt the hairy men with words, and win without a fight.

This shortcut method was obviously spread out by Fang Yuan.

Ku Mo thought about it for a while, before collecting his thoughts and decided to use his time to continue advancing through the rounds.

Just at this moment, before him, space tore open and an unfamiliar young man appeared.

"Eh? Who is it!" Ku Mo was shocked!

He had tried the three kings inheritance many times. He had a clear understanding of it, but this scene had happened before him causing him to be stunned in disbelief.

The person was naturally Fang Yuan.

He heard Ku Mo's shouting and laughed: "Who is it? The person who wants your life!"

Saying so, he activated golden dragon Gu.

The golden dragon appeared, roaring. Its dragon whiskers swayed with the wind, as its dragon eyes stared fiercely, brandishing its four fearsome claws.

Ku Mo saw this and almost peed his pants!

He screamed in disbelief: "How can this be! How can you use any Gu? How is this possible!!!"

Moments before death, he shuddered and activated his Gu worms hurriedly.

But he got no response.

Roar!

Golden dragon came attacking, scratching and almost smashing his entire upper body.

The great Ku Mo, an expert of a generation, and old demonic powerhouse, died just like this.

When he died, he did not even manage to use his token. Of course, with the land spirit's manipulation, even if he used the token, there would be no effect.

"Golden dragon Gu attacks really fiercely, but the handling is so rough, I cannot control it meticulously." Fang Yuan recalled the attack, he had wanted to just smash Ku Mo's skull, but he ended up destroying his entire upper body, slightly shocking him.

Thankfully, the aperture was near the stomach, and did not get destroyed.

Fang Yuan walked forward, his mind entering the aperture, and started to loot it.

Ku Mo had eight Gu worms, but only one rank five Gu, called soft bones Gu, it was very despicable.

This Gu could turn the bones of any lifeforms soft within a radius of twenty-five kilometres. Even if Fang Yuan turned his bones into essence iron bones, he would still be affected and his bones would turn soft eventually. By then, Fang Yuan would have no way to fight back.

Without his skeleton to support him, he would be like a paralyzed man, lying on the ground, his intestines would squeeze together and his blood vessels and muscles would clog one another. Even without any external attacks, before long, he would die from this.

As for his other seven Gu, they were all rank four. These Gu all had to do with the bone path, and were not particularly good ones.

"It's a pity, I do not know much about the bone path, the most I can do is scratch the surface of it. If I inherit this set of Gu worms, the battle strength I can display would not be half of Ku Mo. I should keep it for now." Fang Yuan assessed in his mind.

At Ku Mo's level, the Gu set he created was completely customised for himself, using his battle style, his understanding of the bone path, and his understanding towards battles and Gu masters.

Fang Yuan was most skilled in the blood path. In his previous life, he benefited from the blood sea inheritance, and used the blood path to start his conquest. He had a deep understanding of the blood path, if Ku Mo was a blood path Gu Master, the situation would be different.

After taking Ku Mo's Gu worms, Fang Yuan used the beast strength placenta Gu and devoured his aperture.

After receiving nutrients, beast strength placenta Gu grew a little again. Its concrete surface had a thin layer of luster, and the surface was smoother, like poorly made porcelain.

It was a pity for Ku Mo, a great expert born as a lone cultivator, slogging it out alone his whole life. He had many encounters and opportunities in his life, and together with his hard work, after experiencing great hardships, he reached this level.

Eventually, he died, and all his hard work and fruits of his labor became Fang Yuan's loot. A great rank five Gu Master fell from the apex, becoming Fang Yuan's stepping stone.

"Too bad the dog enslavement Gu can't be taken back, if not these dogs would be mine to manipulate too." Fang Yuan looked at the dogs as he sighed, vanishing on the spot.

...

A battle was ongoing intensely.

Wu Gui manipulated the chrysanthemum akita dogs, fighting and entangling with a large pack of lightning symbol dogs.

Chrysanthemum akita dogs were a type of dog with great unity, the greater their numbers, the greater their strength. But Wu Gui was unlucky, he had only forty or so chrysanthemum akita dogs.

He placed these dogs at the frontline, as he concentrated in controlling them.

The chrysanthemum akita dogs were fighting a lightning symbol dog dog pack five times their sizes, they were all injured but not dead. The exquisite combination and cooperation showed Wu Gui's exemplary talent in enslaving beasts.

Wu Gui had become an enslavement path Gu Master many years ago, but eventually because of a lack of resources, he had to change paths.

Swoosh!

Fang Yuan suddenly appeared behind Wu Gui.

Wu Gui was spending all his effort controlling the chrysanthemum akita dogs, he did not sense Fang Yuan's arrival.

If it was during normal times, he would use an investigative Gu, and once Fang Yuan appeared, he would get attacked immediately. But in this Gu Immortal blessed land, he was just an ordinary person only able to control dog enslavement Gu and some others, all the body modifications on him were also completely restricted.

Of course, it was also due to Wu Gui concentrating deeply on the dog battle.

Fang Yuan did not trash talk, he waved his hand and a bone spike flew out.

Puchi!

A crisp sound, and a long spear-like bone spike pierced Wu Gui's heart, as the sharp pointy tip stabbed into the ground.

Wu Gui's pupils shrunk to pin-size as he was completely stunned and confused at this fatal attack.

"Who... tried to kill me!" He opened his mouth and fresh blood oozed out like a river.

He slowly turned around, trying desperately to see the culprit's face.

But unfortunately, he lost all signs of life when he turned halfway.

Wu Gui's body collapsed like a pile of mud, hanging on the bone spike.

This demonic expert who was even more senior than Tie Mu Bai, famous two hundred years ago, had died as well.

When he died, his eyes were staring wide, trying to see who was his murderer.

But this simple wish was not granted.

The great Wu Gui, died with a grievance!

After he died, the chrysanthemum akita dogs who lost their master's manipulation immediately got engulfed by the lightning symbol dogs. These lightning symbol dogs howled as they pounced on Fang Yuan.

Roar!

Fang Yuan waved his hand, as the golden dragon appeared again, slaughtering all these lightning symbol dogs who did not know better.

Fang Yuan quickly came to Wu Gui's corpse, doing the same thing again. Keeping his Gu worms then feeding his aperture to the beast strength placenta Gu.

Wu Gui had one rank five Gu.

It was oval and black like a yuhua stone[1] . But the surface had seven white markings, and it looked extremely peculiar and dark. It was the pitch black Gu.

Once the Gu is activated, it would ooze out black smoke. Any Gu worms below rank six would get contaminated by the black smoke and receive various degrees of sealing, losing their abilities.

As for his other Gu worms, there were eight to nine, all rank four. But they were mixed among different paths, and were a mess, unlike Ku Mo and Tie Mu Bai's complete Gu set.

"These are Wu Gui's Gu worms, although they can form into a set, they are not a complete set. The reason why he can roam the southern border is mostly due to the pitch black Gu."

Undeniably, pitch black Gu is an extremely useful rank five Gu.

Fang Yuan was extremely happy to have obtained it.

He kept the pitch black Gu into his aperture, but placed the rest of the rank four Gu into his pocket.

His aperture already had many Gu worms, among them, he had five rank five Gu worms, and many rank four Gu. This was placing a lot of pressure on his aperture.

Mostly importantly, it was due to the Spring Autumn Cicada, this rank six Gu was recovering, and it was emitting great pressure on Fang Yuan's aperture.

"The flow of time in the blessed land is three times out the outside world, accelerating Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery. I have to race against time, quickly refining the second aperture Gu. With the second aperture, I would be able to relieve the pressure Spring Autumn Cicada is giving me."

To Fang Yuan, the situation was extremely rushed.

He did not only want to refine the second aperture Gu, he also wanted to guard against this major threat, the Spring Autumn Cicada. Towards the end of the refinement, the blessed land would be full of flaws, and after connecting to the outside world, he might receive the group attack of many Gu Masters.

By then, the land spirit would be weak and powerless, it would be useless and Fang Yuan would be in the most danger during that period.

"Refining the second aperture Gu, to closer we get to the end, the tougher it gets. Especially that final step, I need to use the divine travel Gu, I will need to focus and concentrate, my body would be in huge danger!"

Wu Gui's demise, was the best lesson to Fang Yuan, he had to guard against such situations.

But his situation was slightly different.

"I have another chess piece, that is Bai Ning Bing! Hehehe, she used the poison vow Gu before, she can be trusted. It seems that towards the end, I will need her to protect me."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan vanished, and appeared before Bai Ning Bing.

"Fang Yuan, how did you get here so suddenly?" Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Yuan, shocked and suspicious.

[1] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yuhua_Stone Back

Chapter 381: All must die!

Bai Ning Bing widened her eyes in shock as Fang Yuan suddenly appeared out of nowhere.

By now, Gu Masters already had a clear understanding of the three kings inheritance. And because she was at Fang Yuan's side, Bai Ning Bing had much deeper understanding of three kings inheritance.

However, precisely because of this 'deep understanding', she was even more shocked.

Fang Yuan's sudden appearance looked like a simple phenomenon but it contained astonishing implications!

"Bai Ning Bing, do you still remember our vow? I wonder if you still want Yang Gu now?" Fang Yuan did not mention how he appeared but looked at Bai Ning Bing with his unfathomable and abyssal gaze with his hands behind his back.

"Hmph, as if you don't know the answer." Bai Ning Bing snorted and narrowed her blue eyes.

She knew Fang Yuan would not speak aimlessly, he definitely had a motive: "It seems you need my help? Speak up, don't try to conceal anything, otherwise I will not help."

Fang Yuan laughed loudly without being moved: "Back at Shang clan city, we took a poison vow that if one side is in mortal danger, the other must help. I will tell you truthfully that not long later, I will be besieged by Gu Masters and I need you as my protector to block any obstruction towards my Gu refinement."

"Gu Masters' besiegement? Hehe, I am not surprised, there are plenty of Gu Masters who want to kill you. But refining Gu? What Gu are you refining?"

Fang Yuan was straightforward this time and told the whole story directly.

The most important thing now was that he needed Bai Ning Bing's full cooperation. This matter also could not be concealed. Bai Ning Bing was not someone so easy to fool.

If because of him hiding the truth, some misunderstanding occurred and caused the Gu refinement to fail in the end, it would be truly disastrous.

"What! This Gu Immortal blessed land's land spirit is still alive? You are refining an Immortal Gu? You have truly large guts, you are looking for your own doom! Wait a second. What did you say just now? You killed Tie Mu Bai, and also Wu Gui and Ku Mo?"

Fang Yuan kept it brief and said the whole story in a few sentences but the information it contained was huge, sending an enormous shock to Bai Ning Bing's mind.

She felt like she was listening to a story.

Fang Yuan did not speak anymore but directly took out his loot.

"These Gu!" Bai Ning Bing looked at the Gu worms Fang Yuan took out and was flabbergasted, even losing her self-control.

These Gu were genuine. They were the best proof.

"You really killed them?" Bai Ning Bing stared at Fang Yuan, shock clearly visible in her eyes.

Who was Tie Mu Bai?

He was Southern Border's super clan Tie clan's previous clan leader.

He was a genius with outstanding innate talent, his temperament was even more firm and unyielding.

His battle accomplishments in his whole life shone with splendor. And with his talent, he researched many battle tactics of the metal path, causing countless enemies to be terror-stricken by the mention of him.

At a young age, he roamed outside and his name spread throughout Southern Border. In his middle years, he ruled Tie clan with an iron fist and made everyone fear him. At his old age, he became an emperor of a region, his reputation spread wide with no one daring to disobey him!

He was venerated as the glory of Tie clan, radiance of the righteous path. When he announced his seclusion and retirement, many people, be it demonic path or righteous path, let out a breath of relief.

Now, he was out of seclusion and that shook many clans. Even Shang Yan Fei would have to bow in front of him to greet him.

The rank five Gu Master of Wu clan Wu Lan Shan was the cousin of the current Wu clan leader, but even she had to bow despite her pride when facing Tie Mu Bai.

And this Tie Mu Bai had died by Fang Yuan's hands!

Not only him, Wu Gui and Ku Mo, two rank five Gu Masters also lost their lives to Fang Yuan!

Even more absurdly, not only did they die, all their Gu worms were taken by Fang Yuan!!

"These three rank five Gu Masters really died with grievance..." even Bai Ning Bing, this outsider, felt stifled at the deaths of Tie Mu Bai and others.

"Alright, it is about time. Next, I will send you to King Quan Inheritance. Advance through the rounds according to my instructions. I need dog beasts, the more the better." Fang Yuan's tone was hasty.

"Hmph, I did not say I will help you." Bai Ning Bing's gaze flickered.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Don't worry, if I succeed, I will give Yang Gu to you. Besides, there will be other benefits as well. After leaving San Cha mountain, you can go wherever you want to, I won't stop you if you want to part ways and will also welcome you if you want to go together. But whether you agree or not, I will refine the Gu."

Bai Ning Bing was exasperated: "You! You shameless guy, you are relying on the poison vow to force me?"

If Fang Yuan was attacked and died while refining Gu, then according to the poison vow, Bai Ning Bing would also die. That is to say, Bai Ning Bing must protect Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sighed, his tone became mild and even seemed to have a trace of gentleness: "Ning Bing, this is not a threat, but cooperation. Think about it, since Qing Mao mountain, we have been cooperating, and no dangers have been able to stop us as many enemies fell under our feet. This time is also not an exception. Weren't you always wanting Yang Gu? You can turn back to a male when you obtain it. Or have you have become fond of your female identity?"

Bai Ning Bing felt goosebumps all over her when she heard Fang Yuan call her Ning Bing.

And when she heard Fang Yuan's final sentence, she clearly knew Fang Yuan was spurring her; she could not help feeling provoked and shouted: "Shut your mouth!"

"It is settled then." Fang Yuan laughed loudly and waved his hand, giving Bai Ning Bing a dog enslavement Gu, then disappeared.

The scene before Bai Ning Bing also changed suddenly, and she was sent to the first round of King Quan Inheritance by the land spirit.

Fang Yuan suddenly appeared in front of Wu Lan Shan.

Wu Lan Shan got a shock when someone suddenly appeared in front of her. But she was a famed figure and a majestic rank five Gu Master, calming her mind in seconds.

"Little Beast King, it is you! You can casually enter and exit this place?" Wu Lan Shan retreated a step, sharp light blossoming in her beautiful eyes.

Fang Yuan pointed his little finger and shot out a bone spear.

Puchi!

There was a soft sound as the bone spear pierced through Wu Lan Shan's heart like lightning.

Wu Lan Shan's beautiful flower-like appearance seemed to be frozen as she looked at Fang Yuan incredulously: "You... you can use Gu?"

The moment she finished saying this, her aura dissipated indicating her demise.

Another rank five Gu Master died.

However, Fang Yuan did not obtain her rank five Gu.

The moment Wu Lan Shan died, a mysterious light burst out of her body and enveloped her three rank five Gu worms, tearing through space and bringing them away.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, he knew Wu clan had a rank six Immortal Gu called no loss Gu which possessed the mystical ability to retrieve precious Gu worms.

Although this blessed land could restricted Gu worms of rank one to five, it could not restrict Immortal Gu.

In fact, no blessed lands can restrict the abilities of Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan took the rest of the rank four Gu which were also quite valuable. After that, he took out beast placenta Gu and swallowed Wu Lan Shan's aperture.

This was already the fourth rank five Gu Master's aperture.

Beast placenta Gu was nourished and looked like a delicate pottery, and gave a sleek feeling at touch.

Fang Yuan analyzed it and found the aptitude had increased to seventy-five percent.

The aptitude became more difficult to raise the higher it became. At first, the aptitude had directly raised to forty percent when the beast placenta Gu had swallowed just Tie Mu Bai's aperture. Later, it swallowed apertures of Wu Gui, Ku Mo and Wu Lan Shan in a row, and was only able to raise by another thirty-five percent.

"Of course, this has to do with the foundation of the Gu Master. There are altogether five rank five Gu Masters on San Cha mountain. But only Tie Mu Bai, Ku Mo and Wu Gui are at rank five peak stage; among them, Tie Mu Bai's foundation was the most profound with the huge amount of resources from Tie clan. Wu Lan Shan and Wang Xiao are both at rank five upper stage. And Chou Jiu is only at rank five initial stage. Killing these people might not be enough to raise the aptitude by another ten percent. But no worries, there are plenty of Gu Masters, Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian and the rest, all of them must die!"

...

"Corpse dog is purple all over, its skin is slightly rotten, its lower back is crooked and its canines protrude out. Use Yin dogs to restrain them and you will definitely succeed."

"Choose the left path, the reward for that round is three tasks at once Gu which will be of great help to you."

"Next, you will encounter a heavy tai dog king. It is in a seriously injured state but is even more ferocious. You will need to sacrifice a lot of dogs to capture it. This dog king is the only heavy tai dog king in the first twenty rounds. At the twenty-second round, there will be a large group of wandering heavy tai dogs, you can use heavy tai dog king to directly recruit them without losing anything!"

There would be a voice guiding Bai Ning Bing every time she progressed through a round.

This voice was of the land spirit.

Immortal essence was scarce, the land spirit moved Bai Ning Bing to King Quan Inheritance and was not willing to misuse immortal essence on her.

Bai Ning Bing could only go through each round personally.

However, although the land spirit's control over the blessed land had fallen to rock bottom, it was extremely clear about the contents of three kings inheritance.

There was almost no loss in immortal essence for it to guide Bai Ning Bing, but to Bai Ning Bing, it was of extremely huge help; as if there was a bright lantern guiding Bai Ning Bing through the dark tunnel.

Bai Ning Bing was able to make best choice at every round and her strength continued to expand like a snowball.

"Next, you will encounter a Gu Master as your opponent. But no need to worry, he has just fought a huge battle and only has few dog beasts remaining, you will be able to eliminate him easily. At that time, I will confine him, and after you kill him and take his Gu, you can greatly increase the number of your Gu worms." The land spirit guided again.

Bai Ning Bing nodded and slowly walked out of the fog.

"It is you..." Her opponent was clearly shocked at her sight.

Bai Ning Bing was also stupefied, this person was none other than the person who had tried to make things difficult for her and Fang Yuan before he entered the inheritance; the Yun clan's young clan leader Yun Luo Tian.

Yun Luo Tian arrogantly snorted: "You are called Bai Ning Bing, right? It is your bad luck you ran into me, you don't even have half the amount of dogs I have..."

He had not even finished speaking when he stopped. His eyes opened wide and his throat let out a strange ka ka sound like a rooster that had its throat jammed.

From the mist behind Bai Ning Bing, a large numbers of dog beasts walked out one after another.

Endlessly...

Chapter 382: Continue Killing

"Impossible! How can you have so many dog beasts?!" Yun Luo Tian screamed, pointing at Bai Ning Bing, as he shivered, his expression looked like he had seen a ghost.

The sheer number of beasts around Bai Ning Bing had surpassed his wildest imagination.

"How many rounds has it been? Even a rank five Gu Master cannot reach such a number!!" Yun Luo Tian screamed as loudly as he could to vent the horror in his heart.

"You must control some loophole, you cheated. You actually cheated, you shameless scoundrel!!"

Yun Luo Tian's composure was completely gone, he no longer had the attitude of an Yun clan young clan leader.

Bai Ning Bing sighed lightly, Yun Luo Tian was right, he hit the nail on the head.

It is true, she cheated. And it was the blessed land's spirit who helped her.

Under the land spirit's guidance, she had an easy time going through the King Quan Inheritance, like she was on a vacation, it was a complete walk in the park. Compared to the difficulties she faced back when she explored the inheritance alone, this was a clear contrast.

"The incredulous feeling of cheating cannot be described with words! If doing this means I am despicable, I would rather become even more despicable than this, hehehe."

Bai Ning Bing exclaimed as she waved her hands.

Woof, woof, woof...

Countless dogs received her commands and moved like flood water.

In Yun Luo Tian's vision, he could see a sea of dogs charging towards him like a tsunami.

He gritted his teeth: "Bai Ning Bing, do not be smug. Once I get out, I will expose you in front of everyone! You know such a huge secret, everyone will be interested, especially those rank five Gu Masters! Hahaha, you are finished!"

Saying so, he took out a token and used it.

But nothing happened.

"Eh?" Yun Luo Tian was shocked, activating it again.

"What happened? Why is it not working? I used it the last time and I was transported out immediately." His gaze flashed as a bad feeling emerged in his heart, causing his expression to turn uncertain.

He took out another unused token, he was the Yun clan young clan leader, he had two tokens to protect him.

But this time, there was no effect either. The token stopped working.

Yun Luo Tian stared with his eyes wide opened, staring at his token, sweat emerging on his forehead.

Bai Ning Bing's dog army had surrounded him, and started slaughtering his dog group.

"How can this happen? Send me out now!" Yun Luo Tian's breathing became quicker, as he used the token frantically, to no avail.

"Ah!" He screamed, his beautiful face distorted with fear. His hair was messy and his eyes were bright red, like an angered bull.

"It is you, you did this didn't you? It must be you! You made the token ineffective, hehe, what great methods you have. But be clear of this, I am the great Yun clan young clan leader. If you kill me, you would offend Yun clan. The entire Yun clan won't let you off."

Yun Luo Tian recovered from his fear and screamed at Bai Ning Bing.

His arrogance as the Yun clan young clan leader was sustaining him, not letting him kneel down and beg for his life, instead he was getting more haughty.

But such an attitude was completely useless against Bai Ning Bing.

"I'm not even afraid of Tie clan, would I fear your tiny Yun clan?" Bai Ning Bing snickered.

On the battlefield, Yun Luo Tian was alone, his dog groups were no match for Bai Ning Bing's, massacred till none was left.

Bai Ning Bing willed, and the closest dog barked before pouncing on Yun Luo Tian.

Yun Luo Tian struggled with his life, but his strength could not match the dog.

His throat was bitten by the dog, as blood poured out of it.

As for the other beasts,they stood in a circle and waited.

"I curse you... I curse you have to a terrible death!" Yun Luo Tian cursed before he died, his tone filled with hatred and anger.

Bai Ning Bing shook her head in disdain, walking forward and keeping Yun Luo Tian's Gu worms.

This Yun Luo Tian walked the cloud path, they were all rank four Gu, and were all of high quality. As for the enslavement path Gu worms he obtained from King Quan Inheritance, they greatly benefited Bai Ning Bing's Gu worms.

As for his corpse, it was teleported by the land spirit, sent to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was stepping on Wang Xiao, forcing out the location of Wu mountain.

Wang Xiao was the owner of Wu mountain, a rank five upper stage Gu Master, a true regional emperor. He was an established expert.

If it was outside, ten Fang Yuan added together would not be his match. But here, Fang Yuan defeated him easily, like dealing with a baby.

Wang Xiao was extremely angry, he was stepped on by Fang Yuan, as his face and the soil made intimate contact.

For a great rank five Gu Master, the lord of Wu mountain, this was a great humiliation!

"You want to know how to enter Wu mountain? Hehe, stop your wishful thinking! Kill me if you want, after you kill me, you will not be able to know that true path to enter the mountain."

Wang Xiao sneered as he struggled intensely, but Fang Yuan could use his strength path Gu worms, Wang Xiao could not compare to him in terms of strength.

After an intense struggle, he was breathing heavily out of exhaustion, while Fang Yuan's leg was still firm as a mountain.

Wu mountain was a slightly famous mountain among the hundred thousand mountains of Southern Border.

This mountain was mysterious and illusionary, hidden in a deep layer of fog. In the fog, there were many small paths, but only one led inside.

Wang Xiao knew this path, and thus entered the mountain and made the mountain's resources his.

Like Qing Mao mountain, a famous mountain like Wu mountain had at least three to four spirit springs. Other than that, there were large numbers of wild beasts and wild Gu. All sorts of resources that could sustain three to four middle-size clans.

But Wu mountain was completely owned by Wang Xiao.

"Wu mountain is a natural danger zone, it is easy to defend and no matter how many righteous Gu Masters there are, they cannot break into it by force. Wang Xiao used this to become a regional emperor, living freely and easily. If I obtain it, I could use it as my base, and I would have no worries for my rank five resources." Fang Yuan thought.

Wu mountain was Wang Xiao's good fortune, Fang Yuan desired it greatly. But Wang Xiao refused to speak, he knew that once he spoke, he would be killed. Not speaking gave him a chance of survival instead.

Pew!

At this moment, with a light sound, Yun Luo Tian's corpse was transported over.

Fang Yuan kicked Wang Xiao aside, walking over to the corpse and used the beast strength placenta Gu to devour the aperture.

"It's him? That Yun clan young leader!" Wang Xiao recognised Yun Luo Tian, and also witnessed Fang Yuan using beast strength placenta Gu, his heart chilled.

Fang Yuan was obviously killing people to refine Gu!

"This Gu can devour apertures, not good, my aperture is way more valuable than Yun Luo Tian's." This beast strength placenta Gu had already become smooth and clear, like a beautiful porcelain. But in Wang Xiao's eyes, it was extremely dangerous and mysterious, giving off a demonic feeling.

Seeing Fang Yuan walk over, Wang Xiao shouted: "Wait, wait. We can negotiate, I can promise you to give you the actual path into the mountain, but you must ensure my safety, I have one poison vow Gu on me..."

Fang Yuan's killing intent surged, although he had the eating one's words Gu and can break the vow, he had little time now, how could he waste time to create the eating one's words Gu?

As he killed these Gu Masters, his immortal essence was depleting, and the blessed land was getting closer to destruction.

The longer they dragged, the weaker the land spirit, an the less immortal essence he had to refine the second aperture Gu.

At the same time, the blessed land's flow of time was three times the outside world. The Spring Autumn Cicada was posing a huge threat.

Fang Yuan killed so many people, he already used nearly two portions of the immortal essence, about half of his planned amount. The blessed land's destruction was accelerated, and some people should be able to feel it already.

Fang Yuan's greatest advantage was having the initiative. If he continued to drag this, it would get more disadvantageous for him.

Compared to the second aperture Gu, Wu mountain's benefits were huge but not irreplaceable.

"Speak, which is the path into Wu mountain?" Fang Yuan stepped, and broke Wang Xiao's right wrist, shouting sharply.

"Let me go and I'll tell you!" Wang Xiao screamed in pain.

"Hmph, stubborn!" Fang Yuan stepped again, the sound of bone breaking was heard as Wang Xiao's left kneecap was crushed to bits.

Wang Xiao shuddered under the pain, as sweat flowed down his back, but he gritted his teeth and stared deeply at Fang Yuan, refusing to speak.

Fang Yuan was silent, knowing that coercion would not work.

Wang Xiao was an expert of a generation!

He had a cruel and ruthless nature, never going easy on his enemies, but also strict on himself.

He designed an "ice water bed" for himself. Such a bed, as long as one sleeps for six hours, the entire bed would sink into the ice water below.

Wang Xiao slept on such a bed, only resting for six hours a day. He encouraged himself, and worked hard, giving it all his effort. Other than eating, cleaning, and resting, all his other time was spent on cultivation.

His aptitude was not extremely good, uncomparable with Tie Mu Bai and Bai Ning Bing. But because of his hard work, he climb up step by step, becoming famous in southern border, a great demonic expert that no one dared to look down on.

In Fang Yuan's memories, after Wang Xiao came to Yi Tian mountain, he killed many righteous experts, and his ruthlessness spread, one time, he even got close to vying for the position of the demonic head.

Fang Yuan felt pressure in his heart offending such a person.

Killing Wang Xiao was weakening the demonic faction in the Yi Tian mountain battle. But Wang Xiao could not be kept alive, he had to be killed.

"I have to refine Gu not long after, I do not want to be attacked by you." Fang Yuan sighed, striking the final move and killing Wang Xiao.

Later, he took the Gu and devoured the aperture, this process was extremely smooth.

After devouring Yun Luo Tian and Wang Xiao's aperture, the beast strength placenta Gu's aptitude had risen to eighty-three percent. As for the immortal essence expenditure, it had reach slightly more than two portions, he had reached a critical stage.

"Not good, the immortal essence expenditure is higher than my estimation. This blessed land is too old, originating from the antiquity era, it is a miracle that the blessed land is still standing today."

Fang Yuan's expression was solemn, the actual expenditure had slightly exceeded his initial estimations.

Chapter 383: Profound Concept of the Universe, Red Lotus Demon Venerable

"Young man, the primeval essence expenditure had deviated from the plans, you should stop now." The land spirit noticed this error, and suggested.

Fang Yuan's expression turned cold, retorting immediately: "That won't do, eighty-three percent is not part of my plans, my plan is to reach ninety percent!"

"Most things in life do not happen according to one's wishes. How can we get everything we want? Young man, you have been blinded by greed, you are starting to lose your rationality." The land spirit spoke calmly.

Fang Yuan cursed in his heart, without the land spirit's help, he could not use the immortal essence. Land spirit was already thinking of stopping, Fang Yuan had to convince it.

"Ba Gui." Fang Yuan breathed out some turbid air, relaxing his tone: "The primeval essence expenditure exceeding by a bit is no big deal. In my plan, we had some spare essence."

Fang Yuan planned the immortal essence into sixteen portions.

Among that, eight was for Gu refinement, four was to sustain the three kings inheritance and three portions and a bit more for killing Gu Masters. The final bit would be kept as spare in case anything happened.

Fang Yuan had a meticulous nature, he had planned this for so long, how could he not have a back up plan?

But the land spirit was not convinced, although it was created from lingering thoughts, it had intelligence and could think.

"Young man, your calculation is incorrect. Have you ever considered that the Gu refinement process might fail? There is no way you won't have issues, once you fail you will waste immortal essence. Eight portions to refine Gu, that was the minimum requirement, that last bit of immortal essence is to allow you to waste when you make multiple attempts. Now that you want to use up this bit, if you fail the refinement even a little bit more, the second aperture Gu's refinement will not succeed." Land spirit retorted.

Fang Yuan was anxious secretly, he had not passed the test and was not the blessed land's owner, he could not directly command the land spirit.

If land spirit refused to cooperate, there was nothing he could do.

There was still a rank five Gu Master and many rank four experts left in the blessed land now, these will all be obstacles for him when he refines the Immortal Gu later.

Fang Yuan killing these people now was to eliminate his future enemies, to protect himself.

But the immortal essence left in the blessed land was simply too little, Fang Yuan had to carefully think and plan his usage properly. At the same time, he had to face the blessed land's inspections.

"Young man, stop taking risks. If you continue being adamant, I will not cooperate with you, I will even take away your examination chance, and leave the opportunity for others." Land spirit was firm in its tone.

Fang Yuan sighed deeply hearing this.

Land spirits were very rigid, in this situation, it was nearly impossible to convince the land spirit.

"We can keep the others, but that rank five Gu Master has to die. He is one of the four great doctors of southern border, he has a great network and relationship, we have to eliminate him to be safe." Fang Yuan urged.

"For your safety during refinement, you have already planned to use that young girl, together with the beast groups, she can block them for a while. At the same time, I will risk my life to protect you. The most important thing is the success or failure of your Gu refinement." Land spirit denied Fang Yuan's suggestion.

Fang Yuan's expression sank.

The final rank five Gu Master Chou Jiu, known as 'killer ghost doctor', although his battle strength was not outstanding, he had great influence.

In his previous life's memories, he went to Yi Tian mountain and joined the demonic faction. Next, he obtained the third-in-control position. With a wave of his hand, countless Gu Masters gathered.

With his healing, the demonic faction faced less deaths and injuries, their morale surged and that caused great problems for the righteous path.

Only until Shang Yan Fei invited Doctor Su Shou, together with Divine Doctor Sheng Shou, did they manage to suppress Chou Jiu's glamor.

The battle of Yi Tian mountain made everyone see the ability of Chou Jiu. The 'killer ghost doctor' also became publicly recognised as the head of the four great doctors.

After Yi Tian mountain was subdued by the righteous path, Chou Jiu was captured, and Wu clan leader valued his talent and wanted to recruit him. But Chou Jiu refused to submit, scolding Shang Yan Fei and Doctor Su Shou, exposing some of their ancient history, causing the furious and ashamed Shang Yan Fei to kill him on the spot.

Any rank five Gu Master was a genius, they cannot be underestimated.

These Gu Masters could emerge from the commoners, and ascend to the peak of the mortal realm in such a cruel environment, surviving many rounds of elimination, they were all heroes or champions.

Once he thought about how a person like Chou Jiu might attack during the final step of the Gu refinement, Fang Yuan could not rest easy.

"Although my cultivation is rank four upper stage, and my cultivation speed is stunning, on this huge stage, I am still too weak, I cannot contend with these rank five Gu Masters. If I had my rank six cultivation back in my previous life, no matter how many rank fives come, I can kill them all like livestock!" Fang Yuan sighed internally.

"You still want to kill someone? Impossible, I will not allow it! Immortal essence cannot be wasted like this, we have to preserve most of it for the Gu refinement." Land spirit heard Fang Yuan's request and immediately rejected him: "Demonic Gu Masters are all like this, they like to take risks. Sigh, young man, do not be so extreme. In this world, why do you think the righteous path is blooming and suppressing the demonic path? It is because demonic path is too extreme, too greedy, and likes to place themselves in danger. The righteous path pursues stability, slow and steady, unmovable like the mountain."

"Ba Gui, you are wrong. Demonic path members have a tough life, they are forced to take extreme means, if they did not fight for the greatest benefits at every given opportunity, and did not take risks, how could they cultivate, how could they compete with the righteous path? Greed, selfishness, extremity, and risk-taking; these are all laws of survival of the demonic path. As long as the benefits are enough, so what if we have to walk on a tightrope? One wrong step leads to game over, making the impossible possible, that is the excitement of the demonic path! The life of a demonic path member is like wine, intense and alluring." Fang Yuan rebuked loudly.

Land spirit heard such words and sighed endlessly: "Young man, the demonic nature is too entrenched in you, you can't turn back anymore, in the future it will lead you to destruction. If heaven commits a sin, it can be forgiven, but if one commits a sin himself, he deserves to die."

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "Hahahaha, Ba Gui, you are too naive. What is a sin? Commiting a sin means one deserves death, that is only the weaklings' naive and helpless expectation, they spread such ideology, hoping people would abide by it so as to protect these weaklings. As for me, I want to be a person who commits a sin, yet is able to roam freely and travel the world, a demonic head who slaughters living beings and enjoys all that I can get. I not only want to slaughter Gu Masters, I also want to succeed in refining the second aperture Gu and become the greatest winner! Ba Gui, feel this, what do you think this is?"

Saying so, Fang Yuan activated the Spring Autumn Cicada, and for the first time, leaked its aura out into the world.

The land spirit was flabbergasted!

"This, this is the aura of a rank six Immortal Gu! It seems... it seems to be the Spring Autumn Cicada... Spring Autumn Cicada is the seventh mysterious Gu in this world! You are a mere mortal, how can you possess such an Immortal Gu?"

To convince the land spirit, Fang Yuan took a gamble and exposed the existence of the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was a rank six Gu, and the second aperture Gu was also an Immortal Gu, such benefits were enough for Fang Yuan to take this risk.

"Why can't a mortal own an Immortal Gu? I'll tell you the truth, the Spring Autumn Cicada was refined by me." Fang Yuan said.

"I understand, I get it. You were a Gu Immortal, but you used the Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth and came back to the past to change history!" Land spirit gasped and sighed.

"Oh? Ba Gui, you seem to know some information regarding the Spring Autumn Cicada, please enlighten me." Fang Yuan quickly inquired.

"Since the immemorial era, there were two types of Gu Masters, space path and time path, forming the basis of heaven and earth. Space path represented up, down, left, and right, while time path represented past, present, and future. Take my blessed land for example, at its peak, there was 6000 km² of land, and the flow of time was six times the normal speed." Land spirit said.

How much was 6000 km² ? On Earth, that is about the size of Brunei.

As for six times the normal speed of time, it was measured according to the river of time.

At its peak, the blessed land's time was six times of the outside world. Six days inside the blessed land was one day outside.

Of course, by now, the blessed land had severely weakened, not only were the territories mostly eroded, the flow of time was only three times as fast.

In this world, there were many different blessed lands, and the size and flow of time were all different.

Land spirit continued: "Spring Autumn Cicada is one of the Gu worms of the time path. Back then, it had a master who left his name in history, that is Red Lotus Demon Venerable! He resisted the Immortal Court, and broke the chains that bound fate, giving the people of the future hope, and allowed them to grasp their own fate in their hands."

"Red Lotus Demon Venerable?! The most mysterious Demon Venerable in history?" Fang Yuan gasped.

In the Gu world, rank nine was Venerable.

Demon Venerable meant a rank nine demonic path Gu Master. Immortal Venerable is a rank nine righteous Gu Master.

In the eons of history, Demon Venerable and Immortal Venerable were merely a handful of people, they represented a supreme legend. There was only one Venerable in each era, never did two appear at the same time. Thus, Venerables represented true invincibility!

And among these rank nine Venerables, Red Lotus Demon Venerable was the most mysterious, and had the least records in history. Even Fang Yuan merely knew about his existence.

Now, this was the first time he was hearing about Red Lotus Demon Venerable's details.

Land spirit continued: "This world, wide as one can imagine, is split into five regions, north, south, east, west, and central. They are close together, yet completely independent regions. With one river of time, flowing from the past, through the present, towards the future. That is the time and space of this main world."

"If one says that history is a series of still images, then the river of time is a thin thread that connects these numerous images into a line, You used the Spring Autumn Cicada, forcing your way out of the images, and travelled along the line, moving in the reverse direction as you inject your will and memories into one of the images. That would cause this image's events to change, and consequently affect the future images as well.

"So that's it." Fang Yuan benefited greatly from land spirit's words.

He had used the Spring Autumn Cicada twice, and each was a unique experience, causing Fang Yuan's understanding of the Spring Autumn Cicada and the river of time to become clearer.

Land spirit's words gave Fang Yuan the inspiration for a new and unique understanding.

"To think that you are a future Gu Immortal, and even refined the Spring Autumn Cicada. In this blessed land, you are truly the most appropriate candidate to refine this Gu. Nevermind, since you are so confident, I shall trust you once, who do you want to kill?" Land spirit gave in.

Originally, it thought Fang Yuan was only a mortal, he would definitely waste a lot of immortal essence when refining Gu.

But right now, it recognised Fang Yuan's Gu Immortal identity, and reduced the estimated immortal essence that he would potentially waste, thus accepting Fang Yuan's request.

Fang Yuan smiled and promised: "Land spirit, it is right to trust me. I will not disappoint you, the Gu refinement will succeed. In the future, I have to rely on this second aperture Gu to ascend to Gu Immortal realm once again."

Land spirit laughed too, having a sense of acknowledgement towards Fang Yuan: "That's right, you are a Gu Immortal, you know the value of the second aperture Gu much more than mortals. When you become a Gu Immortal, the second aperture will give you unparalleled benefits!"

Chapter 384: Scheming Ghost Doctor, Secret Door of Life and Death

"To think that this three kings inheritance is a trap, the true winner is you, little beast king!" Killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu laid on the ground, staring deeply and closely at Fang Yuan as he exclaimed.

After Fang Yuan convinced the land spirit, he rushed to Chou Jiu and beat him up.

Chou Jiu had an ugly appearance, his hair was like dry yellow grass, his brain was protruding and his eyes were of different sizes. His cheekbone was very high, his nose was flat, there was a large clump of hair growing out of his nostrils, and his yellow teeth were projecting outwards.

But his gaze was very complicated, he had a plotting ability that ordinary people could not possess.

"Little beast king, I know about you, you have great talent, from a vagabond, you grew to this extent, I admire you greatly. Compared to you, I am merely several years older. When I was young, I did not have such accomplishments. You are a dragon among men, you will eventually soar to the heavens, and roam the world freely. I have no intentions to be enemies with you, if possible, I would like to use the information regarding the door of life and death to preserve my life."

Fang Yuan had killed four rank five Gu masters earlier, some of them were shocked, some furious, some fearful, but this Chou Jiu was extremely calm.

After understanding his situation, he placed his ego down and praised Fang Yuan.

He laid on the ground, not moving, as if he gave up on resisting.

But at this moment, the land spirit suddenly transmitted: "Quickly kill him, he is activating his token and Gu worms furiously, I am trying to suppress them but this is causing great immortal essence expenditure."

But Fang Yuan was slightly stunned, almost thinking he had hallucinated: "Door of life and death?"

This door of life and death was a big deal, it was recorded in \<\<Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, a secret forbidden land in ancient times. It was similar to the river of time and ordinary abyss.

After Verdant Great Sun died, Ren Zu went to the door of life and death to attempt to revive him.

Legend says that behind the door of life and death holds the secrets of life and death, if a person can comprehend it completely, they would be able to control life and death itself.

"Chou Jiu knows the location of the door of life and death?!" Fang Yuan's heart was palpitating, as his expression turned cold, warning severely: "Chou Jiu, activate your Gu worms one more time and I will kill you immediately."

Chou Jiu's expression changed, his pupils shrinking as he slowly sat up, looking at Fang Yuan: "You can sense me using Gu worms!"

A thought flashed across his eyes: "You can use Gu worms, while I can't use mine at all. Sigh, it seems there is only one possibility — the land spirit is still alive and you subdued it. So this blessed land has such a secret. What a pity, back when the three kings obtained this place, they did not truly control the blessed land, thus you have obtained it now. But this blessed land is on the brink of destruction, there is no way to save it. The land spirit must be extremely old and weak too right, otherwise the Gu Masters would've been chased out already. Why would you need to eliminate us personally?"

Although Fang Yuan did not control this blessed land, after expressing his identity, the land spirit would listen to some of his instructions in order to assist him with the Gu refinement.

Chou Jiu was over a century old, he was old and scheming, easily guessing the scenario.

"Since you control the blessed land, then I won't bother with this pointless act. As long as you preserve my life, what you will obtain will be out of your imagination." Chou Jiu said, stopping his secret actions.

Fang Yuan laughed without denying: "Talk about the door of life and death. You know the location? The door of life and death is a forbidden ground not inferior to the river of time, there is an extremely wide area inside, reflecting the five regions of the main world. Legend says that there are many unique and natural Gu worms inside, like life Gu, and death Gu."

Chou Jiu nodded: "I know the door's location, not only that, I have even explored it multiple times and captured some of the life Gu and death Gu inside, eventually refining one life one death Gu. I placed this Gu inside the door of life and death, every time a person dies because of me, it will absorb this death energy and convert it into lifeforce. Because of this lifeforce, my healing methods are extremely profound. This is the reason why I became one of the four great doctors of southern border."

Killer ghost doctor revealed his own secret, to increase his trustworthiness.

"Oh? So that's it." This was the first time Fang Yuan heard such a thing, although he had his previous life's memories, he was not all-knowing.

"Then in that case, tell me, and I may spare you a life." Fang Yuan promised.

But Chou Jiu shook his head: "The secret regarding the door of life and death is way too important. I have once vowed before the sea oath Gu, to not reveal the details to outsiders. Once I say it, I will turn into dust, wiped off from this world. But if you join the shadow sect, you will be one of us, and I will be able to tell you."

"Sea oath Gu? Shadow Sect?" Fang Yuan frowned.

Sea oath Gu is a rank six Immortal Gu, it was very famous during ancient times, together with mountain pledge Gu. Mountain pledge and sea oath, they worked like the poison vow Gu, but poison vow Gu was an expenditure Gu while these two Immortal Gu could be repeatedly used.

Fang Yuan had heard of the sea oath Gu and had an understanding of it. But he was unfamiliar with 'Shadow Sect'.

Hearing this name, it sounds like a sect for Gu cultivators. That means, the loner Chou Jiu, had a secret organisation behind him?

Fang Yuan felt a little threatened, the situation was slightly out of his expectations.

It was not hard to kill Chou Jiu now, but Fang Yuan knew nothing about Shadow Sect, this gave him a sense of insecurity.

"That's right, my sect is the Shadow Sect. The great ancestor who created Shadow Sect, was a rank eight Gu Immortal of the Immemorial Era. He was the one who found the door of life and death, and placed it into his blessed land. Later, many Gu Immortals were nurtured in Shadow Sect, the benefits are endless for you if you join Shadow Sect."

Saying so, Chou Jiu said a bunch of benefits, truly expending his verbal talent, spouting an exaggerated tale.

Fang Yuan struggled a little, before calming down: "Hehehe, Chou Jiu, that's a nice plan there. If I join Shadow Sect, you not only will be free from danger, I will even have to call you senior brother. In such a traditional sect, respecting seniority is the most important thing. If I join it, I will definitely have to make an oath and be restricted with all sorts of methods. At the end, I even have to contribute my gains on San Cha mountain, and do missions for the clan in the name of loyalty, am I right?"

"Shadow Sect?" Fang Yuan sneered, shaking his head: "Let's not talk about the possibility of you lying, even if it is real, so what? A sect that was created in the Immemorial Era, it is a miracle that it is still around now. You mentioned there were many Gu Immortals in history, but they are mostly dead already right. Otherwise, Shadow Sect would be a great force in the southern border, why would you have to fight alone, and slog it out single-handedly?"

Chou Jiu's expression turned white, he had to reassess Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was so young, but he was so calculating and scheming. Facing potential benefits, he could remain so calm and analytic, what sort of young man is this? He is definitely a hundred year old monster!

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, continuing: "I am the type of person who likes to take all the benefits for himself, don't tell me about win-win situations. Even if you made the sea oath, it is not unbreakable. Sea oath Gu and mountain pledge Gu have an obvious weakness. When you made the oath, you had to face the sea or a large mountain. As long as the piece of ocean or the mountain is destroyed, the oath will lose its effect."

Chou Jiu's heart froze.

Fang Yuan was knowledgeable and knew many things, he was not like a newbie at all.

These kind of people were the hardest to fool.

Chou Jiu calmed his spirits: "It is useless. The sea that I made the oath to is inside the Shadow Sect blessed land, if you want to destroy that sea, you will need to know the location of the blessed land. But for me to say that location, you have to destroy the sea first. It is a dead loop."

Fang Yuan sneered, killing intent surging: "Since there is nothing that can be done, forget it. You can die now."

Chou Jiu sighed greatly: "If you want to kill me, go ahead."

He did not move, but in his heart, he felt certain.

The door of life and death was a legendary location, who did not care about their life and death? Little beast king definitely cannot endure such a temptation, his actions now were only to scare him.

But Fang Yuan shot out the bone spike resolutely.

This bone spike flew towards Chou Jiu's heart.

At once, an intense sense of danger assaulted Chou Jiu.

"What! He actually wants to kill me?!" Chou Jiu was shocked, quickly evading.

Pew!

A crisp sound and the bone spike pierced his shoulder, inches away from his heart, only after it stabbed through his back did it stop.

"You, you!" Chou JIu pointed at Fang Yuan, his trembling voice contained fear, shock, and confusion: "Little beast king, you madman! You really wanted to kill me, if I did not dodge, I would've died! That is the door of life and death, the door of life and death! Back then, even Ren Zu had to spend all his effort to find it. This is an unparalleled holy land, the controller of life and death, as long as you can obtain it and comprehend it, you will attain immortality!"

Fang Yuan looked at him coldly, speaking plainly: "Didn't you say you can't tell me the secret? Then what use do I have of you?"

"You can join the Shadow Sect!" Chou Jiu's body was sweating, either out of pain or fear.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, raising his hand and aiming again.

Chou Jiu quickly waved his hand, shouting: "Wait, wait, don't be rash. There are other methods than this, we can use the poison vow Gu, if we make a poison vow, we can trust each other."

"I do not need your trust." Fang Yuan replied coldly.

"Then use the slavery Gu, I will acknowledge you as my master, don't kill me."

"You are a rank five Gu Master, we need to use the rank five slavery Gu. This Gu is extremely rare, way more expensive than its other rank five counterparts, where do you want me to find it? Moreover, even if we use these Gu, can you tell me the location of Shadow Sect's blessed land?" Fang Yuan retorted.

Chou Jiu's expression froze.

Fang Yuan observed his expression, and his heart moved, knowing that the words were true.

Fang Yuan's killing intent was not real, he was merely trying to test Chou Jiu.

Chou Jiu suggested the poison vow Gu, slavery Gu, he was already frantic, but still did not dare to mention the location of the blessed land. It seems he really did make the sea oath.

Chou Jiu wanted to lie and make up a random location.

But as long as he did not die from the oath, it means he lied. If he said the real location, the oath would take his life as well.

Or rather, even if he managed to say it, he would lose all his value and Fang Yuan would not let him off.

In this situation, Chou Jiu was at his wits' end.

Recognising this, he laughed bitterly: "To think that I Chou Jiu would die here today."

"Being able to die in my hands is your honor." Fang Yuan replied plainly.

Chou Jiu looked at Fang Yuan seriously, nodding in agreement: "That's true, with your talent and mentality, as long as your luck is not too bad, you will definitely be a walking disaster of the demonic path. You want to kill me, there is no point in begging anymore. It is fine if I die in your hands, at least better than getting killed by those scumbags outside. Actually, I have a plan to allow you to learn about the door of life and death."

Saying so, a cunning light flashed across Chou Jiu's eyes.

Chapter 385: Kindness, Grudge, Affection, Hatred

"Oh? What method?" Fang Yuan's eyebrows raised.

"Regarding this matter, I have to start from a long time ago..." Chou Jiu heaved a deep sigh as he recalled; hatred, grief, deep love and other complicated expressions appeared on his face.

"I have no time to listen to your story." Fang Yuan ruthlessly interrupted.

Chou Jiu choked: "Then I will make it short."

"My original name was Zeng Ah Niu. I was a farmer who made a living by collecting herbs, one time I unluckily fell from a cliff but I profited from it and entered Shadow Sect's blessed land. By passing the land spirit's test, I was able to become a disciple of Shadow Sect. The sect only had two disciples, me and a senior sister."

"Senior sister's surname is Chen and her first name is Jiu, she was as beautiful as an immortal fairy. She was raised by the land spirit since young and had never left the blessed land, thus her nature was truly innocent. Since birth, I was extremely ugly and had always suffered bullying and ridicule. But senior sister was always amiable and warm to me. I slowly started having feelings for her after being in contact with her all the time. We took an oath in front of the blessed land's sea, to protect and stand by each other. We cultivated together and entered deep into the door of life and death, capturing life Gu and death Gu...."

"That was the happiest time of my life and I had thought it could continue forever. After an earth calamity, the land spirit suffered injuries and went into hibernation; a hole appeared in the blessed land and connected it to the outside world, allowing a scoundrel to sneak in."

"This scoundrel was heavily injured at that time, and if I had known what would happen later because of him, I would have definitely killed him on the spot! But I didn't do that and instead saved him. He claimed his surname was Shang, and had blood red hair. He had exceptional eloquence, and using his flowery words, he slowly deceived senior sister during his recuperation. His appearance was indeed slightly better than mine and used his pretty boy face to win senior sister's favor. Senior sister was innocent and ignorant, the more she talked with him, the happier she became; in the end, she took the initiative to take care of him in every possible way."

"We argued many times about this, falling out with each other a lot. After that thief recovered, I wanted to expel him and continue living a fairytale life with senior sister. But who could have thought her heart had already changed and actually broke the oath we took at that time, injuring me and defecting with that scoundrel!"

"I was really regretful! I regretted my compassion which led to a disaster, and I hated senior sister Chen Jiu for falling in love with somebody else, and even more hatred towards that despicable scoundrel for robbing what I cherished. After I recovered from my injuries, I left the blessed land and roamed around Southern Border, searching for this adulterous couple. But what I didn't know was, this scoundrel had really high status and was the leader of Shang clan!"

Chou Jiu paused and looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was expressionless, he knew many behind-the-scene details due to his previous life memories and already knew who Chou Jiu was talking about in the middle of his conversation.

Chou Jiu could only give a forced smile at Fang Yuan's indifference: "It seems you have already guessed their identities. That's right, that thief is the current Shang clan leader Shang Yan Fei and my senior sister Chen Jiu is Doctor Su Shou. Shang clan is a super clan while I am a lone force, I roamed around Southern Border all these years and put in a lot of effort to deal with this adulterous couple! Unfortunately... unfortunately I am going to die here today and have no way of achieving my wish."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan silently listened to end and suddenly laughed.

He looked at Chou Jiu who was sitting on the ground, his eyes shining brightly: "Killer ghost doctor, you made quite a good plan. According to your words, Shadow Sect has only you and Chen Jiu, if you die, I will have to obtain the information about life and death door from Shang Yan Fei and Doctor Su Shou. But why would they tell me about the matters regarding the blessed land of Shadow Sect so easily? At that time, we will have to fight, and no matter who wins, both will be favorable to you."

"Hahaha... little beast king, you are very blunt and straightforward. People who only plot and scheme will always act under the radar, but your thinking is meticulous and your way of doing things is domineering, you are truly a formidable person who has yet to shake the world. You are right, that is my plan. It is an open scheme and you have already seen through it, so are you still going to make inquiries about the Shadow Sect's blessed land from them?" Killer ghost doctor laughed heartily.

Fang Yuan looked at this rank five Gu Master for a while before sighing: "Of course."

Life and death door was an immemorial forbidden ground like the river of time.

There were many unique Gu inhabiting in that place.

Spring Autumn Cicada existed in the river of time; life and death door naturally also had similar Immortal Gu.

It was impossible for Fang Yuan to not be moved by such an enormous benefits. Thus, he clearly knew Chou Jiu's scheme, but was still going to go head-first into it.

Qiu laughed loudly with tears appearing in his eyes: "Little beast king, although you are a talent of the younger generation, I really admire you. I really look forward to the future where you collide with that adulterous couple. It is a pity I won't be able to see it."

"Our Shadow Sect has different views on life and death. We encountered each other among the countless sea of people because of life and yet my death will be because of you, this is a truly extraordinary fate. Maybe, you really are fated to find Shadow Sect's blessed land and the door of life and death. I might as well give this mysterious fate to you and hope you can grasp it."

Chou Jiu became tranquil and his gaze were deep as if he had seen through life and death: "It is no matter if I die now, after all in this world, who can live forever? One can gain a long life but immortality is a hopeless prospect. Even those Immortal Venerable and Demon Venerable will only turn into ashes in the end. Little beast king, I will end my own life, you don't need to do it."

Saying so, he committed suicide by biting off his tongue!

Blood sprayed out as his life went away, the ghost doctor, the head of the four great doctors in the future died like this.

"I did not expect to gain such important information by killing this ghost doctor. Shadow Sect's blessed land, life and death door... If I am able to rule them, they will definitely be a foundation to my hegemony. It seems I will have to change my plan again."

Every single Gu Master who cultivated to rank five needed to go through the survival of the fittest and many competitions before they were able to distinguish themselves; none of them were a simple character.

They all possessed their own individual opportunities, advantages, trump cards and secrets.

Right now, all the rank five Gu Masters in the blessed land were annihilated by Fang Yuan.

Tie Mu Bai, Wu Gui, Ku Mo, Wu Lan Shan and Chou Jiu had their own distinct individuality, deep foundation and powerful strength. If the current Fang Yuan was to fight them alone, any one of them could easily suppress him; he was absolutely not their match.

"So Doctor Su Shou's real name is Chen Jiu while the killer ghost doctor named himself Chou Jiu, it seems the hatred was born from love. No wonder in my previous life, during the battle of Yi Tian mountain, he took the initiative to go there and threw himself into that whirlpool, challenging Shang Yan Fei and confronting Doctor Su Shou. And after he was taken as a prisoner, he exposed the matter back then and was killed by Shang Yan Fei."

As for the kindness, grudge, affection and hatred entangling these three, Fang Yuan did not want to judge.

Sympathize with Chou Jiu? But Doctor Su Shou's choice was also completely understandable. Favor the rich and disdain the poor, detest ugliness and love beauty, these were common in the world.

Shang Yan Fei was a famous handsome man in Southern Border; comparing him to Chou Jiu, one was day and another was night.

The main reason Doctor Su Shou felt deeply attached to Chou Jiu was because she was pure and Chou Jiu was the first male she saw. And later when she met Shang Yan Fei, her eyes were opened and had a comparison.

Moreover, Chen Jiu was someone who innately pursued beauty.

When a patient came to visit her, she would first look at their appearance. If they were ugly, she would not treat them. If they were average, it would depend on her mood at that time and the patient's examination fees. If they were handsome and beautiful, she would treat them on the spot and not even charge fees.

Someone reproached her for this and she argued righteously: "You ugly beings, the fact that you are alive is simply staining the beauty of life, you should all just die and that will solve all troubles. As for beautiful things, of course we need to cherish and protect them by all means."

These words had caused an uproar in Shang clan city at that time. In the end, Shang Yan Fei personally appeared and suppressed this event.

Doctor Su Shou's position in Shang clan city was unique.

Back when Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing saw Doctor Su Shou together at Shang clan city, the difference in her attitude was very clear. She was indifferent to Fang Yuan whereas she was very gentle and amiable to Bai Ning Bing.

"But speaking of it, the four great doctors all have their own peculiarity. Leaving aside killer ghost doctor and Doctor Su Shou, Travelling Doctor Jiu Zhi likes to disguise himself as an old beggar and wander around aimlessly. Divine Doctor Sheng Shou is a male who likes other males."

Fang Yuan thought casually while taking out all the Gu of killer ghost doctor.

Chou Jiu had many Gu worms.

Most of them were healing Gu and besides that were movement Gu.

He did not have rank five healing Gu, but instead had a rank five movement Gu called warp Gu.

Warp Gu's shape was abstract and looked like a fried twisted dough. Its dark golden body was twisted around seven to eight times, its head was twisted around its body, its eyes and wings were misaligned; as if its creator had created it at a whim.

However, this appearance instead matched with its original owner's appearance.

Fang Yuan slightly sized it up before storing it. Then he used beast strength placenta Gu to swallow Chou Jiu's aperture.

Looking at Chou Jiu's corpse, he chuckled: "Chou Jiu... Chou Jiu, you are really cunning. If I did not have my previous life's memories, I would have truly been deceived by you."

Although Chou Jiu was dead, he was hiding a chance of resurrection.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Chou Jiu's throat had been cut and assassinated during the middle stage of the battle in Yi Tian mountain. But not long later, he came back to life, causing both righteous and demonic path to be extremely startled.

It turns out, he had used remnant life Gu.

Remnant life Gu was a rank five expendable Gu, and as long as a Gu Master's body is intact after death, they can slowly recover after some time and resurrect.

However, since Chou Jiu was at the blessed land, the remnant life Gu's law fragment in his body was suppressed by the heavenly power and could not activate for the time being. But as long as the blessed land slowly crumbles, its suppression power would weaken and the remnant life Gu's power could activate again and resurrect him.

Chou Jiu had repeatedly praised and flattered Fang Yuan and put on a show that he was carefreely facing death; it was all to give a good impression to Fang Yuan so that after his death, his corpse would not be ripped apart by Fang Yuan.

In truth, Fang Yuan also did not have a habit of mutilating corpses.

"But today, I will make an exception for you." Fang Yuan ruthlessly attacked and soon turned Chou Jiu's corpse into minced meat.

He hesitated for a while and was still not satisfied, so he burnt the pool of blood and flesh into ashes.

With a wave of his palm, the ashes fluttered and drifted everywhere.

"Chou Jiu, if you can still resurrect from this, I will admit you have skills! Hahahaha..."

Chapter 386: He also died

"This is the forty-eighth round." Wu Shen Tong counted in his heart.

He came from Wu clan, the number one super clan in southern border, they had deep foundations, and were the supreme overlord of the righteous path. And he was the heavily nurtured enslavement path Gu Master in Wu clan, his attainments in enslavement was nothing to be scoffed at.

Wu Shen Tong's name might sound domineering, but in truth, he was thin as a stick, his skin was pale-yellow, and he looked like a sickly scholar.

In truth, he once had a broad shoulder and thin waist, and had a perfect body. But in one battle, he was afflicted with Long Qing Tian's jade sky Gu poison.

He went to Divine Doctor Sheng Shou for treatment.

Divine Doctor Sheng Shou touched his chest, his eyes shining as he sighed: "You came too late. The Gu poison has seeped into your bone marrow. I can preserve your life and cultivation, but because this poison is deeply rooted, it cannot be removed. From now you, you have to come here once in a while for treatment, I will help you detox at regular intervals."

Precisely because of jade sky Gu's poison, Wu Shen Tong became thinner and thinner each day, eventually ending up like this.

"I wonder which Gu Master is my next opponent?" Wu Shen Tong walked in the fog, his gaze solemn.

Just earlier, in the three options, he chose the front path.

In King Quan inheritance, towards the later stages, more options appeared. Most Gu Masters would choose to fight dog groups for safety, and in truth, they only chose other Gu Masters out of desperation.

No matter how big the dog group is, they were still beasts. With a Gu Master's guidance, even if the dog group is weak, they possessed great threat.

Wu Shen Tong however, took the opposite route, whenever he was given a chance to battle another Gu Master, he would not choose any other path.

"In terms of enslavement path mastery, I am top-tier in southern border. In this San Cha mountain, I am almost the best. Only two people can threaten me, one is Wu Gui because he is a rank five Gu Master that had once walked the enslavement path. But sadly, enslavement path used too much resources and he had to change paths midway. The other is Zhang San San, he is a true enslavement Gu Master, but his cultivation is inferior to me."

In the enslavement path, Wu Shen Tong had great advantage. In terms of seniority, Zhang San San was his junior. In this King Quan Inheritance, even if he had to fight Wu Gui head on, he had no fear.

With such great strength, he obviously had to target his enemies and eliminate as many competitors as possible.

Eventually, he will be left alone to devour this King Quan Inheritance.

This was Wu Shen Tong's brilliance.

"If I had to count, my next opponent should be the twenty-third. Hehe, it is your bad luck to have encouraged me."

Wu Shen Tong snorted internally as he stopped his steps.

Beside him, his group dog guarded him closely.

He looked at the other end of the fog, from the fog, a group of green-purple dogs with rotting skin appeared.

"Oh, corpse dogs." Wu Shen Tong laughed lightly.

He knew that these dogs were extremely useful early on in the inheritance. That is because these dogs can consume corpses to recover their injuries.

But towards the later parts, these corpse dogs would get weaker and weaker. That is because, these dogs were not as fast as the lightning symbol dogs, had lower defense than the steel armor dogs, and were not as united as the chrysanthemum akita dogs.

"Only those half-assed enslavement path Gu Masters would love these useless corpse dogs. Different paths are worlds' apart, how would those who aren't enslavement path Gu Masters know the true meaning of enslavement path without decades of experience?"

Wu Shen Tong thought about those Gu Masters and laughed in disdain.

But the next moment,he frowned lightly.

From the fog before him, corpse dogs continued to appear.

"This number is slightly huge, it seems that to win, I will have to pay a small price." Wu Shen Tong thought.

But soon, at the same time as the corpse dogs, different kinds of dogs started appearing in his vision.

"Chrysanthemum akita dogs! The number is slightly big, hmm... it seems this person has some attainments in the enslavement path." Wu Shen Tong nodded lightly.

"A combination of chrysanthemum akita dogs and corpse dogs, although the number is slightly big, their formation is extremely brittle. I just have to use a few dog kings to charge forward later, and they would disperse easily, as long as I act forcefully, I would be able to defeat them and attain victory."

"Eh, the other party actually has hedgedogs?"

From the fog, Wu Shen Tong saw hedgedogs appearing.

These dogs, their entire bodies were filled with spikes, attacking them would injure oneself.

If the steel armor dogs with huge defense were called tough, then these hedgedogs were tough with spikes. To eliminate them, one has to be prepared to get their throats punctured.

"So many hedgedogs! It seems this person is lucky, being able to gather such a huge group. Why didn't I have such luck?"

Wu Shen Tong sighed, immediately changing his battle strategy.

"The opponent had hedgedogs, I will use the steel armor dogs as the vanguard, and flank with the lightning symbol dogs. Once they engage in battle, the steel armor dogs will charge in and encircle with the lightning symbol dogs, attaining victory easily!"

But after the hedgedogs appeared, large numbers of lightning symbol dogs appeared from the fog.

Wu Shen Tong's expression turned grim.

The appearance of the dog group meant his earlier strategy no longer worked. That is because the opponent possessed a dog with high speed like lightning symbol dog, they could reverse flank him.

"To think they also have the lightning symbol dogs, and so many!" More and more lightning symbol dogs appeared in his vision, as Wu Shen Tong's expression turned ugly.

He thought: The other party has so many dogs, this cannot be explained with luck. Evidently, the other part is also an experienced enslavement path Gu Master, already able to threaten him.

"Who is it? Is it Wu Gui or Zhang San San? Regardless, this will be a tough fight. I can only improvise my battle tactic, and change accordingly, thankfully, I have a token!"

Thinking so, Wu Shen Tong's heart settled.

He took a look at his dog troop, there, a group of dogs laid on the ground, around a hundred and twenty.

The dogs were large in size, twice the size of ordinary dogs, they had sharp claws and their backs were wide and thick, while their nose and mouth resembled a lion's.

This was the heavy tai dog.

Heavy tai dog had defense equivalent to the steel armor dogs. In terms of unity, they matched the chrysanthemum akita dogs.

"In this King Quan Inheritance, out of the hundred types of dogs, only a few can be part of the main troop. Heavy tai dog is one of them. Lightning symbol dog, chrysanthemum akita dog, and steel armor dog, these dogs are too extreme, their weaknesses are too apparently, they cannot be relied on. Only a dog like heavy tai dog can be relied on. The larger the numbers, the stronger their battle strength.

Wu Shen Tong looked at his heavy tai dogs, feeling satisfied.

These were saved up by him after much difficulty. In usual battles, he did not use them, saving them until now.

"It seems this will be a hard battle, I have to use the heavy tai dogs. I believe that when I strike, the opponent should be very surprised. Hahaha..."

Thinking of this, Wu Shen Tong's lips curled into a smile.

But the next moment, his smile froze on his face.

From the other end of the fog, heavy tai dogs appeared too.

"The other party also have heavy tai dogs? Indeed, they are an expert in enslavement path, they naturally understand the excellence of the heavy tai dogs, thus they kept a few."

More and more heavy thai dogs appeared from the fog, as Wu Shen Tong started squinting, his brows frowning into a wrinkle.

"So many, why do they have so many heavy tai dogs?"

He had always regarded the heavy tai dogs as his trump card, seeing his opponent have them placed much mental pressure on Wu Shen Tong.

Suddenly, Wu Shen Tong's pupils shrunk as he stared at the fog.

He saw a domineering dog king.

"Heavy tai dog king! They actually have a heavy tai dog king!" Wu Shen Tong saw this and his heart sank.

With the dog king, the dog group's battle strength will surge several times. More importantly, Wu Shen Tong does not have a heavy tai dog king to fight back, his trump card would be suppressed by his opponent's dog king and have less fighting strength than normal.

In just a short moment, his trump card was no more.

"Tough battle, this will be an unprecedentedly tough battle! Who is it? Wu Gui or Zhang San San? It has to be one of them! High chance it is Wu Gui!"

Wu Shen Tong had lost his confidence towards this battle.

"The opponent's troops are larger than mine, I am likely to lose this. Even if I win this, it will be a tough victory and I would face great losses, unable to continue anymore."

Wu Shen Tong felt regret already.

But very quickly, he felt more than just simply regret.

His eye socket expanded more and more, as his mouth opened subconsciously.

His eyeballs were bulging out of his sockets, like his head was hit on the back. His expression turned from suspicious to shock, from shock to fear.

From the fog, not only did a large number of heavy tai dogs appear, even green hua dogs, smoke song dogs, light heng dogs and star heng dogs appeared!

Green hua dogs, a body covered in green scales, having an extraordinary disposition.

Smoke song dogs, oozing smoke from its nose and mouth, extremely rebellious.

Light heng dogs, a body of white fur, bright and gentle.

Star heng dogs, long and slim, stood out from the crowd.

How is this possible!" Wu Shen Tong screamed: "Green hua, smoke song, light heng and star heng all have differing specialties, they are on the same level, known as the five great mountain[1] dogs collectively, able to form a grand formation! How did they get so many dogs?"

What was hardest for Wu Shen Tong to believe was that the other party not only had large numbers of five great mountain dogs, they also had their respective dog kings!

"Who in the world is he? How can he have so many dog kings? Unbelievable! Is this an illusion?" In the fog, dogs were still coming out one after another, causing a great mental impact on Wu Shen Tong.

Compared to him, the other party was like a giant fighting a baby.

They could be compared at all!

Wu Shen Tong had no battle intent left. He had no way of winning this battle.

The other party just has to wave their hand and the dog groups would overwhelm him, regardless of his manipulation skills, there was no difference.

The different in military force could not be made up for with technical skills.

"Who is it? Did a rank five enslavement path Gu Master come to San Cha mountain? Impossible! Even if it is a rank five enslavement path Gu Master, how can they have such a large army? I have to see who the other party is!"

Wu Shen Tong grabbed his token as he stared at the fog.

From the fog, a persona appeared.

"Finally revealing your true identity?" Wu Shen Tong's sweat was dripping down his forehead as he gulped.

Swoosh!

At this moment, there was a light sound and Fang Yuan appeared behind him.

"Who?" Wu Shen Tong felt something and before he turned back.

Fang Yuan placed his palm on his head, squeezing.

Splat!

His head was popped like a balloon.

He was dead too.

From the fog, Bai Ning Bing walked out casually.

"How many rounds left?" She looked at Fang Yuan, yawning, like she had not gotten out of bed.

[1] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sacred_Mountains_of_China Back

Chapter 387: Rank Five Slavery Gu

Others had to rack their brains and make countless plans to advance through the rounds; people like Wu Shen Tong and Wu Gui also had to meticulously plan and choose their options. But with the help of the land spirit, Bai Ning Bing just had to move forward.

The pitiful Wu Shen Tong, a grand rank four peak stage Gu Master, could not even see Bai Ning Bing's appearance at the end.

As for Fang Yuan's appearance, Bai Ning Bing was not in the least bit surprised because the land spirit had reminded her.

In fact, this was the cooperation of the two.

Fang Yuan needed Wu Shen Tong's aperture while Bai Ning Bing needed Wu Shen Tong's enslavement path Gu worms and these dog groups he had accumulated.

With Wu Shen Tong's death, his large dog beasts group was naturally incorporated into Bai Ning Bing's troops, increasing her enormous dog army by ten percent.

Looking at the vast dog group, Fang Yuan joyfully nodded: "Your dog beasts army has already become an initial formation. In this King Quan Inheritance, with this group, you can already snowball to the final round without any problems. Remember, at the last few rounds, there are a large group of lion mastiffs. These lion mastiffs are all mutated beasts and have much more battle prowess than the five great mountain dogs. They were the trump cards of King Quan. Besides them, there are two dog emperors, ancient mutated beasts which are more powerful than common mutated beasts. Back in the day, they were the left and right arms of King Quan, each of them can match a rank five Gu Master, you must subdue them!"

Bai Ning Bing nodded and left, continuing to charge through the rounds.

"You are indeed someone who came from the future, using Spring Autumn Cicada to come back to the past. You know about three kings inheritance inside out." The land spirit transmitted its voice and praised, "I need to remind you, the immortal essence portions are almost depleted and are only enough for you to kill two more people. Who do you plan on killing next?"

Fang Yuan nodded and said without hesitation: "Zhang San San."

Beast placenta Gu already had eighty-nine percent aptitude and shone like a gem. Compared to its previous rough muddy shape, the difference was like night and day.

Killing two more rank four Gu Masters was enough to achieve ninety percent aptitude.

Second aperture's aptitude could not be higher than the Gu Master's first aperture. Fang Yuan's first aperture was A grade of ninety percent. Thus, the second aperture Gu's current limit was also A grade ninety percent.

Even if he raised it to ninety nine percent, when it was used, Fang Yuan would only have ninety percent. The remaining nine percent aptitude would be wasted.

Of course, if Fang Yuan could raise his first aperture's aptitude in the future, the second aperture would also have the potential to rise.

Zhang San San was only a rank four upper stage Gu Master, a stage lower than Gu Masters like Yi Huo and Kong Ri Tian.

But in Fang Yuan's view, he was the enemy who possessed the most threat.

It was because he was an enslavement path Gu Master second only to Wu Shen Tong and Wu Gui.

Fang Yuan had a plan: "Bai Ning Bing is not an enslavement path Gu Master in the end and is a complete newbie at commanding the dog groups. Later, she will definitely be confused when commanding so many dog beasts, it will be remarkable if she doesn't make any mistakes. Fortunately, I don't need her to command and control the dog beasts, and only need her to form a huge battle formation to protect the main hall and wait quietly."

Like this, it would greatly fill up for her inadequacy in commanding ability.

However, such battle formation would be extremely rigid and in case she runs into a proficient enslavement path expert, the situation would turn into a mess.

For instance, Wu Shen Tong and Wu Gui would only need to command a small group of dogs to make several attacks and probe out the actual situation. They could then send troops to lure the dog beasts repeatedly and cause disorder in the battle formation, creating a hole in the defense.

Fang Yuan would need to concentrate all his attention at the crucial stage of refining Gu. Land Spirit would also become very weak and all the defense would lie in the dog group, so Fang Yuan naturally wanted to eliminate the enslavement path Gu Masters who possessed the most threat.

After a while, Fang Yuan killed Zhang San San very smoothly.

Even Wu Gui, Wu Shen Tong and the others were killed by Fang Yuan, Zhang San San naturally could not escape his claws.

But his death gave Fang Yuan an unexpected surprise.

From Zhang San San's aperture, Fang Yuan actually obtained a rank five slavery Gu.

Slavery Gu were available from rank one to rank five. Once these Gu were implanted on someone, it could control that Gu Master.

Rank five enslavement Gu could be used to control rank five Gu Master and was thus very precious and extremely rare. Back in the day on Qing Mao mountain, Gu Yue clan's fourth generation clan leader had a great battle with flower wine monk. After he lost the battle, he asked for forgiveness and said he was willing to be enslaved by slavery Gu and be at flower wine monk's disposal. In the end, flower wine monk was deceived by these words and during his moment of carelessness, he was counterattacked by the fourth generation clan leader, dying regretfully on Qing Mao mountain.

"Famous Gu Masters are not to be underestimated. This Zhang San San is an enslavement path Gu Master, it is not strange for him to possess enslavement Gu. The reason he had not used it was to wait for a good opportunity and get a rank five expert. After all, if a rank five slavery Gu were to be used on a rank four Gu Master, it would be a huge loss."

Fang Yuan slightly thought and guessed Zhang San San's thoughts.

He looked at the beast placenta Gu, its aptitude had already neared ninety percent, he only needed to kill one more.

Immortal essence portions were exhausted, so Fang Yuan could only kill one more anyway.

"With this enslavement Gu, I can control one person. Sigh, if I had known this Zhang San San had this Gu, I would have first killed him and used the enslavement Gu to subdue a rank five Gu Master."

Fang Yuan felt some regret. If he had used this Gu to subdue Tie Mu Bai, it would be greatly advantageous to his Gu refinement!

Even if he did not get Tie Mu Bai, Wu Gui, Ku Mo, Wu Lan Shan or Chou Jiu were also extremely good choices.

However now, they were all dead, Fang Yuan at best could only subdue rank four Gu Master, but using rank five enslavement Gu on rank four Gu Masters was equivalent to using an ox-cleaver to kill chicken, a complete waste of its value.

However, despite the rank five enslavement Gu being extremely precious and it would be a waste of its value, Fang Yuan was still going to use it!

He would be facing enormous risks while refining second aperture Gu, and would no doubt be much safer with a second rank four Gu Master beside him.

But there were so many rank four Gu Masters in the blessed land, who should he subdue?

Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian, Long Qing Tian, Yi Chong along with Li Fei Le, Tao Zi, Feng Tian Yu, Yan Jun, Li Xian, Hu Mei Er, Tie clan's four old-timers, Tie Ruo Nan and others; some were powerful, some were cunning, some were sinister, some were brave, some specialized in long ranged attacks, some had outstanding movement ability, some were superior in healing, some had huge wealth, some had large connections...

Every choice had its consequences.

Fang Yuan's thoughts rumbled like lightning and after thinking for a good while, he decided upon a choice.

"It shall be him. Land spirit, transport me." Fang Yuan decided and said with no hesitation.

After about three minutes, Feng Tian Yu was kneeling in front of Fang Yuan and wholeheartedly said: "This subordinate Feng Tian Yu greets master!"

"Feng Tian Yu, you could refine rank five Gu when you were at rank three. Although the rank five Gu died after half a day, you achieved instant reputation from this. Now, things have changed, your clan is dwindling and facing extinction, you are no longer the young clan leader that had infinite prospects once." Fang Yuan looked at the kneeling Feng Tian Yu and said indifferently.

Feng Tian Yu raised his head: "Having lord as my master, it is this subordinate's honor and fortune."

"It is good that you understand this point. Next, continue to charge through the rounds according to my instructions. King Xin inheritance has an undefeated hundred battles Gu, bring it to me." Fang Yuan instructed.

"Yes, this subordinate will exhaust all his strength to do this task for master!" Feng Tian Yu promptly replied.

Under the control of the enslavement Gu, he had become a loyal and devoted slave of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt reassured at Feng Tian Yu.

He was not only a famous and talented grand master of the refinement path in Southern Border, he was the biggest beneficiary of King Xin's inheritance in his previous life.

In Fang Yuan's memories, it was him who obtained undefeated hundred battles Gu.

Now after rebirth, Fang Yuan was not only going to obtain undefeated hundred battles Gu, but also take the original owner as his subordinate.

"Feng Tian Yu will be guided by the land spirit, it won't be a problem for him to charge through King Xin's inheritance. Like this, I have already acquired two of three kings inheritance."

However, this was also not Fang Yuan's main reason.

The reason why he chose Feng Tian Yu was because of his innate talent at refinement path.

After all, it was the first time Fang Yuan was refining the second aperture Gu. With such a grandmaster of refinement path beside him, it would definitely be a huge help in refining the Gu.

After taking in Feng Tian Yu, Fang Yuan began to consider his last target to kill.

Kill who?

Fang Yuan's first thought was not the strongest Yi Huo and was also not the influential Hu Mei Er and Tao Zi, but rather Tie Ruo Nan.

Like Tie Mu Bai, Fang Yuan also thought highly of Tie Ruo Nan's future prospects. Such a genius that had already been sharpened through trials, if she was allowed to grow, she was bound to be a huge threat. She was more terrifying that even Yi Huo and others.

However, the problem now was, the threat Tie Ruo Nan brought to Fang Yuan was far lower than Gu Masters like Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian and others.

For the second aperture Gu refinement, if Fang Yuan killed Yi Huo, it would absolutely be more helpful than killing Tie Ruo Nan.

To kill Yi Huo just to be safe, or root out Tie Ruo Nan in consideration of the future?

Fang Yuan's thoughts were suddenly interrupted by the land spirit: "Not good, something happened!"

"What?" Fang Yuan was surprised, the land spirit's tone hid a trace of panic.

"A rank four Gu Master has discovered a weak area of the blessed land. That area had been seriously damaged due to earth calamity, the heavenly power at that area is the weakest and the Gu Masters can use one Gu there. Now, he is using a rank five Gu to spread poison all over the place. He will open a passage to the outside world in around eight minutes at this rate, and create a hole in the blessed land!"

Fang Yuan immediately sensed the seriousness of the matter.

In his previous life, he was a rank six Gu Immortal and had once possessed a blessed land, naturally knowing the importance of this.

If there was a hole in the blessed land and it connects with the outside world, the immortal essence expenditure would double. If it was not stopped and repaired in time, the hole would grow bigger and bigger, finally attracting winds of assimilation.

Once the winds of assimilation blew, the blessed land would be destroyed.

"I have already separated and cut off most of the areas with holes in the blessed land. But there are three places that are in crucial areas and can't be cut off. To think this person's luck is so good to actually bump into one of the areas and even be aware of the hole. For the actual situation, take a look." The land spirit heaved a sigh.

A scene appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

In the scene, there was a Gu Master wearing dark blue robe, he was thin and his gaze was gloomy.

It was none other than Long Qing Tian!

Right now, he was activating his sole rank five poison Gu — jade sky.

Everywhere around him, the land and the sky were all suffused with a layer of pale green light.

He who once dyed the sky jade green!

Jade sky Gu was Long Qing Tian's core trump card, a Gu from the immemorial times and was fundamental extinct now. Long Qing Tian had used this Gu to roam Southern Border and gain terrifying reputation for poisoning countless people.

Now, he was poisoning this part of the blessed land!

Chapter 388: Jade Sky Qing Tian, Hu Immortal Jin Huang

"To think my luck is so good, I accidentally found this weakened zone." Long Qing Tian's gaze shone as he showed an excited expression.

After all, although the three kings inheritance had a hundred rounds, each one had multiple choices, like the branches of a gigantic tree.

Him arriving at this place was rarer than one out of ten thousand, his luck was maxed out.

"The heavenly power restricting this place is very weak, I can actually use one Gu. Haha, I will use the jade sky Gu and poison this blessed land, that way, I will be able to communicate with the main world and form a connection.

"Once the path is made, I will be able to use Gu worms here at will, I will not have to obey the three kings' rules. After that, I will use this place as my base and expand my influence, and get all the rewards. Hehehe, eh? Who is it!"

Long Qing Tian sensed something and turned around, seeing one person far away.

"Little beast king Fang Zheng?" Long Qing Tian squinted, feeling weird that Fang Yuan was here.

Fang Yuan did not reply, he waved his hand and a bone spike flew out.

Long Qing Tian snorted, activating his defensive Gu.

All around him was the jade-green jade sky Gu's poison, already invading a huge area. Fang Yuan did not have detoxification methods and did not dare to touch the Gu poison, thus he could only engage in long range battle.

At this time, Fang Yuan only had the mutated beast phantoms left, but he did not have the rank four all-out effort Gu, thus he could not summon them as he wished.

But he had killed so many Gu Master experts, and obtained many different Gu worms that could be used for long range attacks.

In a few rounds of battle, Long Qing Tian was defeated by Fang Yuan.

Long Qing Tian could only use one Gu at any given time. Fang Yuan could use any number of Gu with the help of the land spirit. The difference between the two was huge.

Although he won, Fang Yuan's expression was ugly.

Long Qing Tian's corpse was a pale jade-green color, already poisoned by the jade sky Gu poison.

This demonic expert, before his death, smiled at Fang Yuan darkly, before activating the jade sky Gu and killed himself with poison.

Fang Yuan did not kill Long Qing Tian, he knew he had no hopes of surviving and suicided.

"As expected of a demonic head." Fang Yuan breathed out deeply.

Jade sky Gu contained a special poison from the immemorial era, it is already extinct. In the current southern border, only the four great doctors can cleanse it.

If Fang Yuan wanted to devour his aperture, he would have to make contact with the poison. If he got poisoned, in less than two hours, his whole body will fade into a green light.

Very few Gu Masters could survive after getting hit with the jade sky Gu poison.

Wu Shen Tong from Wu clan was extremely lucky.

Even if Fang Yuan risked getting poisoned, he might not get any Gu. With the weak heavenly power here, Long Qing Tian could easily self-detonate his Gu worms one by one.

The benefits were not proportional to the risks, Fang Yuan would not do it.

"But because of this, my last portion of immortal essence has been expended on Long Qing Tian. The beast strength placenta Gu's aptitude can only reach eighty-nine percent."

Fang Yuan felt great pity, after working so hard, he did not reach his desired ninety percent.

"I am after all too weak. The execution of these kind of plans can only be left to chances.

This unexpected situation that Long Qing Tian caused caught him off guard.

Fang Yuan was human, not god, he did not expect this to occur.

Although he had his previous life's memories, and could clearly recall the details, for such minor details, if nobody mentioned it, who would know?

Moreover, after his rebirth, he changed many events. Whether this incident by Long Qing Tian happened in his previous life was unknown.

"Nevermind about the beast strength placenta Gu, what's worse is that the land had already been infected by the jade sky Gu poison, the poison will eventually break out! By then, this land will rot, and turn into green-blue light, creating a huge hole."

Fang Yuan looked at this area, as the green color darkened and spread further out.

Such a loophole would accelerate the blessed land's destruction. That also means that the land spirit will get even weaker.

"If it was a younger blessed land, as long as immortal essence is sufficient, even if the poison cannot be cured, it will be able to cut away this rotten area and fix the hole. But this blessed land is already too old, and lack in immortal essence. Forming a hole here now is like the last straw that breaks the camel's back. Sigh, I have little time left to refine Gu, I must hurry."

At this point, Fang Yuan's merciless slaughter had reached its end. He returned to the hall, and fought against time, refining his Gu!

As days passed, Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure intensified.

Fang Yuan only slept an hour a day, forcing himself to the limits.

As he worked hard like his life was on the line, other than a few unavoidable failures, his process was rapid. Even the land spirit was full of praises.

While Fang Yuan moved closer towards success, his younger brother was extremely high-spirited.

....

Central Continent, Tian Ti mountain.

At the middle of Hu Immortal blessed land, on Dang Hun mountain, Fang Zheng climbed with great effort, surpassing people after people.

During this period, he became the center of attention, attracting many people's gazes.

"It's him, that Fang Zheng from Immortal Crane Sect! He surpassed another person again!" Someone was jealous and envious.

"Fang Zheng..." Looking at Fang Zheng's ascending silhouette, Fairy Bi Xia had a complicated gaze.

"Something weird is going on with this lad! At this rate, he might be the first to reach the peak!" Wei Wu Shang who has some rivalry with Fang Zheng had to admit that Fang Zheng had a high chance of success.

Fang Zheng used both his hands and legs, climbing laboriously.

He breathed raggedly, with Lord Sky Crane's help, he surpassed the ten sect elites one by one.

Eventually, there were only three people above him.

Xiao Qi Xing, Ying Sheng Ji, Feng Jin Huang!

"This lad is finally at the front, I did not use one's own way Gu in vain." He Feng Yang was watching closely, after seeing this, he sighed in relief.

"Without any accidents, the victor will be one of these four." A Gu Immortal said mentally.

"Immortal Crane Sect's speed is fast, but hehe, it is still uncertain who wins until the last second."

"Indeed, Immortal Crane Sect is only fourth now, and had a huge difference with the first three. Now, it depends on whether he can surpass them in the limited time ahead."

The Gu Immortals conversed.

The entire inheritance competition had reached its final stage!

...

In the grand hall, a lump of multi-colored light about the size of a water tank floated in the air as it spun.

Fang Yuan controlled it as his eyes were bloodshot, muttering: "Retrieve ninety grams of willow orpiment."

At once, a relief sculpture moved away from the flooring, and turned into solid mass, it was the willow orpiment.

This was a material was from ancient times, rarely seen in today's world, it was retrieved by land spirit, carving out ninety grams and placing it into the rainbow-colored light.

Fang Yuan concentrated, not having any carelessness, as the light turned yellow, he spoke: "Retrieve thirty snowball Gu."

Thirty snowball Gu flew into the yellow light, the light lump that was water tank size was still yellow, but its volume was shrinking.

Eventually, it turned into a tiny inconspicuous soil-yellow rock.

Fang Yuan carefully held this rock, breathing in deeply. To refine this Gu, he spent two days and one night, it had finally ended.

He was extremely tired, lying down and falling asleep immediately, wanting to sleep for an entire week straight.

But after an hour, he was woken up by the land spirit.

This rock could not exist for long, after another fifteen minutes, it would evaporate. By then, Fang Yuan's hard work would have gone down the drain, and he would need to start over.

"Refining Gu is difficult, it has to be a strength path Gu Master that has mastery over the refinement path. Even I, who has my memories and foundation, found it hard, and almost failed many times before, it was truly nerve wrecking. No wonder no one managed to refine the second aperture Gu in my previous life."

Fang Yuan sighed as he patted his cheeks, waking himself up.

After resting for an hour, he felt much better, but his head was still heavy. He had used up too much mental energy, and he was mentally drained.

The second aperture Gu was a rank six Gu, refining an Immortal Gu was not an easy task.

Fang Yuan did not need to look at the mirror to know that he definitely looked pale with deep eye bags, having messy hair and an extremely exhausted expression.

"Land spirit, how much immortal essence left?" He asked.

"Five portions left." Land spirit answered, weakness could be felt from its voice.

Eighteen days had past since Long Qing Tian was killed.

The rate of weakening of the blessed land shocked Fang Yuan secretly.

To sustain the three kings inheritance, immortal essence was expended greatly. Such a phenomenon had caused the outside world to go wild.

At this period, more and more Gu Master came to explore to blessed land, some were established experts.

"Only five portions of immortal essence are left, but the Gu refinement is only two-thirds done. Land spirit, what day and month is it?" Fang Yuan asked with a grim expression.

"According to your calendar, today is the nineteenth of October."

"Nineteenth of October, according to my calculations, the second aperture Gu's refinement will reach the last step in five days. October twenty-fourth... eh? In history, isn't this the day where Feng Jin Huang attains victory and inherits the Hu Immortal blessed land?" Fang Yuan thought of Feng Jin Huang.

This girl had exemplary talent and a strong background, after inheriting Hu Immortal blessed land, she shot up rapidly. In future, she cultivated to Gu Immortal realm using this, and spread her influence throughout the world, shining with a brilliant light.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he escaped southern border and arrived at central continent, becoming a Gu Immortal and after creating the bloodwing demonic sect, this woman was his mortal enemy. They had at least a few hundred battles, and eventually, Fang Yuan allied with numerous demonic path Gu Immortals and attacked Hu Immortal blessed land together, paying a painful price to kill her.

"My influence now should not have reached central continent yet. Feng Jin Huang obtained Hu Immortal blessed land, the benefit was as great as the heaven! Even second aperture Gu cannot compare to it."

Fang Yuan sighed, his previous life's enemy was about to soar to heaven, yet he was too far away and could not stop it.

Fang Yuan did not know that his brother was still alive, and was engaging in a fierce competition with Feng Jin Huang and the others.

The influence of his rebirth, had already affected central continent's ten sects.

Chapter 389: Only one step left

October 20th.

In the main hall, faint red rays of light began to vanish and shone upon the surroundings.

The relief sculptures on the bronze tiles had already disappeared by more than half.

Fang Yuan's face was pale and he looked haggard, his eyes were red as his gaze was fixed at every change in the light lump.

Everything was silent.

October 21st.

The land spirit brought a bad news; a rank five expert had entered the blessed land.

Fang Yuan looked at the image and immediately recognized this person: "So it was Xiao Mang of Xiao clan. He is an expert of the light path and possesses rank five extreme light Gu. In my previous life, he appeared on San Cha mountain, he came after all."

The land spirit gasped: "Extreme light Gu? Then it means this Xiao Mang can summon the light of glory of the immemorial era! This enemy is a huge threat to us!"

The land spirit was extremely worried.

Immemorial times had nine heavens; white heaven, red heaven, orange heaven, yellow heaven, green heaven, azure heaven, blue heaven, purple heaven and black heaven.

The sunlight of the immemorial era was extraordinary, it was the light of glory and could pierce through the nine heavens and spread its warmth and grace to all living beings.

At present, red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue and purple heavens were no more, only white heaven and black heaven remained. The sunlight no longer contained the glory of the immemorial era, and had weakened to the extreme, being able to pierce through only the white heaven.

Rank five extreme light Gu, once activate, could burst out with the intense light of glory of immemorial era. This light did not have even a little bit of attack power, but it could pass through everything and shine upon on every corner of the world.

That is to say, even this blessed land could not cut off immemorial light.

Fang Yuan scoffed: "Ba Gui, you can be relieved. He obtained the extreme light Gu from robbing a tomb and is an incomplete Gu. He can only use it three times every month. If he crosses this limit, the Gu will self-destruct."

The land spirit let out a breath of relief: "That's good. These days, I have been getting weaker. At the final juncture, you will have to rely on yourself."

"Hehe, I have always liked relying on myself." Fang Yuan laughed and continued to refine Gu without saying any more.

October 22nd.

Puff...

"Damn it, another failure!"

Fang Yuan spat out a large mouthful of blood, his eyes turned black and almost lost his consciousness.

He gritted his teeth and held the ground; he felt the world was spinning, he seemed to see stars and there were continuous buzzing sounds in his ears.

Especially, his chest felt stifled and he felt like vomiting.

After a long while, this nauseous feeling eased slightly.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air and slowly sat down.

"Failure in Gu refinement will cause a backlash. I have already failed three times in this step, it is not that my skills are bad, I already did it perfectly but this step seems to rely on luck and has a probability of one in a ten chance of success. Sigh! There is no time!"

Fang Yuan was looking pale, he resisted the pain of the backlash with great difficulty and began his fourth attempt.

At this moment, the immortal essence in the bronze cauldron was less than four portions.

October 23rd.

Fang Yuan stopped his actions and looked at the Gu worm in his hand with bright light shining in his eyes.

This Gu was like a beetle with a big and graceful belly, a pointed head and tail. It did not have any legs or antennas. It's shape was vague, seemingly like a vague carving on crude earthenware, with no vitality like a grey stone.

The earth spirit was joyous: "Young man, I really didn't misjudge you! You have succeeded in refining this false Gu, now you only need to advance a step and turn false into real and refine the true second aperture Gu!"

"That's right, only one step remains." Fang Yuan's tone was complicated, relaxed and yet heavy.

Refining this second aperture Gu was like climbing a mountain. There were thousands of steps and who knew how many times he had failed, and he had gotten almost no rest, but finally he reached this stage. His previous effort and investment were not in vain, thus he was relaxed.

However, this final step was the most crucial moment, a step of qualitative change and required the use of Immortal Gu divine travel Gu.

Although Fang Yuan had succeeded in refining Spring Autumn Cicada, he had never used Immortal Gu to refine Immortal Gu; this final step was the step which he did not have any certainty of, so his mood was heavy.

"Three hundred years as spring, five hundred years as autumn. With unlimited divine opportunity, swim and roam in the wilds, adding in third watch, and another third watch, obtaining nine. Nine as extreme, the refinement is complete... This final step required the use of lifespan Gu, divine travel Gu and also two third watch Gu." Fang Yuan pondered.

He understood the earlier steps and could even modify them. But as for this step, he only slightly understood its real intent.

"Land spirit, what changes have occured in the blessed land?" Fang Yuan suddenly asked.

"Two batch of troops have arrived with dozens of rank three Gu Masters, each being led by a rank four Gu Master; their momentum is great." The land spirit showed the scenes to Fang Yuan.

"So it is Che clan and Zuo clan, tsk, the two clan leaders are leading and it seems most of the elders have come." Fang Yuan recognized them with a glance.

The whole San Cha mountain was located in between Zuo clan's Leng Chan mountain and Che clan's Fei Lai mountain.

These two clans were continuously expanding and in the recent years, had been competing at the front line of San Cha mountain with the intent to occupy it.

However, the sudden appearance of the three kings inheritance thoroughly ruined these two clans' plan.

There were a hundred thousand famous mountains in the whole Southern Border along with countless unnamed mountains and hills which were covered with wild and ferocious beasts, their surroundings were dangerous and extremely hard to pass.

Other forces could only send their elites. But these two clans were nearby and had restrained themselves at the beginning, but now when they felt the strange change in the inheritance, they finally send most of their troops.

To Fang Yuan, this was bad news.

At the final juncture, everyone was sure to attack the center of the blessed land, this main hall. These Che clan and Zuo clan's troops were all Fang Yuan's enemies.

"Besides them, when the time comes, there will be Li Xian, Hu Mei Er, Yi Huo, Kong Ri Tian and other experts. At the final juncture, I will have to concentrate fully on refining Gu and leave the defense to land spirit, Bai Ning Bing and Feng Tian Yu. This is however only the external danger."

"At the final step, I will need to use two third watch Gu in a row, causing the time to flow nine times faster on me! This is a great tonic to Spring Autumn Cicada and at that time, its pressure will increase drastically and endanger my aperture. This is the internal danger."

"With both internal and external danger, danger lurks everywhere. But I can only grit my teeth and persevere. I have already reached this stage, only one step remains before I am able to step on the summit. I will bet on this. If I really succeed, I will have a second aperture and as I cultivate to rank six in future, I will not fall too far behind Feng Jin Huang.

In Fang Yuan's plan after rebirth, Qing Mao mountain and Shang Clan were only a platform while the second aperture Gu was the stepping stone.

But it was because of these small accumulations that he could sprint further.

Next, there will be many opportunities which he would have no qualifications to participate without a certain cultivation and strength!

"All living beings have to go through survival of the fittest, I can't compromise on these opportunities and have to make every second count. Only then will I not let down my future knowledge...."

Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh before beginning to rest, preparing for the final day.

October 24th.

Fang Yuan woke up from his deep sleep and slowly opened his eyes.

"It has been so many days since I had such a comfortable sleep, next is the great battle!" He stood up and slowly paced around the main hall.

Under the land spirit's guidance, there were already two people standing outside the main hall.

"Master!" Feng Tian Yu immediately kneeled in front of Fang Yuan and offered a Gu worm.

This Gu was nothing special in its appearance, looking like a round piece of limestone. It was none other than undefeated hundred battles Gu.

"Subordinate was able to accomplish the mission, and after going through the hundredth round and receiving King Xin Inheritance, I was able to take in these hairy men."

At his side stood several hundred hairy men, their bodies were filled with dense hair and were standing there quietly.

"Good." Fang Yuan nodded and indifferently praised, he was not surprised.

These hairy men had the innate nature to follow the people who were better at refining Gu than them. It was not surprising for Feng Tian Yu to charge through the hundredth barrier and have these followers.

Fang Yuan then walked towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing looked at the great bronze main hall, her gaze flashing with a trace of understanding: "It seems this is the blessed land's center area."

Saying so, she looked at Fang Yuan: "Hmph, you best remember your promise."

Fang Yuan smiled: "You can be at ease."

He looked behind Bai Ning Bing, seeing the near hundred thousand dog beasts that did not seem to have an end; some were occupying an area, some were having fun with each other and some were running around, making a din.

Fang Yuan slightly furrowed his brows, this was the weakness of Bai Ning Bing's commanding ability. If it was Zhang San San, Wu Gui or Wu Shen Tong, any one of them could arrange these dogs in a tight formation and have them stand there without moving, like an army.

However, this was after all something entirely beyond Bai Ning Bing, she had never received any enslavement path training before, and it was already not easy for her to be able to reach this stage.

In fact, Bai Ning Bing was feeling dizzy now, her every movement was slightly lagging and her soul felt heavy, she felt her body was like a marionette.

Controlling so many dog beasts at once was truly demanding a lot out of her.

"Listen to my arrangements now, be in a defensive formation. No matter how the enemies provoke you, do not take the initiative to attack. Remember it at all costs, remember." Fang Yuan warned.

"Okay, since it is your arrangement, whether this succeeds or fails has no relation to me." Bai Ning Bing coldly replied.

"Hehe, no matter success or failure, I will give you the Yang Gu." Fang Yuan assured with a smile.

"Hmph, you better do what you said."

...

"Two light pillars have disappeared, this means King Xin and King Quan Inheritance have been taken!" Early morning, at the peak of San Cha mountain, there was a commotion among the Gu Masters.

"This time's inheritation opening is extremely strange, it has been maintaining itself till today, causing the blessed land to deteriorate extremely fast." Someone was doubtful.

But compared to this, more people were paying attention towards the inheritance.

"Who are the two lucky guys who inherited the inheritance?"

"I think King Xin Inheritance should be inherited by Lord Tie Mu Bai. He has not come out since he entered."

"King Quan Inheritance might have been inherited by Wu Gui."

"No, it should be our clan's lord Wu Shen Tong."

"Hmph, the way I see it, our demonic path's enslavement master Zhang San San also has a chance of winning."

The crowd argued for a while before someone finally discovered something strange.

"Strange, none of the several rank five Gu Masters that entered the inheritance has come out. What is going on?"

"King Xin and King Quan Inheritance were inherited, but why have the other guys not come out?"

"They are being detained in the blessed land. This blessed land is already nearing its extinction, not long later the passage will open wide and let all of us enter and exit at will." A resonant voice spread.

"Lord Xiao Mang!" Immediately, the righteous path Gu Masters recognized the identity of the speaker.

"This Xiao Mang has not entered the inheritance after he arrived on San Cha mountain, what the heck is he planning?" Demonic Gu Masters felt apprehensive inwardly, Xiao Mang's arrival had suppressed their flames.

Xiao Mang proudly smiled after succeeding in attracting everyone's gaze: "Now I will use extreme light Gu to open the passage for us!"

When he finished speaking, he opened his eyes wide and furiously activated his primeval essence while lifting his fists high.

Extreme light Gu!

Heaven's will Gu!

Empty fist Gu!

Killer move — Immemorial Light Fist!

Three Gu activated at once, causing the whole sky to dim.

Everyone looked with shock as light rays formed into an enormous fist the size of a mountain, it appeared abruptly and disappeared just as suddenly, striking at some unknown place.

Extreme light Gu might have no attacking power, but when combined with the other two Gu, it could form an incomparably intense attack!

Bam!

A formless membrane was pierced through, the blessed land shook and an enormous hole formed into a passage that connected to the outside world.

Chapter 390: Mo Wu Tian

On San Cha mountain peak, only one light pillar remained.

But a grey plain appeared in front of everyone like a foggy image. It looked like it was separated by a veil, giving off a dream-like atmosphere.

How could a plain appear on the mountain peak?

This was caused by Xiao Mang; he penetrated the blessed land and created a loophole.

For a moment, everyone was silent; some were dazed, some shocked, and some looked at each other, no one moved.

Xiao Mang snorted inwardly before slightly signalling with his eyes at somewhere in the crowd.

A Gu Master immediately ran out of the crowd: "Lord Xiao Mang's might is unrivalled, even forcibly piercing through the blessed land. Like this, we are no longer confined by the restrictions of three kings inheritance and all of us can enter!"

After he finished shouting this, he walked out of the crowd and with several jumps, entered the hole inside the blessed land.

He then activated his Gu worms in front of everyone.

One, two, and three... the heavenly power's suppression around the hole had weakened, allowing him to activate three Gu worms.

This scene immediately caused the crowd to be restless, countless people seemed to be startled awake and their breathing turned rough.

Being able to use Gu meant they had the ability to defend themselves. That is to say, the risk in the blessed land greatly decreased.

However, the performance was still not over, this Gu Master suddenly ran back and with several jumps, got out of the blessed land and returned to San Cha mountain.

"Hahaha!" He laughed loudly and cupped his fists to Xiao Mang, "Thank you lord for your favor!"

Xiao Mang chuckled: "There is no need for thanks, no need. I only felt that everyone should have the rights to compete for the treasures of heaven and earth. It is too much that only a few people hog them. However, how much you can seize will have to depend on yourselves."

"We are very grateful to Lord Xiao Mang!"

"Lord Xiao Mang is a great person, and his elder brother is the hero Xiao Shan."

"Truly, they are a pair of dragon and tiger brothers!"

"Looking at all the great rank five Gu Masters at San Cha mountain, only Lord Xiao Mang cared about us weaker characters, he is a role model of the righteous path, he is so kind..."

The cheers and flattery of everyone entered Xiao Mang's ears like a tide.

The crowd of people charged into the blessed land.

"A bunch of idiots." Xiao Mang was beaming with a warm and gentle smile, but was disdainfully scoffing inwardly.

"I came really late compared to Tie Mu Bai, Wu Gui and the others. King Quan and King Xin Inheritances have been taken, now only King Bao remains! Damn them! I had already pleaded with father and the elders, but they were only concerned about Xiao Shan's illness! Hmph, it would be best if he dies, then I will become young clan leader..."

"Hmph, only after coaxing and pestering was I permitted to come to San Cha mountain, but it is too late already! How can I compare to those guys who came before me? Only by creating a hole in the blessed land, and causing chaos can I get benefits from within!"

"As for this blessed land, the more people that goes in, the more burden it will have to bear. Hehehe, the heavenly power will get weaker and weaker. So what if you guys obtained the inheritance? I can completely use my Gu worms to seize them! King Bao, King Quan and King Qin Inheritance, they are all mine! If I can't obtain them, then you guys can also stop thinking of them!"

...

"Alright, this is more or less it." Fang Yuan nodded with satisfaction as he looked at his surroundings.

This bronze main hall was situated on a hill. The hill was not steep and rather had gentle slopes around it.

Such a terrain was not easy to defend, but the numbers of the dog beasts slightly made up for it.

For over two hours, Fang Yuan had been arranging the formation for Bai Ning Bing and explaining to her how to deal with any situations that could occur.

BOOM...

Right at this time, the whole world shook and some dust fell off from the ceiling of the bronze hall.

"Not good, that Xiao Mang used extreme light Gu to pierce through the blessed land and formed a passage. Large numbers of Gu Masters are rushing in, killing and competing; the whole situation has completely fallen into chaos!" The lands spirit's voice resounded.

Fang Yuan chuckled without any panic.

In his previous life's memories, it had been the same. Xiao Mang's arrival signified the development of this scene.

"Chaos is good, Xiao Mang wants to profit from this chaos while I need this chaotic situation to help me drag for time." Fang Yuan's dark eyes flashed with eerie light.

"Eh? A rank five Gu Master actually mixed in among this crowd... this young man is really amazing to be able to deceive my senses, I only found something wrong when he made his move!" The land spirit suddenly said.

Fang Yuan furrowed his brows, this development was beyond his expectation: "Who is it?"

The image in front of him stopped and showed a young man with long black hair that reached up to his waist. He had a pair of deep and dark purple eyes with thick eyebrows which ends were raised up, giving him a crazed disposition like burning flames.

He gave off an awe-inspiring demonic aura, disregarding the world, an unbridled tyrannical aura that seemed to want to destroy the world like the descent of an evil dragon.

"Mo Wu Tian!" Fang Yuan gaze concentrated and recognized the man.

This person was a genius of the demonic path who had inherited an ancient inheritance and was a soul path Gu Master. Whether it was his reputation or power, Fang Yuan was not his match.

In his memories, in the battle of Yi Tian mountain, Mo Wu Tian had beheaded several rank five righteous path Gu Masters, his reputation was fearsome and his demonic flames soared to the skies. At the end, when the demonic path was completely defeated, Mo Wu Tian broke through the besiegement and stormed out with no one being able to obstruct him.

"In my previous life, Mo Wu Tian did not come to San Cha mountain! It seems the influence of my rebirth has already affected a person of such strength?"

Just as Fang Yuan was contemplating, inside the image, Mo Wu Tian seemed to have discovered being watched; he slightly turned around and unexpectedly looked right in Fang Yuan's direction.

"So it was this way..." He muttered in a soft voice and the corner of his lips formed a sinister smile.

"This is bad, he seems to have sensed us and is charging towards here!" The land spirit immediately gave a warning.

Fang Yuan's eyes squinted into a slit, Mo Wu Tian was actually targeting him with an intense hostility. What are his intentions, and what did he discover?

"The chaos will only last for a some time and when Tie Mu Bai and the others don't show up, it will start creating doubt. We don't have much time, we need to immediately start with the Gu refinement! Land spirit, raise the fog. Feng Tian Yu, follow me into the main hall and help me in Gu refinement!"

They were pressed for time, Fang Yuan shouted his commands and brought Feng Tian Yu into the bronze hall.

As for the hairy men that followed Feng Tian Yu, they were left outside to surround and protect the main hall, forming into the final line of defense.

Looking at Fang Yuan and Feng Tian Yu's departing figures, Bai Ning Bing's eyes flashed with a cold light.

The fog began to rise and spread, covering the main hall quickly before covering all the dog beasts on the hill.

...

The bronze hall was spacious and majestic, its walls echoed back Fang Yuan and Feng Tian Yu's footsteps, making the silence and the emptiness of this place even more conspicuous.

At present, the bronze tiles on the main hall were already a scene of emptiness — most of the materials and Gu worms were already consumed in refining Gu with only a few relief sculptures remaining now.

Fang Yuan walked to the bronze cauldron with Feng Tian Yu and sat cross-legged.

"This is the final step, the true crucial moment!" He took a deep breath, his eyes as clear as water.

Feng Tian Yu's breathing, however, was rough, showing his excitement. To a refinement path Gu Master, refining an Immortal Gu was something they looked forward to the most their whole life.

"Let's start." Fang Yuan took out the false second aperture Gu and directly threw it into the bronze cauldron.

The bronze cauldron burned without fire, the thin layer of immortal essence on its bottom started to rapidly decrease and combust!

It combusted and formed into a blue smoke that gracefully rose and covered the false second aperture Gu.

The false Gu floated above the bronze cauldron and was turned into dazzling yellow light by this blue smoke.

Fang Yuan and Feng Tian Yu concentrated all their attention into blending the blue smoke and the yellow light.

After an unknown period of time, the blue smoke turned into beads of grass that floated in the air and started growing. The yellow light turned into flowers that fluttered and fell into the grass.

"It is time!" Fang Yuan took out a dagger and cut his artery, bleeding out his own essence blood.

This step was extremely important; only with this step, could the refined second aperture Gu become Fang Yuan's. Otherwise, it would be an ownerless object that would fly away once it was refined.

Large amounts of essence blood infused into smoke. The blue smoke and yellow light immediately let out sizzling sounds and turned into a red cloud like a wave of blood sea.

The blood surged and turned into a sphere that floated in the air without spreading.

The cloud was continuously evolving: Blood sea gradually calmed down and formed a field, a large expense of red paddy that was scarlet like blood grew from the field.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air at this and promptly used a Gu to heal his wounds.

Even so, he had lost a huge amounts of blood and his face had turned wan.

"Wild grass grow wildly, the qi of blood like the sea. Three hundred years as spring, five hundred years as autumn. With unlimited divine opportunity, swim and roam in the wilds, adding in third watch, and another third watch, obtaining nine. Nine as extreme, the refinement is complete!"

He already knew the recipe inside out, but still recalled it once more now.

"Three hundred years as spring, five hundred years as autumn... next, it is lifespan Gu! Ba Gui!" Fang Yuan shouted.

The land spirit was already on standby and immediately took out two lifespan Gu at Fang Yuan's call.

These lifespan Gu were one large and one small like ginseng or tree roots and gave a crude sense of touch.

The small was three hundred years lifespan Gu; it was like a blue snake that had formed into a round loop, it could increase a Gu Master's lifespan by three hundred years with no side-effects. The large one was like a young dragon that wanted to fly to the sky, bearing its claws; it could raise the lifespan by five hundred years and similarly with no side-effects.

The worth of these two Gu was self-evident. Feng Tian Yu's eyes blossomed with light and his whole body shook at the sight of these two Gu.

Fang Yuan first threw in the three hundred years lifespan Gu into the cloud.

The cloud swallowed the lifespan Gu and immediately started raging like boiling water.

Right now, the cloud seemed to have become a blue scaled long snake that attempted to slip out of Fang Yuan's control!

Fang Yuan was caught unprepared and almost lost his grasp on this blue snake.

When he managed to react, most parts of the blue snake had already slipped out with only its tail remaining in his hands.

Fang Yuan tightly gritted his teeth and opened his eyes wide; they were completely red!

He poured in all his attention and all his strength to tightly grasp the cloud and not let it escape.

Once the cloud escaped, all his previous effort would turn into an illusion!

Chapter 391: Demonic Path Alliance Army

Seconds passed like days, eventually, the cloud gradually settled down in the air.

Fang Yuan finally had the break he needed to curse the original owner of this blessed land. Such an important point was not mentioned at all in the recipe!

All because of him concentrating hard and reacting in time, together with the help of Feng Tian Yu, he was able to calm and stabilize the situation, slowly getting back his control, otherwise he would have failed.

As time passed, a mystical aura slowly spread.

The cloud completely digested the three-hundred-year lifespan Gu, calming down and turning back to the scene of 'blood field red wheat'. But at this moment, the red wheat had turned blue-green, as if new crops were growing in spring, almost overcrowding. This was what the recipe described as "three hundred years as spring".

"That mysterious Gu Immortal must've only developed the recipe but did not actually do it himself, otherwise, he would have mentioned it." Fang Yuan caught a break and thought hard: "Next, I have to use the five-hundred-year lifespan Gu, but no need to rush."

He wiped the sweat off his forehead, calling the land spirit: "Ba Gui, show me the image of the poisoned land.

Immediately, smoke images appeared in the air, showing a picture.

Long Qing Tian's corpse laid on the ground, as his surrounding sky and land were dyed a deep green colour.

This was Long Qing Tian's jade sky Gu poison.

This Gu originated from the immemorial era, it had a strong poison that Fang Yuan would not dare to touch.

At this moment, two Gu Masters appeared in the image, they had rank three cultivation.

"This place is weird, why is it so green?"

"Quickly, see, that corpse — It's Long Qing Tian!"

They entered this place and found Long Qing Tian's corpse by accident.

"Long Qing Tian is rank four peak stage, a famous demonic head, he was actually killed!"

"Quickly go see, his corpse might have something good!"

The two were happily running towards Long Qing Tian's corpse, driven by greed, they did not realize their bodies were infected by this green light.

"Courting death." Fang Yuan sneered, as expected, in less than ten steps, their poison reacted and the two of them turned into green light, dissipating.

"The jade sky Gu poison has gotten very deep, this region is almost finished, it has completely rotted, the loophole it forms will be even greater than the one Xiao Mang created."

Time was precious, every second was important, but Fang Yuan did not move regardless of how anxious he felt.

After five minutes, with a boom, the blessed land shook and the hall vibrated.

The second loophole tunnel was created!

The land spirit sighed, this way, the blessed land's speed of destruction doubled!

"Continue refining Gu!" Fang Yuan took out the five-hundred-year lifespan Gu and threw it into the cloud.

The cloud rumbled again, trying to break free of Fang Yuan's control.

But Fang Yuan was mentally prepared, he was not caught unaware like last time, and restrained it completely.

But quickly, he felt that there was nothing he could do.

The cloud's change this time, was not only giving off a slippery feeling, but also an arrogant brute force. Like a green snake that had evolved into a flood dragon, about to break free from Fang Yuan's control.

Feng Tian Yu quickly came to help, the two worked hard to suppress the cloud's transformation.

The cloud rumbled many times, about to break free at times, but was eventually suppressed.

Five minutes later, the cloud became clear again, showing a blood field with golden wheat ready for a bountiful harvest. It was the "five hundred years as autumn" scene.

Thankfully, he only refined this Gu after the poison broke out, if not, when the second loophole formed and the hall shook, this Gu refinement would have been interrupted and would not have succeeded.

Fang Yuan waited a while more, as the cloud slowly dispersed after maturing. From the water tank size, it shrunk into a new Gu, falling down.

Fang Yuan held it, it was like a peanut shell, golden and having markings on the surface, that is, scarlet blood traces.

The first false second aperture Gu could only survive for a week, it was unstable. As for this Gu, it could survive for forty years.

At this step, the real second aperture Gu had already formed, and was nurturing in the peanut shell.

But if it was allowed to develop on its own, not just a thousand years, but even if given then thousand years, it might not turn into the real product. Only by using a strong external force, to eliminate the false and make it real, turning from phantom to solid, can it attain a qualitative change, breaking free from mortality and become an immortal!

And this external force is none other than the rank six divine travel Gu!

"Next, we have to use an Immortal Gu to refine an Immortal Gu!" Fang Yuan took deep breaths, regulating his internal flow as he started the most important step of this entire refinement process.

At this time, in the outside world, sounds of killing was overwhelming the mountain...

"This dog is mine!"

"As long as you hand over your Gu worms, I will spare you your life."

"Kill all these eggmen, these variant humans are actually occupying one spirit spring, what a waste of resources!"

...

All sorts of plundering and robbing were happening, as Gu Masters killed till their eyes turned red, casualties increased greatly.

"Strange! Why have we not seen Lord Tie Mu Bai after so long!"

"Where did our Wu clan Wu Shen Tong go?"

Tie clan and Wu clan Gu Masters felt something amiss.

"Search, quickly go search!"

"The heavenly power's restriction is very small now, we can use most of our Gu worms. The situation is a mess now, there is killing everywhere, as blood flow into a river, we need to find our clan's experts to suppress the situation."

"Are there any places left unsearched?"

"The deepest part of this blessed land, there is a thick fog."

Just as these people placed their sights on the bronze hall, Mo Wu Tian had walked to the edge of the fog alone.

"There is the aura of a Immortal Gu..."

His purple eyes was deep and mysterious, with arrogance and wildness hidden within. Using the purple eyes, the fog dissipated at times, as an endless number of dogs appeared in Mo Wu Tian's vision.

He frowned.

There was strong defenses, just him alone cannot penetrate this defensive line. He needed external help.

His brows eased as Mo Wu Tian turned around.

He moved like lightning, tearing through the sky, moving a hundred miles as he landed before Hu Mei Er.

Hu Mei Er was first scared till she turned pale, after recognising Mo Wu Tian, she smiled: "Young master Wu Tian, you came too! This three kings inheritance has little meat but many wolves, you might get disappointed. Eh! You have advanced to rank five!"

Hu Mei Er looked at this man, unable to hide her shock.

She gulped, trying to alleviate this shock as she forced out a smile: "That's great, you have rank five strength, you have the ability to gain great rewards from this situation. These green eggmen have huge numbers, they have built structures and castles, I cannot break through. There is a green egg empress inside, as long as we capture her, we will be able to have endless fortune."

"Hehehe." Mo Wu Tian looked at the castle, laughing lightly: "Back then, King Bao, Wang Ba Dan, had eight egg empresses, and produced numerous eggmen. King Xin, Wang Xiao Ya's inheritance has divulge information Gu and undefeated hundred battles Gu. King Quan, Wang Er Gou, had two dog emperors, Ying Ming and Ba Huang. This is the essence of the three kings inheritance, but none of them interests me."

Hu Mei Er's smile froze: "To think that young master Wu Tian knows the three kings inheritance so clearly. Since you have no interests in it, why don't you let me have it."

"As expected of a woman, you are too short-sighted!" Mo Wu Tian laughed loudly, staring at Hu Mei Er's eyes: "Let me tell you, the land spirit of this blessed land is not dead, in the deepest area, a deceased Gu Immortal's treasure awaits!"

"What?!" Hu Mei Er was stunned.

"But there is a thick fog there and over a hundred thousand dogs guard it. To go to the central control hall, it is not enough with just the two of us." Mo Wu Tian laughed deeply.

Hu Mei Er was a smart woman, she immediately understood Mo Wu Tian's intentions.

Her eyes shone as she laughed curtly: "Hehehe, isn't it easy to recruit people?"

Hu Mei Er was a decisive person, she abandoned the green egg empress, recruiting demonic Gu Masters alone with Mo Wu Tian.

With her network, and Mo Wu Tian's cultivation and reputation, a large group of demonic Gu Masters soon gathered.

Adding in the details of the Gu Immortal's treasure, the demonic merchant Li Xian, Fiery Star Bao Tong, Rock Lizard Li Qiang and others all gathered.

Mo Wu Tian returned to the fog, no longer alone, but with a demonic army amounting to thousands of people.

"They are finally here..." Bai Ning Bing sitting on the hill stood up slowly.

The fog could obscure people's vision, but because of the land spirit's help, Bai Ning Bing had a clear vision, and could see the demonic alliance army.

Mo Wu Tian observed for a while before saying: "Li Qiang, bring three hundred people and attack head-on. After a few dozen steps, you will face the steel armor dogs. Fight as you retreat, move towards the left and engage with the chrysanthemum akita dogs. Defeat them and you will charge towards the south-east direction.

"Hu Mei Er, bring five hundred people, and go left. As you fighting your way through, you will encounter lightning symbol dogs, hedgedogs and corpse dogs, do not mind the losses, just charge towards the north."

"Bao Tong, go on the right path, bring eight hundred people. Towards the southwest direction, make a din and shout as you charge, no dogs will obstruct you for five hundred steps. After you encounter the lightning symbol dogs, fighting and charge with all you've got, if you cannot break through in forty-five minutes, retreat back here!"

"Li Xian, bring four hundred people as back-up, prepare for mobilization anytime, If I give no commands, take care of the returning troops."

"Then what about you Mo Wu Tian?" Li Xian's eyes shone with deep meaning as he asked.

"I will obviously stand guard at the base, why, you have a problem?" Mo Wu Tian looked at Li Xian lightly with his expression purple eyes.

Li Xian felt a chill in his spine.

"When did this Mo Wu Tian become so scary? His cultivation surged and his killing intent is overflowing, it seems he received an amazing ancient inheritance, if not, how could he improve so much? I had thought that little beast king could fight with him, but now it seems that he is truly the demonic path's number one genius, he is simply too fearsome."

Li Xian's heart turn cold as he obeyed the command.

With such an arrangement, four demonic experts brought their troops and charged towards the fog according to Mo Wu Tian's orders.

Chapter 392: Demonic and Righteous attacking together

"It's coming." Bai Ning Bing's gaze shone as her expression was nervous, quickly mobilizing the dog group.

The still dog army started moving, like a giant millstone. As for these Gu Masters, they became the green bean and yellow beans, in a short amount of time, they were grinded to paste. More than half were dead, some saw the danger and retreated immediately.

The demonic army suffered a huge lost, investing over a thousand men, but only a few hundred returned.

"Young master Wu Tian, did you really see clearly?" Li Qiang questioned: "I charged in according to your instructions. We did encounter the steel armor dog on the first wave, and we retreated towards the left, but we met with the assault of both lightning symbol dogs and chrysanthemum akita dogs. The numbers were too great, we can't deal with that. After a fruitless slaughter, we could only come back!"

Bao Tong's temper was even more irascible: "I brought eight hundred people, but did not hear the shouting sounds from the northwest side. But towards the southeast side, I heard people fighting. I brought my troops there and met with the combined attack of the lightning symbol dogs, hedgedogs and corpse dogs."

Hu Mei Er's expression was also ugly: "Young master Wu Tian, I listen to you and prepared to attack. But eight hundred steps in, I did not see any dog groups. Just when I was confused, dog groups came encircling us, luckily we managed to turn around and fight our way back, if not my life would've been lost there."

Li Xian was expressionless, standing at one side. His group was meant to protect the returning Gu Masters, and fight the approaching dog groups.

Although there were lots of retreating troops, not a single dog came over, causing him to waste his time waiting.

Mo Wu Tian's expression was solemn, after a while, he spoke: "I can see the actual scenario much more clearly than all of you. There is someone manipulating these dogs, it is not a fixed formation but an ever-changing one. That is why all of you failed."

Everyone was shocked: "There is someone controlling them? Who is it?"

Mo Wu Tian shook his head: "The fog is too dense, I can only see a faint figure, I can't tell the identity of the other party. But there is definitely a mastermind, only a human's intelligence can react so perfectly. But no matter, I have some understanding of the enslavement path, from now you, you have to attack like this, to break through their encirclement and obtain the Gu Immortal treasure!"

Everyone's face had blood stains as they looked at each other, nodding reluctantly due to Mo Wu Tian's rank five strength as well as the allure of the immortal treasure.

But this time, they still returned in defeat, suffering even greater losses than before.

"The person behind this has high attainment in enslavement path, I underestimated him." Mo Wu Tian frowned, he had thought of a perfect plan, using all four routes to cooperate, but the other party reacted quickly and found out his intentions. Purposely controlling his troops to intercept the four routes before they converged, such movements were at the level of a master.

"Mo Wu Tian, you have to give an explanation! We fight with our lives and lost so many people, but we have not even seen the shadow of the treasure. Are you standing here for fun? You are a rank five Gu Master, you should put in some effort too!" Bao Tong was furious as he screamed while gripping his injury.

"Oh? You want an explanation? Hehe, then I'll give you a satisfactory answer." Mo Wu Tian laughed sinisterly, as his purple eyes shone.

"You!" Bao Tong was caught by surprise as he stared at Mo Wu Tian, unable to move.

A moment later, he fell on the ground.

Dead.

The Gu Masters went into a commotion.

Fiery Star Bao Tong, he was a famous rank four fire path Gu Master. Mo Wu Tian did not even attack, he killed him with a single stare!

"You want an explanation, I gave you an explanation, are you satisfied? If you are unhappy, you can tell me." Mo Wu Tian looked at his corpse as he waited for an answer.

"You're not speaking, it seems you are satisfied." Mo Wu Tian laughed, looking around: "Hehehe, Bao Tong is satisfied, what about you guys? Do you want an explanation from me too?"

It was complete silence all around.

Mo Wu Tian killed people in the blink of an eye, Bao Tong was rank four upper stage but he could not even take one hit, dying immediately.

The demonic Gu Masters were scared and shocked, regretting their greed, why did they follow Mo Wu Tian?

Now that they were roped in, they want to leave? Hmph, too late!

Hu Mei Er and the others lowered their heads, not looking at Mo Wu Tian's eyes. Mo Wu Tian's killing technique caused fear in them.

They had thought that he had just advanted to rank five, and might not have true rank five prowess, but to think his fighting strength was on par with Wu Gui and the others!

How old was he?

Number one genius of the demonic path, without a doubt!

After establishing his dominance, Mo Wu Tian laughed sinisterly again: "Bao Tong's Gu are still around, you guys can split up among yourselves, treat it as a compensation from me."

As he said so, the Gu Masters' eyes glowed.

Li Xian was the first to react, with a swoosh, he moved like a rabbit, pouncing on Bao Tong's corpse and taking his Gu.

Almost at the same time, Hu Mei Er and Li Qiang reacted and started their plunder as well.

The others could only watch, not daring to contest.

The three split Bao Tong's fortune among themselves, earning greatly as the grudge in them dissipated, turning into reverence for Mo Wu Tian.

Mo Wu Tian could kill people with his gaze, that was not surprising, it was a sight-based killer move.

This type of killer move directly competed souls against each other, the loser would have their souls scattered, not even given the chance to self-detonate their Gu.

Mo Wu Tian was a soul path Gu Master, the strength of his soul was way above his peers, dealing with Bao Tong and the others was extremely easy.

"Cough, cough." Li Xian coughed, saying: "Since there are beast groups guarding, that area has to be where the central control hall is, the Gu Immortal's fortune is most likely there But how do we get in with all these dogs?"

He was wise like a ghost, as the person who obtained the most benefits out of Bao Tong's body, he immediately expressed his support towards Mo Wu Tian.

Speaking of the Gu Immortal treasure, Hu Mei Er and Li Qiang's attention were brought back to this.

Mo Wu Tian looked at this group of people, they were all injured and exhausted, together with some lingering fear, the morale was at an all-time low.

He sighed: "Truly a motley crew. It seems I can only recruit more people to have the hopes of breaking in. Spread the news, regardless of righteous or demonic... just say that Tie Mu Bai and the others have entered the hall and obtained King Quan Inheritance, those Gu Masters are blocking us outside the hall and are trying to hoard the treasure."

"This..." Hu Mei Er hesitated.

Mo Wu Tian laughed coldly: "Time is running short, once the blessed land collapses, we will have nothing left. Without more people, can we break through?"

"Young master is right." Hu Mei Er quickly replied.

"Finally stopped." On the mountain slope, Bai Ning Bing breathed out a sigh of relief, but lightly frowned.

The methods Fang Yuan handed to her were already half used up. After a few more attacks, she would be at her wits' end.

...

"Hahaha, my tactic at finding a chance in the chaos succeeded. After blowing up this wall, I will get King Bao, Wang Ba Dan's inheritance!" Xiao Mang laughed loudly.

Right now, he was alone in a hidden cave.

Before him, there was a tall and sturdy stone door. As long as it is blown apart, King Bao's final inheritance will be obtained.

Bam! Bam! Bam!

Light shone as explosions went off.

A moment later, Xiao Mang stopped his attacks while panting, staring at the stone door hatefully.

The door was intact, there was no traces of any cracks.

"Light path focuses on speed and purification, the destructive power does not match fire path. King Bao evidently wants to find a fated person who can use fire type Gu to break through. But I do not have such Gu." Xiao Mang gritted his teeth, feeling indignant.

At this moment, a Gu Master came to report.

"Go out, who let you in! King Bao Inheritance is mine alone. Eh? What did you say!"

Xiao Mang scolded but suddenly heard his subordinate's report and grabbed his collar, lifting him up: "You say there is a Gu Immortal treasure hidden in the thick fog, and people are trying to take it down now?!"

"Yes, this information has circulated, countless Gu Masters are gathering, how would I dare to lie to you second young master?" The subordinate quickly replied.

"Hmph, don't call me second young master! I hate that title!" Xiao Mang scolded, looking at this stone door reluctantly, as his gaze turned from hesitation to determination.

Wang Ba Dan was only a rank five Gu Master, although he was called King Bao, he was only the same rank as Xiao Mang. How could his inheritance compare to a Gu Immortal Treasure?

"Go, let's go!" Xiao Mang led his subordinates and moved quickly.

...

"The number of people is increasing." On the slope, Bai Ning Bing's frown deepened as there were almost ten thousand people gathered outside the fog.

These people had differing cultivation levels, there were even rank one and twos. But there were still Gu Masters, gathered together, they formed a tidal wave that could sweep everything in its path.

Although she controlled a hundred thousand dogs, she was a sole person.

Outside, countless gazes looked inside with a burning desire. They were all attracted by the Immortal's treasure.

As the people created a commotion, Mo Wu Tian smiled without speaking a word.

His motive was achieved, birds die for food and humans die for fortune, this was human heart!

"Over at the righteous path, they are organising people and charging into the fog." Hu Mei Er looked far away, worried: "Young master Wu Tian, all the demonic Gu Masters are here already, are you going to stand up and direct them to form groups? We can't let the righteous path steal the treasure."

"No worries, no worries. There is such a thick fog, with steel armor dogs acting as steel walls, what can their vanguards do?" Mo Wu Tian laughed coldly, refusing to act.

Righteous path was superior to demonic path, they were more united,and more easy to unite, while demonic path members were loners. Although he Mo Wu Tian had rank five cultivation, he was still young and this was the first time he was leading, he could not subdue everyone. Old demonic experts like Kong Ri Tian and Li Fei Le would not listen to him easily.

Only when they realize that cooperating had benefits, could he use that chance to take over easily!

But now, in the hall, the Gu refinement had reached the crucial period.

After half a day, the golden peanut shell collided with divine travel Gu.

Bam bam bam!

Fang Yuan and Feng Wu Yu's vision turned black as thunder roared in their ears.

"Divine opportunity is unlimited, travel through the lands! Activateeeeeeeeeee!" Fang Yuan screamed, using all his energy to activate divine travel Gu.

Divine travel Gu was an Immortal Gu, how could he, a mortal, activate it easily?

But thankfully, the land spirit helped him secretly, as the immortal essence poured out, the divine travel Gu turned into light speckles as it entered the golden peanut shell.

The qualitative change had begun!

Chapter 393: Group Attack

Xiao Mang looked at the fog in front of him, his gaze deep and solemn.

He relied on his rank five cultivation to gain the commanding position of the righteous path. He organised many assaults, but returned in great failure, suffering a huge loss.

In the fog, countless dogs were hidden, causing every wave of Gu Masters that entered suffer great injuries.

"No matter how big the losses, it will not block my path! Immortal treasure, this is an immortal treasure..." Xiao Mang's eyes shone with brilliance, shouting excitedly in his heart.

"Let's go again, organise the next wave of people." Xiao Mang instructed, but this time, little people joined in.

The painful lesson was right in front of them, despite the great benefits, these righteous Gu Masters started to hesitate, after all they only had one life.

"A bunch of cowards!" Xiao Mang saw them hesitate and scolded in his heart. Time was running short for him, other than this immortal treasure, he also had King Bao Inheritance to obtain.

"If we had an enslavement path Gu Master controlling beast groups, we could use them as cannon fodder, reducing our Gu Master casualties, and regain our morale!" Xiao Mang thought of this point.

In such a situation, the importance of an enslavement path Gu Master was evident.

"Where is Wu clan's Wu Shen Tong? With his help, we would be able to break through the fog and reach the central hall!" Xiao Mang asked.

But the answer he got was disappointing.

Wu Shen Tong had gone missing, even Wu clansmen were trying to find him.

Xiao Mang looked at the demonic faction, and his heart shook: "Not only Wu Shen Tong, even the demonic path's Wu Gui and Zhang San San are not around. Is the Gu Master controlling the dogs in the fog one of these three people?"

Xiao Mang continued guessing as he looked towards the grand hall. However, the fog obstructed his vision, causing him to feel even more irritated at the situation.

"This damn fog, it is so annoying! Too bad Wan Li Xiong Feng is not around, otherwise my clan's divine wind will blow this fog away." Wan clan's Gu Master exclaimed.

"If my clan's old clan leader is here, why would we fear these dogs?" Tie clan's four old-timers snorted.

"Lord Xiao Mang, we are not making any progress, the demonic faction is looking at us like a joke. What do we do?" The righteous path's famous healer Tao Zi came over and asked Xiao Mang.

"These demonic scoundrels!" Xiao Mang looked over at the demonic faction as the irritation in his heart intensified.

"It seems I have to make a move." He snorted, as a brilliant light appeared in his eyes: "All of you, move back."

Everyone heard this and retreated tens of steps away. At once, Xiao Mang's surroundings were vacated, emphasizing his existence.

Xiao Mang stood on the spot, shutting his eyes as his mind entered his aperture, activating his purple crystal primeval essence. The ebb and flow of the primeval sea became greater.

After storing energy for a moment, Xiao Mang's eyes opened, as his primeval sea has turned into a furious tsunami, large amounts of primeval essence entered three Gu worms.

Extreme light Gu!

My will Gu!

Bright spear Gu!

Killer move — My Glorious Spear!!

Xiao Mang's body shone with a piercing white light, the intensity of the light was dense, expanding like a mound.

Xiao Mang's body was bathed in light, he had an impressive appearance, like a descending holy spirit.

He raised a finger towards the fog.

Immediately, the light around him were manipulated, and shot out ferociously.

All of the white sunlight shot out at the same time, forming a 1.8m long and 0.6m thick spear of light.

Sixty percent of the purple crystal essence in his aperture were used up in this one attack.

The spear of light was powerful, penetrating the fog and landed on the mound at breakneck speed.

Bam!

A fierce explosion occurred.

The intense light caused everyone's eyes to be shut tightly, as they took a step back subconsciously.

Even Mo Wu Tian's eyes were squinting into a thin line.

The explosion caused the ground to rumble, as after the light, air current started to spread outwards.

The air currents turned into a strong wind, blowing in all directions causing many people to lose their footing.

Guh! Guh!

In the hall, Fang Yuan and Feng Tian Yu who were refining Gu were interrupted and both vomited a mouthful of blood.

Bai Ning Bing's face was pale, her ears buzzing from the aftermath of the attack.

"This is the strength of a rank five Gu master? Luckily, such a killer move did not hit me directly. If it landed here, my defensive Gu would not even last for a second!"

Bai Ning Bing unavoidably felt great shock.

The killer move of a rank five Gu Master, it was not something the current her could block.

As the whiteness faded from her eyes, she could see that at the location where the light spear landed, thousands of dogs were vaporised. The mound had turned into a crater.

Bai Ning Bing drew in a breath of cold air, with such might, just a few more hits and the dog formation would be ruined.

Her confidence dropped again, but Fang Yuan had instructed her beforehand what she should do in the event she was hit with such a great move.

As Bai Ning Bing manipulated, large numbers of dogs hurried to the crater, as her defenses were raised once again.

"Gasp... so many dogs!" Xiao Mang's heart was heavy, and the righteous and demonic Gu Masters gasped sharply too.

When there was a fog earlier, they could not see clearly, but now that the fog was gone, everyone's vision was clear.

Over ninety thousand dogs, densely packed on the mound, forming an iron bucket defense.

"Lightning symbol dog, chrysanthemum akita dog, hedgedog, steel armor dog, Yin dog..." Some people counted, each dog group had over five thousand and more.

"So many dog kings!" Someone shouted.

No matter how many dogs there were, they could not hide the dog kings due to their disposition. Other than the chrysanthemum akita dogs who were unique, these dog kings were all seated, like a flame in the darkness, extremely eye-catching.

"These dogs and dog kings are not that much of a threat. But there are so many heavy tai, green hua, smoke song, light heng and star heng, these five great mountain dogs!" Some Gu Masters with good vision turned pale.

The outer defense was made up of lighting symbol dogs, chrysanthemum akita dogs, and other ordinary dogs, the inner circle of defense was made up of the five great mountain dogs.

As for the entrance of the hall, the final line of defense, there were several hundred hairy men.

The entire formation was tight and secure, yet not rigid, they all had mobility and flexibility.

"What an iron formation!" Mo Wu Tian's purple eyes shone with light as he felt the situation getting more troublesome.

Even more people directed their gaze to the bronze hall.

The grand yet modest hall had inscriptions and intrinsic designs, giving off an ancient atmosphere.

"That is the bronze hall that contains the immortal treasure?"

"As long as we get past the dogs, we will reach the grand hall!"

"Immortal treasure... immortal treasure... I wonder what mindblowing riches awaits us?"

Everyone's gaze were heated, the goal was in front of them, it made their greed overflow.

"Hehehe, it is time." Mo Wu Tian looked around, sensing the change in the atmosphere.

Greed was like fire burning in everyone's hearts. But the great dog army deterred them, everyone knew that with their own strength, they would never succeed.

This was the basis for cooperation!

"Lord Xiao Mang, let's talk about cooperation." Mo Wu Tian's body was like a black smoke phantom, taking several steps and arriving before Xiao Mang.

Xiao Mang snorted, when he saw the overwhelming dog army, he thought of cooperation.

But he was afraid of getting rejected by Mo Wu Tian and also worried about his own reputation if he approached the demonic faction for cooperation as a righteous rank five cultivator.

Right now, Mo Wu Tian approached him personally, it was music to his ears.

"Hmph." Xiao Mang snorted, his attitude was neither cold nor hot, as he made eye contact with Mo Wu Tian.

Mo Wu Tian immediately understood Xiao Mang's intentions. He was extremely disdainful towards such hypocrisy, but he said: "Then in fifteen minutes, we will attack from the front and back together.

"Mm." Xiao Mang nodded, turning around, no longer looking at him.

Mo Wu Tian sneered, walking back and telling his people: "I just approached Xiao Mang and agitated him, to have a competition with him. Next, we will split into two, attacking together from two sides. We will compete to see who gets to the bronze hall first, whether the righteous faction or us demonic faction wins!"

Xiao Mang announced at the other side: "Demonic scoundrels are greedy and unscrupulous, finding me to cooperate, obviously I rejected them. How can I work with these scum? Fifteen minutes later, they will attack, we will take the chance and attack as they endure some of the pressure for us. Hahaha..."

"Young master Wu Tian rules!""Defeat these righteous hypocrites!" Demonic Gu Masters were riled up as they shouted.

"Lord Xiao Mang is wise!""Let those demonic scoundrels attract the enemy for us!" The righteous Gu Masters were spirited.

"Kill!" Fifteen minutes later, the attack began.

Righteous and demonic were far away, attacking from two directions.

Bai Ning Bing was hidden at some place, relying on her shared vision with the land spirit, using its divine consciousness to scan the battlefield.

Tens of thousand of dogs barked and bared their paws as they charged ahead.

At once, blood flowed and broken limbs flew. All sorts of Gu worms competed, like the dance of fire and ice, lightning exploded and soil was overturned, green vines grew endlessly.

"Kill!" Yi Chong charged ahead, brave and fearless. His body was covered in blue fish scales, the wind blew his fiery red hair into the air.

All around him, there was a light blue spiral wave, together with the black fins that grew on his back, he seemed to have become a fearsome shark in the sea. None of the dogs could block him.

"Immortal treasure... if I can get it and succeed in my mission, I would definitely be able to change my surname to Shang when I return to the clan." Yi Huo's gaze was determined as he turned into the god of fire, attacking even more fiercely than Yi Chong, everywhere he went, there was blazing flames and crying dogs.

Kong Ri Tian laughed heartily, turning into a rain of petals.

Li Xian laughed coldly, while people were not noticing, he used his rank five Gu and concealed his body, secretly moving ahead.

"Let's work together, with me healing there is no worry." Tao Zi shouted as many Gu Masters gathered over.

People were moving and in this great battle, Yan Jun moved slowly and steadily, like a casual traveller.

A strong and brave dog king pounced at him, Yan Hun's expression was unchanging as he turned into a hollow shadow. The dog king jumped over and went straight through the shadow.

The shadow flickered, turning back into Yan Jun's flesh body.

The dog king behind him had engaged the Gu Masters behind already.

The Gu Masters displayed all their abilities, battling with the dog group. The scene was as chaotic as it could be, and Bai Ning Bing could barely cope facing such a huge number of opponents, starting to fluster.

Chapter 394: Success at long last!

"Kill!!!"

"Charge!"

"Damn, why are there so many dogs!!"

Murderous yells, shouts, miserable howls, swearing and dog howls combined to form into a huge clamor that seemed to shake the world.

The battle had not even begun for five minutes; blood had formed into a river and there were corpses everywhere.

Bai Ning Bing hid at some secret place and used all her strength to mobile the dog groups. With the help of the land spirit, she was able to gradually stabilize the situation.

Lightning symbol dog, chrysanthemum akita dog and other common dog beasts suffered the most casualties. Gu Masters had charged halfway through the dog beasts and ran into the formation of the five great mountain dogs, having great casualties.

Heavy tai, green hua, smoke song, light heng and star heng; these five great dogs were very powerful and their circular formation was very reliable. They were like a huge dam that blocked these Gu Masters that were charging like a tide.

At this stage, both righteous and demonic factions suffered heavy casualties.

"Big brother, hold on!" Meng Tu grabbed Jiao Huang's arm; Jiao Huang had suffered heavy injuries from where blood flowed out without stopping.

Jiao Huang borrowed Meng Tu's strength to barely move along with the majority.

Right now, they could not retreat. They could not even stop to rest, if they left the troops, the dog beasts would submerge their tiny bodies.

"Brother, we have made a huge loss this time. We accepted Shang clan's assignment to get Fang Zheng's head. To think we would encounter an immortal treasure, sigh, we gave in to our desire for material benefits and thus fell into such desperate straits." Jiao Huang heaved a sigh.

These two were rank three peak stage Gu Masters, famous assassin group of demonic path. They had even succeeded in assassinating rank four Gu Master Xiao Fu Lu.

They thought of joining Shang clan and thus were prepared to secretly handle Fang Yuan. But the whole way, they did not find any good opportunity.

After charging into the blessed land, they encountered an immortal treasure, and followed with the majority; the result, they sent themselves into danger.

In this chaotic battle, only rank five experts could move unhindered. Rank four peak stage could fight valiantly. Rank four upper stage had to move with the crowd.

Those rank one and two Gu Masters made up the most of the casualties. Rank three Gu Masters also had to rely on luck to survive.

But even so, Gu Masters still charged forward endlessly. The illusionary immortal treasure ignited their most crazed fanatical desires.

They were charging recklessly, all delusional about obtaining the immortal treasure and attaining success in life, becoming an expert.

Only for a certain group of people, at the time of their deaths, they calmed down and regretted endlessly.

Unfortunately, it was too late.

"These people have gone mad, forgetting their own life or death at the enticement of the immortal treasure." Tie Ruo Nan slowed down her footsteps, she was shocked by the state of the battlefield!

Tie clan's four old-timers were surrounding her in a protective formation.

"The way I see it, this probably has to do with that Mo Wu Tian." The head of the Tie clan's four old-timers suddenly said in a soft voice.

"You are saying..." Tie Ruo Nan's gaze flashed.

Far away, Mo Wu Tian was moving forward in the lead, laughing crazily with his purple deep eyes flashing with dazzling light.

He was a soul path Gu Master and had secretly used his Gu to make everyone more fanatical.

"Demonic path members should all be put to death!" Tie Ruo Nan snorted, the killing intent in her heart surging up.

"Young master, Mo Wu Tian is a rank five expert, he is not someone we will be able to fight easily. We need to deal with urgent matters first, our objective is not him." One of the Tie clan's four old-timers persuaded.

Tie Ruo Nan pursed her lips and heavily nodded her head, her gaze firm as iron: "Right, the most important matter right now is still little beast king Fang Zheng!"

"Hahaha, I hadn't thought the enslavement path Gu Master in the dark would only amount to this." Mo Wu Tian laughed wildly, the fierce wind blowing in the battlefield blew his black hair and his demonic flames danced rampantly.

The united charge of righteous and demonic Gu Masters was going on much better than he expected.

Bai Ning Bing was after all a newbie, earlier, she had Fang Yuan's formations and instructions to follow. But the current situation had become more complex with a lot more new changes, it was a lot more than she could take and this in turn were flaws that were clear to Gu Masters at the level of Mo Wu Tian.

Mo Wu Tian's eyes flashed repeatedly with eerie light, at the same time as charging forward, he was doing multiple tasks. He constantly controlled his Gu to attack the dog beasts and also to influence people's minds and create a fanatical atmosphere; at the same time, he was also using his Gu to scout the battlefield.

Enslavement path Gu Masters always had powerful offense and could battle many opponents with just the strength of one person.

But everything in this world was balanced. Enslavement path had a clear disadvantage, besides the huge consumption of resources they needed, their individual strength was weak and were easy to kill.

Mo Wu Tian was searching for Bai Ning Bing's position, as long as he killed Bai Ning Bing, the dog beast formation would fall apart and a large majority of them would even scatter without a fight.

"Found you!" Mo Wu Tian's gaze suddenly concentrated as he discovered the hiding place of Bai Ning Bing.

"Hehehe, give me your life." He laughed and flung his sleeve, his figure turning into a ball of purple demonic fog.

The demonic fog moved through the battlefield at an astonishing speed and in just a few breaths' time was only a thousand steps away from Bai Ning Bing.

"Not good!" Bai Ning Bing discovered the charging fog and her heart sank.

Mo Wu Tian was a rank five Gu Master while Bai Ning Bing was only at rank four, by just this she would be hard pressed to fight him, let alone now when she was doing multiple tasks and controlling the dog beasts.

"Fortunately, I also have my trump cards!" Bai Ning Bing was startled but not panicked as she willed, "Go bite him, Ba Huang."

A hill sized enormous dog emperor heard the command and with one leap, flew over a hundred feet and smashed into Mo Wu Tian.

Woof!

Ba Huang barked loudly, its bark was like a bolt from the blue, suppressing the whole battlefield and turning it silent. Following the bark, the dog beasts flared up with high morale; the casualties among the Gu Masters became more intense.

Dog emperor!

Its physique was majestic with its whole body covered with yellow sleek fur. It had a head like that of a lion with thick mane around its neck that was dazzling like a sun.

This was an emperor among the beasts and was not something that could be looked down upon. Once it used the wild Gu on it, it could contend against rank five Gu Masters!

"Damn it." Mo Wu Tian cursed when he was stopped by Ba Huang.

Bai Ning Bing let out a breath of relief, but right at this time, a dazzling silver light shot through the battlefield and appeared in front of her instantly.

"Hehehe. Demonic path junior, take a good look at me." The silver light turned into a human figure, rank five righteous path expert Xiao Mang!

"Ying Ming!" Bai Ning Bing withstood the pressure and commanded in her mind, sending out the second dog emperor.

This second dog emperor was the size of a normal dog beast. There were gorgeous patterns on its snowy white skin like pink cherry blossoms.

Withstanding Xiao Mang's intense pressure, the wild Gu on the dog emperor activated and created clouds below Ying Ming's feet, allowing it to fly.

"Just a mere wild dog... eh, it is actually a dog emperor!" Xiao Mang scoffed but after few exchanges of lightning fast attacks and defending, he withdrew his contempt and fought cautiously.

Bai Ning Bing's expression was gloomy.

Although the two rank five experts were blocked, this situation was only temporary.

Humans were the spirit of all living beings; human's wisdom was superior to beasts. Sooner or later, Mo Wu Tian and Xiao Mang would understand the dog emperors' trump cards and then could make their moves with ease, even bypassing them to directly kill Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing looked around the battlefield, the other Gu Masters were still in the middle of the battlefield fighting and charging forward; they were temporarily of no threat.

Bai Ning Bing let out a breath of relief and turned her gaze towards the bronze hall.

"There is not much time..." Her blue eyes narrowed, letting out a clear and cold radiance.

Inside the bronze hall, Fang Yuan took large mouthfuls of air, gasping heavily. Meanwhile, Feng Tian Yu was already lying on the ground, unconscious.

Blood flowed out of Fang Yuan's seven orifices, but he did not care; a pair of bright eyes stared at front.

A Gu was letting out brilliant light as it floated it in the air.

It did not have a concrete shape; occasionally, it was like a colorful cloud and occasionally it was like a whirlpool of light.

"Success!" Fang Yuan was filled with joy, he had already succeeded in refining divine travel Gu.

Now only one step remained and he could obtain second aperture Gu!

"You succeeded, you really succeeded!" The land spirit appeared beside Fang Yuan. It was extremely weak but its eyes glowed with light, full of happiness at the success.

"You are worthy of being a future Gu Immortal, you could really refine divine travel Gu, amazing! It was indeed a correct choice to entrust this task to you. Now, the most difficult step has passed; it is smooth sailing ahead! Next, you need to use third watch Gu and it will be a success without the least bit of difficulty."

The land spirit heaved a long sigh, its sigh full of emotions.

"Thousands of years of effort has finally succeeded today. The recipe indeed works, I am truly happy. But such a pity... that I can't see the second aperture Gu in the end..."

After it finished speaking, the land spirit Ba Gui's body gradually turned fainter and fainter till it completely disappeared.

It was dead.

The immortal essence in the bronze cauldron was almost finished with only a thin trace remaining.

The blessed land had already collapsed for the most part and was at the brink of extinction.

The aged Ba Gui had been helping Fang Yuan in refining Gu and also helping Bai Ning Bing to guard; it finally could not endure such pressure and completely withered away.

But compared to previous life where it had died a death of desperation under many Gu Masters' attacks, it was much more blessed during this life and could even be said to have had a proper death.

Ba Gui's death meant the immortal essence could not be used anymore.

However, Fang Yuan was not nervous.

For the next final step, the immortal essence could be replaced with large amounts of primeval stones.

Even if Ba Gui was alive, that trace of immortal essence in the bronze cauldron was required to support the operation of the blessed land and simply could not be used to refine Gu.

"The difficulty of this Immortal Gu refinement exceeds Spring Autumn Cicada. Just now, that huge shock to the main hall almost caused all the efforts to be a waste, and in case the Gu refinement had failed, with just my mortal body, I will definitely die from the backlash without even having time to activate Spring Autumn Cicada."

"Moreover, this most crucial step had an extreme demand on mind and a mortal simply cannot endure it. Fortunately, I chose to enslave Feng Tian Yu just to be safe, otherwise this step could never have been completed."

In his previous life, Fang Yuan was already a Gu Immortal when he refined Spring Autumn Cicada. Now this time, he was refining Immortal Gu with the qualifications of a mortal and he should not have had any chance of success.

However, first, the mysterious Gu Immortal had racked his brain and used up all his life to research and perfect this recipe.

Second, the recipe used the Immortal Gu divine travel which greatly reduced the absurd difficulty.

And finally, it was not done by Fang Yuan alone, he had the help of land spirit and also refinement path grandmaster Feng Tian Yu.

All these helped Fang Yuan to complete the most difficult and dangerous step.

"Next I have to use third watch Gu, this is much more simple. Right, I wonder how the situation outside is." Fang Yuan calmed his mind and then started hearing the shouts and commotion outside the main hall.

"Fang Yuan, be careful. Someone broke through the dog formation, a rank four Gu Master is coming towards you!" Right at this time, Bai Ning Bing's warning arrived.

"Hmm." Fang Yuan's expression was heavy as he slowly stood up.

Chapter 395: Bai Ning Bing?

Currently, the land spirit was dead and Fang Yuan was unable to see the scene outside the hall. However, with his previous life memories, he could guess one or two things without looking at the situation.

"There are only two rank five experts in the blessed land; Xiao Mang and Mo Wu Tian, they will be held back by the two dog emperors for some time. There are a lot of rank four Gu Masters, but at this time, there is only one who can charge to this place. That is the young clan leader of Yan clan, Yan Jun. He obtained the ancient phantom path inheritance and is specialized in hiding and attacking. It should not be a problem for him to charge through the dog beast formation."

Fang Yuan pondered, it was the truth as well.

Phantom path had once flourished in the ancient times; its concept was to be footloose and carefree, invincibility through dodging. As long as one could evade every attack, that was a form of 'invincibility'.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, phantom path Yan Jun had shown great brilliance at the battle of Yi Tian mountain, challenging the demonic path Gu Masters and causing them to suffer severe losses. That was until Mo Wu Tian showed up and beat him into retreating.

"This blessed land doesn't have strong defense! The central area is so important but there is only a bronze hall built there, although it can be used to store things, its defense is really thin; the whole thing is impressive looking but useless! If it was like the Hu Immortal blessed land with Dang Hun mountain as defense, it would simply be like a heavenly moat and even Gu Immortals would have a headache facing it. Even my own blessed land that had the structure of a blood sea was much better than this hall." Fang Yuan inwardly felt resentment. He walked over to Feng Tian Yu and kicked him awake.

"Get up!" Fang Yuan said in a cold voice.

Feng Tian Yu had worked hard and made great contributions, if it were not for him bearing most of the pressure, Fang Yuan might not have succeeded in refining to this stage.

"Ugh, mas... master..." He woke up with bloodshot eyes, his hair was scraggy like weed and his face was pale-white; his body was swaying as he greeted Fang Yuan.

"Go out of the main hall and block the rank four phantom path Gu Master. Even if you have to sacrifice your life." Fang Yuan ruthlessly commanded.

"Yes, subordinate will do his best!" Feng Tian Yu bit his lips and walked out.

His primeval essence was almost completely consumed and he did not have enough fighting strength left. Moreover, as a refinement path grandmaster, he was not specialized in intense battle. It was almost guaranteed that he would not return alive from this mission.

However, the current Fang Yuan still needed to continue with the final step, he did not have any other force remaining, thus he could only send Feng Tian Yu.

"Second aperture Gu is the top priority. Sacrificing a refinement path grandmaster for it is nothing much." Fang Yuan sat down in a cross-legged position and looked at the continuously changing gorgeous light in the air.

At this step, second aperture Gu was already mostly completely and was interchanging between real and surreal, form and formless. It was unable to be moved and also could only exist for six hours.

After six hours, if the refinement has still not been carried out, the light would disappear and all the previous effort would be wasted.

"There is no turning back now, as long as I finish this final step, I will obtain second aperture Gu! It is just that..."

Fang Yuan subconsciously stroked his abdomen with a grave expression.

In the blessed land, time flew three times faster than the outside world; Spring Autumn Cicada was recovering extremely fast and bringing great pressure to the aperture.

Even though Fang Yuan's aperture was rank four upper stage, it could not endure this pressure and there were indications of tiny cracks on the aperture surface.

Next, he would have to still use two third watch Gu, and with the effects overlaid, the time flow would be nine times faster.

At that time, could his aperture endure the pressure?

Fang Yuan was not someone who would recklessly take risks and had already meticulously planned before beginning the Gu refinement.

He had a huge chance of winning this gamble. As long as he got the second aperture and promptly left the blessed land, he would be able to have few months of respite.

He naturally had some backup plans at that time.

"Third watch Gu, go." He calmed down his mind and gathered his concentration to begin the final step.

Under the effect of third watch Gu, that light ball immediately started changing rapidly, the light rays were dazzling and gave off a mysterious aura that was hard to describe in words.

"Divine travel Gu broadens the space and third watch Gu condenses the time. This is the using the laws of both space and time, this truly is the way of Gu passed down from the immemorial era..."

Genuine knowledge comes from practice and Fang Yuan gained some comprehension from this.

Time flew, the first third watch Gu's effect was nearing its end. The light ball faintly solidified, giving off the shape of the final product.

The shouts from outside the main hall became louder, but whether it were Mo Wu Tian, Xiao Mang, or Yan Jun and so on, no one had yet to charge inside.

"Good, next it is the second third watch Gu..." Looking at the refinement finally about to succeed, even Fang Yuan started feeling excited.

However, right at this time!

Bai Ning Bing's voice came: "Fang Yuan, be careful. Tie Ruo Nan has broken the defense line and is coming towards you!"

Fang Yuan's expression changed.

At this moment, his whole attention was concentrated on the refinement and he could not pull out from it, how could he face the enemy? With Feng Tian Yu already being sent out, he did not have any defensive force.

What to do?

"Bai Ning Bing, what the hell are you doing! Are you still not going to come to guard me? I can't move now, if I die, you will also die under the powers of poison vow Gu!" Fang Yuan transmitted his furious voice.

He was extremely helpless and could only call Bai Ning Bing over.

Without Bai Ning Bing to take control, the dog groups outside would definitely be a group of leaderless army and there would be huge chaos. And soon, the group of heroes could kill their way through.

However, Fang Yuan could not care about it!

Right now, he was like a fish on the chopping board, anyone could slaughter him with him not having even a bit of retaliation power. If someone did not protect him, he would be easily killed by Tie Ruo Nan.

Fortunately, the Gu refinement was already at its final stage and now only the second third watch Gu had to be used.

Fang Yuan only hoped for more time.

As long as he made every second count and finished the refinement, with the many rank four and rank five movement Gu on him, he could break out of the siege and escape alive.

As for Bai Ning Bing?

Hehe, she is suitable to block the incoming enemies, her use would be maximised. As for what her ending would be, it was not something Fang Yuan could consider at the moment.

Bam!

The hall's great door was pushed open violently.

Tie Ruo Nan walked inside and saw the scene in the hall; she was first dazed before immediately reacting with both shock and happiness: "Little beast king, today is the day I shall take your head!"

She went in for the kill before she even finished speaking. With a wave of her hand, countless golden needles flew out.

"Bai Ning Bing!" The concentrated aura of death came pouncing on him and Fang Yuan could not help shouting again.

Whoosh!

Cold wind blew and ice started spreading, forming into an ice wall that blocked all the golden needles.

Next moment, Bai Ning Bing also appeared at the entrance of the main hall.

However, her state was clearly not good, she was covered in blood and injuries filled her body. The most severe injury was on her back, a cut that spread from her shoulder to her sacrum, it was so deep that even her bones could be seen.

There were bits of green leaves sticking on her clothes, her silver hair was scorched, and her whole left arm was purple, she was clearly poisoned.

"Quick, block her!" Fang Yuan shouted, "I only need a little time."

"You still have the leisure to say such nonsense, just make the most of this time to refine the Gu!" Bai Ning Bing gritted her teeth and cursed before starting to fight Tie Ruo Nan.

Tie Ruo Nan laughed coldly, her golden needles flew like lightning with extremely terrifying offensive power.

Bai Ning Bing clenched her teeth, she had suffered heavy injuries and did not even have ten percent of her original strength; she soon fell into disadvantage.

Several moves later, Bai Ning Bing's injuries intensified; her ankle sprained and her body wavered, Tie Ruo Nan keenly grabbed this chance to move in for a fierce attack.

Bai Ning Bing was again inflicted with heavy injuries and fell down to the ground.

"I shall kill you first!" An imprint that was on Tie Ruo Nan's forehead flashed and turned into solid, forming a golden flying dagger that shot out fiercely.

Whoosh!

The golden flying dagger cut through the air towards Bai Ning Bing's neck, but it missed by just a hairline gap and pierced into the bronze tile.

Bai Ning Bing rolled quickly and evaded the fatal attack, shouting: "How long do you still need?"

Fang Yuan's heart was thumping loudly as he gritted his teeth and shouted: "Just a little bit, hold on even if you die!!"

"If I die, you won't be able to live either..." Bai Ning Bing cursed but was interrupted by Tie Ruo Nan's attack.

Tie Ruo Nan's offense came in wave after wave, Bai Ning Bing was sent into retreat bit by bit and could only make dodging his priority, struggling in between the thin line of life and death.

Several more moves later, Bai Ning Bing gasped roughly: "I can't continue! Fang Yuan, I am going to self-destruct!"

"Your aptitude has already returned to a hundred percent?" Fang Yuan was startled.

"What do you think!" Bai Ning Bing cursed.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, Bai Ning Bing changing back into northern dark soul ice physique was a definite thing. But he had not expected it to be this quick!

According to his calculation, despite the time flowing three times faster in the blessed land, it should have only have been after several more months.

Fang Yuan was in a critical juncture of the refinement process and was unable to distract his mind to consider too much.

The self-destruction of a ten extreme physique possessed extreme might and even rank five Gu Masters would have to take evasive actions.

Once Bai Ning Bing self-destructed, there would be an extreme change in the whole battle situation.

"Try to hold on, unless you can't control it anymore, don't..." Fang Yuan shouted. He was refining the Gu with his back facing the entrance and could not see the concrete situation of the fight between Tie Ruo Nan and Bai Ning Bing.

The response he received, however, was Bai Ning Bing's deep sigh —

"It's too late."

The next moment, Fang Yuan felt the cold aura spread everywhere in the main hall and the temperature decreased rapidly.

Crack...

There were continuous sounds of ice forming.

"What Gu is this?" Tie Ruo Nan's cry of surprise also reached Fang Yuan's ears.

Fang Yuan turned his head with difficulty to look and saw the main hall already becoming a world of ice and snow. Bai Ning Bing was floating high up in the air, her whole body turning into ice crystal, similar to the situation when she had self-destructed back at Qing Mao mountain.

The cold wind blustered and glaciers rose, crushing towards Tie Ruo Nan with vast and majestic force.

Tie Ruo Nan had a fierce expression as she quickly retreated towards outside.

However, the door of the main hall was already condensed into ice, she was like a turtle trapped in a jar and was surrounded by the icy layers.

"Is this the legendary northern dark ice soul physique?" Tie Ruo Nan cried out in surprise. But it was already too late, she was sealed within the ice like an insect in an amber.

The ice, however, did not stop spreading and was spreading towards Fang Yuan.

"Bai Ning Bing? Bai Ning Bing!" Fang Yuan worriedly shouted, but there was no response from Bai Ning Bing.

Her body had almost become one with ice and her whole face had started turning indistinct. Her crystal like eyes no longer shone and had thoroughly dimmed.

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan's brain was hurting from the anxiety, the ice had already reached his body, he could only use Yang Gu.

Yang Gu flew out and landed on Bai Ning Bing's body, immediately Yang aura and the icy coldness formed into a whirlpool of primeval essence; the scene back at Qing Mao mountain many years ago appeared once again!

Ice stopped spreading but this distraction almost caused the Gu refinement to fail.

Fang Yuan's heart thumped loudly in shock and he immediately concentrated all his attention without being concerned about the situation behind him.

Under his efforts and control, the light clouds finally condensed into second aperture Gu!

"Immortal Gu! I finally succeeded!!" Right now, Fang Yuan's heart was exploding with joy.

All his efforts and all the risks he took had created a very satisfactory outcome!

Pew!

Right at this time, a sharp ice blade pierced through Fang Yuan's heart, piercing from behind him and coming out of his chest.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to needle-size and he looked behind with difficulty —

"Bai Ning Bing? You!"

"Fang Yuan, to think there would be a day where you fall into a trap!" Tie Ruo Nan slowly walked over, her gaze filled with hatred.

Chapter 396: Bai Ning Bing!

The bronze hall was deathly silent.

Time seemed to have frozen as the atmosphere became very heavy.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on the ground with the rank six second aperture Gu floating in front of him.

Immortal Gu refinement had succeeded, but Fang Yuan's attention was not at this immortal Gu.

He turned his head with difficulty and gazed at Bai Ning Bing, his eyes revealing his deep doubts.

Bai Ning Bing who had already recovered his male body was holding an ice blade and was expressionlessly standing behind him.

Tie Ruo Nan slowly walked over and fixed her gaze at Fang Yuan, her expression showing both grief and joy: "Fang Yuan, you had never in your wildest imagination, expect this day to occur right?"

Fang Yuan seemed like he did not hear anything and kept on looking at Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Yuan. With the recovery of his male body, his height had increased, he was wearing a snow white robe, his silver hair was floating in the air and his eyes shone with deep coldness.

He was like a glacier, extremely cold.

"You didn't expect it, right? That you would finally be defeated by me." Bai Ning Bing indifferently smiled while looking at Fang Yuan, "Since my resurrection back on Qing Mao mountain, I had been pondering on how to recover my male body."

"In the days spent with you, I was firmly controlled by you as a chess piece that could be moved at your will. You are not the strongest enemy in my life, but I have to admit that you are absolutely the most terrifying one."

"Fang Yuan, you are someone with innate talent for scheming, and with your vicious methods, you are a very formidable person. But I, Bai Ning Bing, am also not an ordinary character, how could I become someone's subordinate? Hmph! The more you controlled me and the more you exploited me, the more I thought of ways to escape, to make a comeback and counterattack!"

"But the Yang Gu was with you and you could cause it to self-destruct with just a thought. Thus, I did not act recklessly but racked my brains to think of countermeasures until one day, I got a superb inspiration and thought of a way."

"Actually, the scene of you voluntarily hand over the Gu had already happened once on Qing Mao mountain. Hehe, right, that is to repeat the scene back on Qing Mao mountain. The time of my self-destruction will be the time you use the Yang Gu."

"With this as the start, I began to plot secretly." The corner of Bai Ning Bing's lips slowly spread into a smile, "I would self-destruct, but it would naturally not be actual self-destruction since there was a chance you might not use Yang Gu. So, I chose..."

"Ice crystal Gu." Fang Yuan's expression was dim as water.

Back at Shang clan city, Bai Ning Bing chose ice path. Among the ice path, there were three transformation type Gu; frost demon Gu, snow fairy Gu and ice crystal Gu. Wei Yang had strongly recommended Bai Ning Bing to choose snow fairy Gu.

Snow fairy Gu was suitable for female Gu Masters while ice crystal Gu was suitable for males.

Bai Ning Bing, however, chose ice crystal Gu as a female which had caused Wei Yang to feel great regret.

"Hehe, you finally get it." Bai Ning Bing laughed, "That's right, I originally chose ice crystal Gu not because I was peeved but because snow fairy Gu changed the body to a snow fairy with clear appearance that could not be hidden. However, if I turn into ice crystal and use ice explosion Gu with it, it could form a majestic scene that is extremely similar to the self-destruction of northern dark ice soul physique. You have seen it just now, didn't it deceive you?"

"Hmph, if I was not concentrating on refining Gu, I would definitely discover the peculiarity, how could you have succeeded so easily then?" Fang Yuan scoffed.

Bai Ning Bing, however, nodded her head with a serious expression: "Right. You are very meticulous, observing everything to the finest details. When I thought of this method, I also felt it would be strange and there would be a great chance of failure. In fact, there was a change in circumstances that made me almost give up this plan."

The change Bai Ning Bing spoke of was none other than poison vow Gu.

" A great man knows when to yield and when not, my objective was to rely on the poison vow to accomplish my goal. So what if I would be used for some time?" Bai Ning Bing's eyes turned vague as he recalled, "However, the developments after that made me realize that poison vow Gu was not reliable."

"The poison vow between you and Shang Ya Zi, despite there being a very ingenious flaw, I felt that you were too confident. And I had also secretly investigated the contract with Bai clan, the rumors however were still leaked out, making me feel even more uncertain. One thing that I have learned about you is that you make the best preparations for everything, calculating even the worst outcomes. Thus, I could not help but consider this situation — what if you were not restricted by poison vow Gu, what would I do then?"

"I knew that if that was the case, I had already gotten into a desperate situation. I was restricted by the poison vow while you were not, I would become your chess piece which you could use or kill with no way for me to retaliate. Just relying on my own power, I would never be able to escape this predicament, but there was one person who could help me at Shang clan city."

"Speaking of this person, I still need to thank you for the introduction." Bai Ning Bing smiled mockingly.

He thought of the first meeting with Doctor Su Shou.

It was during the banquet organized by Shang Yan Fei. As thanks to Fang and Bai for escorting Shang Xin Ci to Shang clan city, Shang Yan Fei invited Doctor Su Shou to treat Fang Yuan's disfigured face.

And to make Bai Ning Bing give up, Fang Yuan intentionally asked her to go together.

After Bai Ning Bing met Doctor Su Shou with her real appearance, Doctor Su Shou's attitude immediately changed into extreme warmth and compassion.

Doctor Su Shou was one of the four great doctors of Southern Border and had a peculiarity of being attracted to appearance. She was extremely fond of handsome men and beautiful women, as long as their appearance was extraordinary, she would give treatment for free. If the appearance was ugly, she would loathe them and would not treat them even if they gave more money.

Bai Ning Bing asked her about the transformation of Yin and Yang, and with the reply he got, he was even more aware of how important the Yang Gu in Fang Yuan's possession was.

But at the same time, Bai Ning Bing also got to know Doctor Su Shou. Before leaving, Doctor Su Shou had made a serious promise that no matter what problems he faced, he could go find her.

"Cough cough." Fang Yuan coughed out a mouthful of blood, the ice blade had pierce through his heart, but with the help of healing Gu, he was able to hang on to life.

However, the chilly aura of the ice blade was slowing down the speed of his blood flow, and the numbness the cold brought was spreading to his whole body.

Right now, however, these injuries were minor details: "The person you are speaking, is it Doctor Su Shou?"

"Hehehe, you are Fang Yuan indeed, you are right." Bai Ning Bing praised.

"That b*tch!" Fang Yuan cursed but also had new doubts, "But didn't you guys only meet once? Wait... there was also the second time!"

Fang Yuan suddenly recalled something while talking.

At Shang clan city, Bai Ning Bing and Doctor Su Shou had met for a second time!

That time was when Bai Ning Bing lost to Yan Tu by just a little and suffered heavy injuries while also losing her vital Gu. She went to Doctor Su Shou's place to receive treatment and to recuperate.

"Don't tell me?!" Fang Yuan seemed to have thought of something and his gaze immediately turned to Bai Ning Bing as if it was the first time he was seeing this cold and handsome young man.

Bai Ning Bing smiled, his blue eyes shining eerily: "It seems you have guessed it. That's right, I intentionally lost to Yan Tu. Losing a vital Gu is nothing, exchanging it for a chance to evade your suspicions, isn't it a profitable transaction? At that time, I decided to gamble."

Bai Ning Bing went to Doctor Su Shou's place and relying just on his intuition, he decided to take a risk — he told the truth honestly to Doctor Su Shou.

Doctor Su Shou sympathized with his experience and did her best to free him from Fang Yuan's demonic claws.

Bai Ning Bing asked her if there was a way to dispel poison vow.

Doctor Su Shou replied that she could not dispel poison vow, but there was a way which could get rid of poison vow's binding.

She recalled from her memories: Once, when she was young and ignorant, she was deceived by her sect's junior brother into using poison vow Gu to make an oath saying they would never abandon each other. Later, she used this method to get rid of the poison vow.

Bai Ning Bing asked: "What is it?"

Doctor Su Shou's gaze turned grave and said —'To live, one must die.'

Once the poison vow activated, it would cause the death of the vow maker. Doctor Su Shou was a healing Gu Master and her solution was to intentionally let the poison vow activate and cause the Gu Master's death, the poison would be removed and then revive the Gu Master.

"This method is a forceful removal. The absolute majority of healing Gu Masters cannot do it even if they thought of it. I am able to barely accomplish it because of the unique legacy from my teacher. But even so, this has a one-in-three chance of failure. If it fails, it will mean death. Think it through." Doctor Su Shou gave a final warning.

Bai Ning Bing decided on the spot to use this method.

With Doctor Su Shou's help, he got rid of the poison vow fortunately.

Without the poison vow's binding, Bai Ning Bing got in touch with Tie clan and Tie Ruo Nan was able to learn the truth.

The truth that person in front of her was Fang Yuan and not Fang Zheng.

At the same time, she also understood the event that occured on Qing Mao mountain.

To deal with Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing and Tie Ruo Nan launched a secret cooperation.

"We had used iron cabinet Gu and qi flow Gu around an area and planned to create the scene of the self-destruction. Unfortunately, you refused to rescue her. I could only gather a group and hurry to San Cha mountain to make new plans." Tie Ruo Nan spoke.

The scene of Bai Ning Bing being trapped for so many days by Tie clan's four old-timers looked like Tie clan's reprisal because of Bai Ning Bing killing a Tie clan's Gu Master in the inheritance, but in truth, it was all a scheme to deal with Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan fought one against seven and slaughtered Tie Ruo Nan's group which caused Tie Mu Bai to take the stage.

Tie Ruo Nan received Tie Mu Bai's teachings, cultivating and patiently waiting for news from Bai Ning Bing. This was also the reason why she did not take the initiative to look for Fang Yuan although she had extreme hatred towards him.

However, Fang Yuan made an impressive move that shook everybody; he took control of the whole situation after entering three kings inheritance.

Tie Mu Bai's death caused Bai Ning Bing to keep silent and conceal himself even deeper. Using Fang Yuan's trust, he controlled the dog beasts.

With the death of the land spirit, he was unable to suppress the situation anymore and the pressure on him increased. However at the same time, he felt his whole body relaxed as he was free from the land spirit's surveillance.

He was still not at ease though, thus he intentionally gave way for Yan Jun to probe Fang Yuan.

Sure enough like he expected, Feng Tian Yu was sent out, this proved the land spirit had truly died.

Bai Ning Bing was inwardly happy and again maneuvered the situation to make a way in for Tie Ruo Nan and Tie clan's four old-timers.

The reason Tie Ruo Nan came to the main hall by herself was also because of this.

"Fang Yuan, I advise you to obediently surrender. Outside, my Tie clan's enslavement path grandmaster Tie Bai Qi is controlling the dog beasts and obstructing the group of experts. Outside the main hall, there are Tie clan's four old-timers who are using iron cabinet Gu and qi flow Gu to confine the space so that no one can infiltrate here. Surrendering is your only way out."

Tie Ruo Nan walked over and held the second aperture Gu in her hand while pronouncing Fang Yuan's fate.

Fang Yuan was silent.

Chapter 397: The battle has just begun

"There are truly are uncountable geniuses in this world..." After being solemn for a while, Fang Yuan raised his head and sighed.

"Bai Ning Bing, what a Bai Ning Bing... hehehe, I underestimated you, and fell victim to your schemes. It was a beautiful victory, your plan was flawless, while I was careless and overconfident, only thinking about the Immortal Gu, allowing you to succeed, it was my mistake!"

"I'm flattered. The reason I could plot against you was due to the perfect time, place and opportunity. If I were the one who had to refine an Immortal Gu while scheming against both the righteous and demonic factions, I would definitely have done worse than you." Bai Ning Bing answered seriously: "But now at this point, winner takes all and the loser loses everything, I hope you would stop your pointless struggle."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan sneered: "The reason you have not killed me yet is because of the Immortal Gu, you want to know its effects and also the Immortal Gu recipe in my head."

Now that the land spirit was dead, the blessed land was on the brink of destruction, there were loopholes everywhere and without the heavenly power to suppress them, Gu Masters could use their Gu freely.

That is to say, Fang Yuan just had to think about it, and all his Gu would self-detonate, Bai Ning Bing and Tie Ruo Nan had no way to stop him.

"Tie Ruo Nan, Tie Mu Bai and the others died in my hands, you have to take this Immortal Gu back to redeem yourself, otherwise you will lose your young master position." Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly.

Tie Ruo Nan was expressionless, answering frankly: "That's right, Immortal Gu are unique, they are extremely important, when I bring it back it will be an unprecedented merit, I would receive the Tie clan Gu Immortals' nurturing and reward. As for the recipe to refine Immortal Gu, right now only you know about it, if I can contribute it to the clan, I would immediately become Tie clan young clan leader."

"When I ascend to the position of clan leader, I will be like Lord Tie Mu Bai, upholding justice and order. After all these things, I have learnt: To uphold justice, one needs to have great strength as well as a strong force! Only in this way can I repay Lord Tie Mu Bai's teachings, and allow him to feel at peace in the afterlife."

Saying so, Tie Ruo Nan thought about the Tie clansmen who died in Fang Yuan's hands, her eyes turning red as she felt intense fury and hatred, and also the great satisfaction of getting her revenge.

She breathed in deeply, staring sharply at Fang Yuan: "As for you, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, I will not kill you. You were able to refine an Immortal Gu using a mortal body, such refinement talent is truly spectacular. As long as you surrender, I will send you into the Tie clan Demon Suppression Tower to undergo reform. In the future, when you turn over a new leaf, and leave the tower, you will work for Tie clan, and contribute to the righteous path, repaying for your sins, this is the best outcome."

"Demon Suppression Tower..." Fang Yuan squinted: "You make it sound really nice! Hehehe, you want the Immortal Gu? Sure, let's make a transaction."

Fang Yuan talked about the details of the transaction as he focused on the movements outside the hall.

He was stalling for time.

In this situation, it may seem like a dead end but he still had one final resort.

Because of refining Gu, Fang Yuan's mind is tired and he had little primeval essence left. His rank four all-out effort Gu was not refined yet, and many beast phantoms were used up in the Gu refinement process.

He could not force it now, Fang Yuan was not in the best condition, while Bai Ning Bing and Tie Ruo Nan came prepared. Furthermore, there are the four Tie clan old-timers outside as well as Tie Bai Qi who manipulates dog groups.

Spring Autumn Cicada was indeed the best chance he had, but it carried an enormous risk, and carried the danger of dying. Unless he had no other options, Fang Yuan did not want to use it yet.

"My true opportunity lies in the experts waiting outside the hall. With just the dog group and Tie clan's four old-timers, they cannot block them all forever. As long as they fight their way in here, the situation would be completely overturned.

Fate worked in mysterious ways, not long ago, Fang Yuan was using all his methods to block the experts outside, but now he could not wish more for them to fight their way into the hall.

...

"This accursed Tie clan, the mastermind is them all along!"

"TIe clan's old clan leader Tie Mu Bai came personally, what attracted him? We should've guessed..."

"Tie clan is a super clan, but don't think of devouring this alone, the immortal treasure belongs to all of us!"

In the intense battlefield, everyone was excited.

Looking at the bronze hall, many Gu Masters' eyes were burning with passion.

The purple colored light barrier covered the entire bronze hall. Tie clan's four old-timers were at all four directions, guarding it securely.

As for Tie Bai Qi, he was standing at the door of the hall, looking down at all the Gu Masters as he manipulated the dog group.

He was an old man, his head was full of white hair, and he had a third eye on his forehead, shining brightly. He was a rank five enslavement path Gu Master, a Tie clan elder, and was once Tie Mu Bai's capable general. Under Tie Mu Bai's orders, he came out of cultivation, coming to the faraway San Cha mountain.

Right now, Tie Bai Qi was smiling as he looked at the battlefield.

The dog group was under his command, unleashing several times the fighting strength they had compared to before. Tie Bai Qi did not mind the losses, blocking all the experts outside.

"This old fool is really irritating." Mo Wu Tian's hair was flying in the air as he breathed roughly.

Before him, dog emperor Ba Huang was bathed in blood, in a condition worse than Mo Wu Tian. But soon, the healing Gu on it worked, and under the milky-white colored light, it began to heal rapidly.

Mo Wu Tian tried to attack while there was a chance, but a group of green hua dogs charged in.

"This again!" Mo Wu Tian gritted his teeth, forced to kill this group of reinforcements.

While it had the chance, Ba Huang managed to heal most of its injuries and became revitalized again.

Compared to the time Bai Ning Bing sent out the dog emperor and did not have the energy to control it, Tie Bai Qi had a much easier time. He manipulated the entire battlefield, and controlled the situation, showing the strength of the enslavement path fully.

On the other hand, Xiao Mang was also receiving great attention from Tie Bai Qi.

"This won't do, the immortal treasure is going to be taken by Tie clan!" Xiao Mang was anxious and hateful, but dog emperor Ying Ming was blocking his path, not allowing him to pass through.

"Bastard, you forced me!!" Xiao Mang growled, flying into the sky.

The sky already had one huge hole, tens of kilometers in diameter, as the outside showed the sky of the main world, full of clouds and was a bright sunny day.

Xiao Mang flew out of the hole, raising his hands.

Rank four, gather light Gu.

Large amounts of sunlight gathered on his palms, the light turned into a ball, flawless and huge; Xiao Mang was like an ant carrying a huge rice bowl.

Rank five, extreme light Gu.

The glorious light of the immemorial era, gathered into the ball, and caused a qualitative change, as the entire ball was infected with the glory of the immemorial times!

Rank five, river under the sun Gu.

The light ball exploded, turning into an overwhelming water of light, each drop was like a fragment of the sun, extremely bright and dazzling.

Killer move — Torrential Light Stream! [1]

The river of light rolled and crashed as it poured down on the blessed land from the hole.

The light was blinding, and the waves were fierce, it turned the entire battlefield white, and everyone closed their eyes, unable to resist such a strong light.

"Oh no!" Tie Bai Qi tried to stop it, but the light river's formation was already complete, he could only reduce its impact by a little.

The grand light river was like a waterfall, crashing on the purple barrier.

The barrier only lasted for a moment before shattering, as the four old-timers who sustained the barrier spurted out mouthfuls of blood, gravely injured.

The light river broke the barrier and was weakened, but it continued on its way into the bronze hall.

The hall was immediately broken through, and the waterfall swept towards Fang, Bai, and Tie.

Bai Ning Bing and Tie Ruo Nan's pupils shrunk as they subconsciously tried to dodge.

Fang Yuan who was waiting for an opportunity, immediately reacted and activated his primeval essence.

Warp Gu!

He activated this rank five movement Gu.

This Gu was something he got from killing Chou Jiu the killer ghost doctor.

With a swoosh, Fang Yuan vanished on the spot.

The light river crashed on the floor, creating a huge hole that was about two meters deep.

Tie and Bai dodged in time, standing at the edge of the huge hole, extremely calm.

"He escaped indeed, hehehe. It seems he used warp Gu. I think this Gu came from killer ghost doctor." Tie Ruo Nan analyzed.

"We're letting him escape?" Bai Ning Bing looked at Tie Ruo Nan.

"You forgot about fixed star Gu? Don't worry, even if he escapes to the end of the world, Tie clan's four old-timers would be able to arrest him. Let me roam around for now and expend his primeval essence and energy. It saves us some trouble." Tie Ruo Nan smiled lightly, her tone showing a confident attitude towards grasping the situation.

After so many trials and difficulties, she had grown up a lot.

Guh!

Intense pain assaulted him as Fang Yuan vomited a mouthful of blood, feeling extremely dizzy. A sense of disgust almost caused him to fall face flat on the ground, feeling like his intestines were all jumbled up.

Warp Gu was a space path Gu, tearing through space and transporting the Gu Master's body. The strong effect carried an equally intense backlash.

Gu Masters who constantly use warp Gu would have their tendons entangled, their blood would flow backwards, and their joints would be dislocated. On the outside, the Gu Master would get uglier and uglier, no matter how nice he looked originally, he would turn hideous.

To use the warp Gu, one had to use other Gu worms to modify his own body. But to Fang Yuan, he no longer cared.

"Second aperture Gu will be kept safe by you guys for now. I will return this hatred a million fold in the future!" Fang Yuan quickly assessed his surroundings, realizing that although he was out of the hall, he was still a distance from the bronze hall.

Large numbers of dogs came attacking, and he quickly chose to retreat.

Although second aperture Gu was in Tie Ruo Nan's hands, the control was still in Fang Yuan's hands. He refined the second aperture Gu single-handedly, now with just a thought, this Gu would self-detonate.

Of course, unless left without a choice, Fang Yuan would not do something so stupid.

"This battle has just begun. Bai Ning Bing, Tie Ruo Nan, just you wait. Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed sinisterly.

To use second aperture Gu, immortal essence was needed, otherwise, an insane amount of primeval stones were needed to replace it.

To Fang Yuan, he could not keep this Gu into his aperture.

Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure was high enough, if he placed another Immortal Gu in, Fang Yuan's aperture would explode.

If an Immortal Gu was outside the aperture, its aura would leak, and everyone would notice. If Fang Yuan took the Immortal Gu and ran, he would become everyone's target, immediately being chased down by two rank five, more than ten rank four, and countless rank three and two Gu masters.

"Tie Ruo Nan has the Immortal Gu, she is definitely everyone's attack target. Hehe, I'll let you guys compete while I watch on the sidelines, becoming the final winner in the end!" Fang Yuan was resolved to retreat and recover his battle strength, before finding an opportunity to strike.

But heaven did not side with him, as quickly, many Gu Masters found out his movements and screamed.

"Who is it?"

"Little beast king, it seems he came out of the bronze hall!"

"Quick, quick, quick, block him! He must've gotten a portion of the treasure."

The voices attracted people's attention, as Fang Yuan's surrounding Gu Masters quickly turned around and attacked him.

But the first who attacked were a small group of heavy tai dogs.

Not only was Fang Yuan obstructed by righteous and demonic Gu Masters, he was also specially "taken care of" by Tie Bai Qi.

[1] Waterfall Light River Back

Chapter 398: So close to success, yet it was all for naught

"God damn it!" Fang Yuan cursed, waving his hand and summoning a golden dragon.

Golden dragon roared as it turned these heavy tai dogs into meat paste, paving a way for him to move.

"Little beast king, where do you think you're going? Hand over the immortal treasure!" Yi Chong rushed towards Fang Yuan, as the waves came crashing.

Bone wings Gu!

Fang Yuan flapped his wings, avoiding the huge waves and flying into the sky.

"Little beast king, just stay here." Yi Huo waved his hand and fire birds flew out towards Fang Yuan.

Golden aurora Gu.

Fang Yuan's body was covered in a golden light as his speed increased, retreating quickly and leaving the fire birds behind.

"Oh?" This huge change attracted Mo Wu Tian and Xiao Mang's attention.

Xiao Mang shot out a giant hand of light, like a huge elephant, flying swiftly towards Fang Yuan trying to capture him.

Fang Yuan turned at a sharp angle, narrowly avoid it.

But at this moment, there was a gentle sound near his ears.

This sound was like a lover's whisper beside one's ear, or like the voice of one's loved ones, causing an unknowing person to feel deeply emotional and unable to focus.

"Mo Wu Tian's gentle feelings Gu!" Fang Yuan quickly broke free of it after his shock, but his movement was slowed because of this, causing the giant light hand to catch up.

"Oh no!" It was too late to dodge, Fang Yuan could only use his Gu worms to fight back, using offense as defense.

Bam!

The sound of a loud explosion, and the light hand was dispersed, while Fang Yuan flew in the air like a kite with its strings cut, landing towards the ground.

The sound of the wind near his ears woke the unconscious Fang Yuan.

Sensing that he was falling, he quickly activated his Gu worm while shouting: "Tie Ruo Nan obtained a peerless Immortal Gu, she is refining it now!"

Mo Wu Tian and Xiao Mang's attention were instantly diverted.

Immortal Gu!

Everyone went into a commotion as their enthusiasm surged, causing Tie Bai Qi's pressure to intensify.

Fang Yuan caught his breath and quickly used Wu Gui's movement Gu. Large numbers of dark clouds appeared as he hid within, making his escape.

But at this moment...

Swish swish swish swish!

In the air, four chains extended out of nowhere, swift as lightning and flexible like snakes, tying Fang Yuan's four limbs.

Next, the chains tightened and coiled, spreading until Fang Yuan was tied up tightly, dragged into the void.

The next moment, Fang Yuan reappeared in the bronze hall.

Tie clan's four old-timers were at the north, south, east, and west respectively, standing around him.

The were half kneeling on the ground, their right palms facing forward while their left hand gripped their right hand, activating their Gu worms together. On each of their right palms, a black steel chain was extending out.

Tie clan's four old-timers' killer move — Infinite Search and Lock!

　　...

At this moment, in central continent, Tian Ti mountain.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, on top of Hun Dang mountain, a competition that decided the blessed land's owner was at its final moments.

"Fang Zheng, hang in there, victory is within reach!" Lord Sky Crane's voice came from within Fang Zheng. Compared to the start, he sounded extremely tired and weak.

"Yes, just one opponent left..." Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, his body full of sweat as it swayed, hanging on with just his determination.

"I, the great Xiao Qi Xing, was surpassed by a nobody?" Xiao Qi Xing's eyes were staring wide as he looked at Fang Zheng climb, at a height beyond him.

"Sigh, to think that it would end up like this." Ying Sheng Ji sighed, letting go and falling down the mountain.

He was furthest from the peak, seeing Fang Zheng's performance, he knew he had no chance of winning, thus giving up immediately.

Hu Immortal land spirit would not let him die of course, with a snap of her finger, Ying Sheng Ji was transported out of the blessed land.

Climb, continue to climb.

The skin on Fang Zheng's arms and legs were torn, as blood flowed down.

The closer he was to the peak, the greater the vibration shocks on the soul. Fang Zheng was almost unable to think of anything, there was only the mountain peak left in his mind, as his entire potential was squeezed out, he was extremely tired, and this had greatly exceeded the limits of his body.

"This lad..." Feng Jin Huang was moved.

Fang Zheng was obviously exhausted beyond belief, yet he seemed to have some sort of limitless energy sustaining him.

"Mountain peak, mountain peak..." Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, with only one thought in his mind.

He climbed step by step, surpassing Feng Jin Huang and taking the lead!

At this moment, he was only less than a meter from the mountain peak.

Even the cute and tiny land spirit was standing at the edge of the cliff, looking down and watching the birth of her new owner.

Outside the blessed land, some Gu Masters who were watching started to sigh.

"Congrats to you He Feng Yang, this time your Immortal Crane Sect performed the best."

"Hmph, if my rank six exquisite warp Gu was still around..."

"Or maybe star shuttle Gu, fixed immortal travel Gu, or one's own movement Gu, the results would be different."

The Gu Immortals had differing attitudes, some were congratulating while others were sighing in pity.

"We were lucky, just lucky!" He Feng Yang was modest but his tone could not conceal his joy.

But at this moment, a Gu Immortal sneered: "He Feng Yang, you are going to be disappointed. This Hu Immortal Inheritance belongs to us Spirit Affinity House."

As the immortal spoke, a change occurred in the blessed land!

Feng Jin Huang shouted, and a beautiful pair of wings grew from her shoulders.

This pair of wings was extremely elegant and beautiful, all sorts of lights shone on it, it was dazzling and alluring, with just one flap, Feng Jin Huang ascended easily.

"What?"

"This is..."

"The legendary Immortal Gu — Dream Wings!"

Dream wings was a special Immortal Gu, it did not exist in the real world, but only appeared in dreams. Activating it did not require immortal essence, but the Gu Master's spirit and soul instead.

Feng Jin Huang was only a mortal, activating the dream wings forcefully would cause severe damage to her soul, amnesia at best, becoming mentally retarded at worst.

But the proud her had never suffered defeat since her birth. She could not allow Fang Zheng to be the sole winner right before her eyes.

"Even if I have to pay the heaviest price, I have to attain victory!" Under Fang Zheng's shocked expression, Feng Jin Huang flew up quickly, easily surpassing him and claiming the lead once again.

The dream wings were folded back as Feng Jin Huang stood at the side of the cliff, breathing heavily, she felt a strong dizziness from the depths of her soul, almost causing her to faint.

She reached her limits.

Forcefully activating an Immortal Gu, it was not easy for Feng Jin Huang to reach this step.

"I actually lost!" Fang Zheng stared with wide opened eyes, dejected and upset.

At this moment, Feng Jin Huang was so close to the peak, in fact, her arms were already at the edge of the peak, she was one step away!

"I, I am about... to win!"

At this moment, Feng Jin Huang forced herself to raise her head, using the last bit of strength she had.

Her eyes were glowing like amber, her beautiful appearance and her snow-white long neck, was shining like jade in the blessed land's pink light.

She was like a young phoenix, expanding its wings for the first time.

Brilliant and glorious!

At once, even Gu Immortals were dazed.

She bit her lips, placing her arms at the edge of the cliff. Next, she used her remaining strength to drag her body up as well.

At the end, she rolled onto the mountain peak.

She succeeded!

The sole winner of this competition, the new owner of the Hu Immortal blessed land!

　　...

Southern border, San Cha mountain, bronze hall.

Fang Yuan was tied up by the chains.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan, we meet again." Tie Ruo Nan stood before Fang Yuan, laughed heartily.

Bai Ning Bing sighed: "It is no use, Fang Yuan, I secretly planted the fixed star Gu in your left arm. With this Gu to locate you, the infinite search and lock can catch you no matter where you go, even if you escape to the edge of the world, we can still bring you back. You have lost, admit it."

"What?" Fang Yuan lowered his head, seeing that there was a Gu on his left arm.

This Gu was a star fragment of the immemorial era, it was eight-sided and crystal clear, giving off starlight at times, causing Fang Yuan's forearm to shine with a transparent eerie blue light.

"Bai Ning Bing!" Fang Yuan howled, struggling frantically, causing the chains to make a loud clank sound.

In his past life, Tie clan's four old-timers used this killer move to capture Kong Ri Tian, to think that in this life, the same move would be used on him.

Before, when Bai Ning Bing was trapped by the four old-timers, Fang Yuan did not help her immediately, he was wary of this infinite search and lock.

Once he was locked on by this Gu, no matter where Fang Yuan escaped, the chains would extend from the void to capture him. But without the fixed star Gu, infinite search and lock would be like a headless chicken, not a threat at all.

"This fixed star Gu was given to me by the four old-timers personally, and I even spent a long time training to use it. Do you know when I planted it? Hehehe, it was when you injected yellow gold primeval essence to nurture my aperture. You had absolutely no idea huh?" Bai Ning Bing's eyes were shining with cold mockery.

This move was truly nailing the problem at its roots, crushing Fang Yuan's hopes of a reversal!

"Fixed star Gu... good, Bai Ning Bing, you are too good!" Fang Yuan stared at Bai Ning Bing, gritting his teeth.

Tie Ruo Nan continued to urge: "Fang Yuan, you have been locked on by infinite search and lock, you Gu worms have already been sealed and you cannot even use your primeval essence. You have no hope left, of course you can still will your Gu worms to self-detonate, but I would advise you not to do that. You are a smart person, you should know which option benefits you the most right?"

Fang Yuan lowered his head, silent.

Earlier, he had activated his Gu worms furiously, but infinite search and lock was famous for a reason, it was both a space path and seal path killer move. Even the rank five warp Gu was sealed, unable to be used.

"It has ended, Fang Yuan. Demon Suppression Tower is your final resting place. You will spend the rest of your life there." Bai Ning Bing sighed, seeing his mortal enemy captured, he felt extremely complicated, feeling both joy and sorrow.

"Throughout these years, thank you for the excitement you have brought to my life. Because of your existence, it lightened up this lonely life of mine, and I became less lonely and bored. Next, I will have an even more exciting life, and you should be honored that you have been a part of it." Saying so, Bai Ning Bing paid respects to Fang Yuan in an earnest and sincere expression.

Chapter 399: Spring Autumn Cicada

Fang Yuan raised his head, looking at the sky beyond the bronze hall.

There was a huge hole in the blessed land's sky, connecting to the outside world. From Fang Yuan's angle, he could see the sun of southern border.

The sun was setting, it was near dusk.

"5:45pm, at this time, Feng Jin Huang should've just inherited Hu Immortal blessed land?" Fang Yuan thought.

In his previous life, he worked with demonic Gu Immortals, attacking Hu Immortal blessed land and taking over Dang Hun mountain. In the end he paid a huge price, killing Feng Jin Huang and narrowly surviving.

After Feng Jin Huang died, the righteous path grieved, writing the "Biography of Feng Jin Huang". The biography listed all the things she achieved in life, and Feng Jin Huang had three great opportunities in life.

Her first encounter, was when she was three years old, when she was sleeping, she obtained the Immortal Gu dream wings in her dreams.

The second opportunity was Hu Immortal blessed land, on this day, at 5:30pm, she successfully ascended the mountain.

"Feng Jin Huang has the Immortal Gu dream wings, the Hu Immortal Inheritance is definitely hers to take. To not give her such a huge lead, I need the second aperture Gu. Unfortunately, my efforts were in vain!"

He sighed in his heart, but his dazed expression suddenly became resolute again.

He had a chance to reverse the situation, he had not lost yet!

That is because, he had Spring Autumn Cicada.

Infinite search and lock could seal rank five Gu, but it could not restrict rank six Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan raised his head, taking a final look at Bai Ning Bing and the others. There was nothing to say, this time, there was hope if he succeeded, and nothing to say if he failed.

"How can he be so calm?" Bai Ning Bing, Tie Ruo Nan and the others felt something amiss.

Bam!

Fang Yuan self-detonated!

At that moment, Spring Autumn Cicada burst out in two lights, green and orange, as a mystical and profound aura spread out.

All of Fang Yuan's Gu worms, all his primeval essence, all his flesh and soul, all detonated.

Every use of the Spring Autumn Cicada was a great gamble.

Fang Yuan was at a dead end, he bet on everything he had!

After self-detonating, all the energy was injected into the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada turned into a brilliant dot, carrying Fang Yuan's remaining will and tore through space, entering the most famous forbidden ground in this world — the river of time.

The Gu world had southern border, northern plains, western desert, eastern seas, and central continent. There was also one river of time, connecting past, present, and future, that was time itself.

Space and time were the basis that constructed the world.

Swish swish swish...

The river water in the river of time ebbed and flowed, crashing like waves.

Every drop of the water of time was pale white, but over a gazillion droplets of water crashed, intertwined, collided, and spun each time, giving off a brilliant light show.

In this desolate and plentiful river water, Spring Autumn Cicada was like a roaming traveller returning home, its wings flapped as it carried Fang Yuan's consciousness and moved against the flow.

To Fang Yuan, this was the third time he used Spring Autumn Cicada.

The first time, he entered the river of time without any experience. The second time, he was forced to self-detonate, there was too little time.

This time, he was mentally prepared, and finally experienced the feeling of going against the tides.

This feeling was so mystical and incredible. Countless light shadows, like a movie playing in reverse, appeared in his consciousness.

It felt like a second passed, but it also felt like years had passed.

The dangerous waves came crashing each time, Spring Autumn Cicada quickly lost its stamina, and the energy from self-detonating was expended, it struggled and jumped into one of the droplets, vanishing.

Fang Yuan blinked, and the image before him had changed!

"Hold on, hold on, all can be negotiated. I can promise to tell you the true path, but you must ensure my safety. I have a poison vow Gu..."

Fang Yuan heard a familiar voice begging for his life, he looked down and saw Wang Xiao.

He was stunned, as his heart pounded, his expression changed as he revealed an unconcealed joy.

"Hahaha, I succeeded, I succeeded again, I won the bet, I managed to rebirth!" Fang Yuan spread his arms, laughing loudly.

Wang Xiao: "..."

Fang Yuan's sudden performance caused him to feel shocked and suspicious.

"What rebirth? What succeeded? Is this guy mentally unsound? But honestly, there are lots of crazy demonic path Gu Masters. Damn it, I encountered such a maniac!"

Being stepped on by Fang Yuan, Wang Xiao who was lying on the ground thought about this and begged even louder.

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan's laughter continued, this feeling of escaping from a hopeless scenario and restarting once again was simply too good, he felt great!

He first inspected his aperture.

In the aperture, his vital Gu Spring Autumn Cicada was extremely weak once again, its lustrous body had turned into wilting autumn leaves.

Fang Yuan willed, and Spring Autumn Cicada hid its body, entering a deep sleep, regaining its strength through the river of time.

"This way, the threat Spring Autumn Cicada has been alleviated!" Fang Yuan laughed even louder, his eyes shining brightly.

He looked around again.

This was evidently still the blessed land, he was stepping on Wang Xiao, and there was a corpse beside him, it was Yun clan's young clan leader Yun Luo Tian.

He was killed by Bai Ning Bing, and his corpse was sent over by expending immortal essence.

Thinking of Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan's laughter stopped, unable to laugh anymore.

It was this guy, planning for so long and finally betrayed him, causing Fang Yuan to fail even though he succeeded in refining second aperture Gu, falling into deep despair. If not for Spring Autumn Cicada and his good luck, Fang Yuan would've completely lost. Regardless of death or captivity in Demon Suppression Tower, he would have no opportunities left in life.

Demonic path was like this, it was like walking on tightrope, one step was all it takes for destruction. Falling into the abyss, with no hopes of ever getting back up.

"I was simply too careless, thinking about Feng Jin Huang and wanting to refine an Immortal Gu, I ignored the true demon that was hiding near me! But this Bai Ning Bing's acting was also convincing, planning for so many years, working so hard to numb my senses, and then giving me the final blow. Heh, I am still a mortal, I am not an invincible god." Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's mouth was bitter.

Fang Yuan was improving and growing ferociously, Bai Ning Bing was the same.

This was the harshness of reality, and also the beauty of fate.

In this world, everyone was a main character, but everyone was also a side character.

"Everyone has their own advantages, Bai Ning Bing has the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, Tie Ruo Nan has her Tie clan background, Feng Jin Huang gained an Immortal Gu in her dreams when she was three years old. As for me, I struggled for hundreds of years, cultivating bitterly until I refined the Spring Autumn Cicada."

Fang Yuan thought about this, and his emotions surged again, he smiled brilliantly and recited: "

Viewing thousands of mountains in deep crimson

Layers of trees dyed red

On the limpid blue water

Hundreds of barges race against currents

Hawks spread their wings in the vast sky

Fish swim freely under deep water

All living things vie for freedom under the autumn sky

Pondering over the immensity of the universe

I ask this boundless and misty earth

Who rules the fate of this world?"

If heavens had emotions it would grow old, the Great Dao is emotionless and impartial. Every living being has the chance to rise up, it depends on how one uses their opportunities, and how one fights!

In this world, no one is born to be a side character. And there is no one who is an eternal main character.

Living beings compete, the weak are eliminated.

Precisely because of the heroes competing in this world, facing off with their respective strengths and trump cards, can history be so immense and interesting, making the world such a mystical place.

Thinking so, the bitterness, hatred, shock, grieve and joy vanished in Fang Yuan like a trace of smoke.

His heart was clear, his demonic resolution shone deeply in his eyes.

He started to think calmly.

"So I rebirthed at this time. According to my previous life's development, I grilled Wang Xiao regarding the path towards Wu mountain, but he did not tell me even after dying. I had no choice and had to kill him, using the beast strength placenta Gu to devour his and Yun Luo Tian's apertures."

Fang Yuan was solemn, his expression like ice, as he recalled in his mind what was about to happen.

"Next, I spent a lot of effort, exposing the Spring Autumn Cicada to convince the land spirit. Next, I killed killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu, Wu Shen Tong, and Zhang San San. I unexpectantly obtained a slavery Gu from Zhang San San, and was about to continue killing people when an accident occurred. I had no choice but to interfere and kill Long Qing Tian, but because of the jade sky Gu poison, I had no gains."

"Next, I refined Gu, defended the hall, and got betrayed by Bai Ning Bing..."

Fang Yuan's mind worked like lightning, almost instantly recalling the previous life as his eyes squinted into a line, subconsciously clenching his fists tightly.

"The situation is really perilous!" With his rebirth, Fang Yuan looked at the situation clear as day, his previous life's carelessness became this life's alertness.

Firstly, Bai Ning Bing already knows about the details regarding the refinement of the Immortal Gu.

She had secretly cooperated with Tie Ruo Nan, Tie clan had to be prepared long ago, that Tie Bai Qi might have already hidden himself in San Cha mountain, ready to strike at any moment.

The enemy is hidden while I am exposed, this is not good!

Next, during the last few days of refinement, Xiao Mang would arrive here. The unexpected Mo Wu Tian would also join in with his new rank five cultivation.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan killed several demonic heads causing the demonic faction to have no leader. Mo Wu Tian's arrival easily overturned that as he gathered the demonic path's strength using his rank five cultivation. It could be said that because of him, it hastened the outside experts' attack on the hall.

The enemy is strong while I am weak, that is even worse!!

Lastly, the most severe point...

Fang Yuan raised his left arm.

In his previous life, he was kept in the dark, but now he knew: Bai Ning Bing had secretly planted the fixed star Gu on him, on this forearm. Once the Tie clan's four old-timers used the infinite search and lock, he would have no way to escape, captured even if he ran to the edge of the world.

"Now that I think about it, Tie clan did not move earlier because first, I killed Tie Mu Bai, and that situation greatly exceeded their expectations. Secondly, they want to reap the benefits from others' conflict, attaining the fruits of victory without loss. Thirdly, they are extremely vigilant. Although infinite search and lock can restrict rank five Gu worms, it could be resisted in other ways. What if they arrested me but did not find the Yang Gu? Thus because of this, they kept it as a final trump card."

Fixed star Gu was secretly planted, Fang Yuan was now like a fish in the net, he could not escape. It was almost a hopeless situation.

(Author's note: This book is the realization of my dream these six years. Thus it contained many things, and is different from other books. One point especially, that is Fang Yuan the main character, is able to fail. Demonic path was never about winning every battle, demons lose too. If I do not write out the failure, I would not be able to represent the true nature of "demonic". Any risk has a price to pay, if one day, in the event Fang Yuan's death would make the book more interesting, or even elevate it to another level, then I would write him to death, that is also the tragedy of the demonic path.)

Chapter 400: Life is but a few hundred years, it is all a grand gamble!

"Fixed star Gu, this is like a rope tied around my neck. Although I have methods to get rid of it, I need a lot of time to prepare. If I want to immediately get rid of the fixed star Gu, unless Bai Ning Bing took it back personally, otherwise, I can also chop off my left forearm..." Fang Yuan's heart was burning with this urge.

Fixed star Gu was hiding in Fang Yuan's forearm, once he discarded his forearm, Tie clan's four old-timers would only be able to retrieve his broken limb.

If if he did that, Fang Yuan would lose a limb.

He would have to treat it in the future, making a broken limb grow back, creating something from nothing, it would spend a lot of effort.

Not mentioning how troublesome healing would be, the thing now was once he loses his left arm, it would be alerting his enemies. Tie clan and Bai Ning Bing would immediately realize that Fang Yuan knew what was going on, and would immediately start their attacks.

That way, the attackers of the main hall would also include Tie clan and Bai Ning Bing.

To Fang Yuan, such a situation was worse than the previous life.

"I cannot alert them prematurely! I was lucky to rebirth, compared to last time, my only advantage is that I know what is going to happen. I have to go with the flow, since Tie clan and Bai Ning Bing are still usable to me now. Once I lose my arm, not only would Tie clan be forced to go against me, the situation will also change, and derail from the tracks of my previous life, I would lose my rebirth advantage completely."

But if he did not get rid of his arm, how would he get out of this situation, and counterattack under such dire circumstances?

Fang Yuan pondered, all sorts of people, incidents, cause and effect flickered in his mind.

Wang Xiao, Chou Jiu, Wu Shen Tong, Zhang San San, Long Qing Tian, Xiao Mang, Tie Ruo Nan, Bai Ning Bing, Mo Wu Tian, Yan Jun, Feng Tian Yu...

Slavery Gu, jade sky Gu poison, land spirit, bronze hall, immortal essence, fixed star Gu, second aperture Gu, undefeated hundred battles Gu...

Numerous choices give birth to unlimited possibilities. Infinite possibilities affect each other.

Fang Yuan's mind worked rapidly, all sorts of inspiration and scenarios happened in his head like lighting a flint in the darkness.

What should he do to protect himself, while maintaining the biggest benefits?

He thought and thought, expending his mental energy, in just a little bit of time, his ears were buzzing.

"Wait!" Suddenly, Fang Yuan's body shook.

"Maybe... take a step backwards, and the sea and sky becomes wider? Should I consider this from a wider perspective?" An absurd thought appeared in this head.

"No way, if I do this, the risks are greater!" He shook his head, muttering as he denied this idea.

But this thought was rooted in his head, it continued to influence him.

"If I do this and manage to succeed, my gains will be overwhelming!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone brilliantly.

But the next moment, he shook his head again: "If there is even an inch of calculation mistake in this plan, I will be completely finished, the consequences would be worse than falling into Tie Ruo Nan's hands. The Spring Autumn Cicada has already been used, I cannot use rebirth again for a while..."

As he thought, Fang Yuan's gaze became solemn and deep.

Suddenly, he laughed lightly: "To think that I, a great demonic leader in my time, am being so careful and worried now, afraid to execute my plans. As long as there is hope, I should be brave enough to do it. Only an overwhelming benefit can cause me to go forward relentlessly. Fortune and risks come together, why should I go slow and steady to build my foundation? I want to ascend to heaven in one step!"

"That's right, this is the plan! Death without a proper burial if I fail, fly into the sky like a dragon if I succeed, and pave the way for my future plans. Hehehe, hahaha, life is but a few hundred years, it is all a grand gamble!"　

"Little beast king, don't be rash, we can talk this out. You want the path into Wu mountain, we can negotiate this, it can be discussed." Wang Xiao underneath his feet begged.

Fang Yuan laughed at times, remained solemn at times, frowned at times, and went back to laughing happily at times. He scared this rank five Gu Master, the lord of Wu mountain, a great demonic expert to death.

In Wang Xiao's heart, Fang Yuan was a maniac, a mentally ill person.

Demonic path is extreme, without a clan's support, cultivation is difficult. At times they struggled at death's door, they face great mental pressure. It is not uncommon for demonic Gu Masters to develop mental illnesses.

Especially when Fang Yuan talked to himself sometimes, or even made poems for himself, it intensified Wang Xiao's worries.

Against a normal person, he had his ways to deal with them. But dealing with a madman, even a Gu Immortal has no confidence.

"Oh? You plan to tell me Wu mountain's entrance?" Fang Yuan frowned, looking at Wang Xiao.

"Of course, but you have to let me off." Wang Xiao saw a reaction from Fang Yuan and shouted anxiously.

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan's gaze became sharp, pressing with his feet and with a crack, Wang Xiao's head was smashed to bits.

Wang Xiao was a great expert, devious and cruel, cold and emotionless. To get him to say the correct entrance into Wu mountain, Zhang San San's rank five slavery Gu was needed.

But in Fang Yuan's new plan, Wang Xiao had been discarded, there is no need to waste time talking to him, thus he was directly killed.

A pity for Wang Xiao, the lord of Wu mountain yet he died so pathetically in Fang Yuan's hands.

After killing Wang Xiao, Fang Yuan took his Gu and used beast strength placenta Gu, devouring his and Yun Luo Tian's apertures.

"This way, beast strength placenta Gu's aptitude is eighty-three percent. In terms of immortal essence, we spent a little bit more than expected, slightly exceeding two portions. Ba Gui, you want me to stop?" Fang Yuan suddenly said.

Land spirit: "Eh? How did you know my thought?"

"Of course I know." Fang Yuan snorted, leaking the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura: "Ba Gui, have a feel, what do you think this is?"

The land spirit was speechless!

"This, this is the aura of a rank six Immortal Gu! It seems... it seems to be the Spring Autumn Cicada... Spring Autumn Cicada is the seventh mysterious Gu in this world! You are a mere mortal, how can you possess such an Immortal Gu?"

In his past life, Fang Yuan spent a lot of time talking to Ba Gui, eventually failing to convince it, thus gambling and revealing his greatest trump card, convincing the land spirit.

This time, Fang Yuan revealed Spring Autumn Cicada's aura from the start and went straight to the point: "Ba Gui, I will not lie to you, I am a future Gu Immortal, using the Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth myself into the past."

"What?!" Land spirit was shocked beyond words, the information was too great, it could not accept it so readily.

Fang Yuan's expression was arrogant: "I came back from the future, I know everything. Ba Gui, I am your next master, I succeeded in refining the second aperture Gu in my previous life..."

Fang Yuan spoke.

In his last life, he convinced the land spirit, but now, he had the knowledge of the future, as well as the experience of refining second aperture Gu as evidence, the land spirit was quickly convinced.

"Young man, you really are my future master? Listening to your words, it seems you really succeeded in refining second aperture Gu! Regardless of whether you are lying to me, I am exhilarated. Because this means the success of second aperture Gu has been raised by thirty percent!" Land spirit said happily.

"Enough trash talk, Ba Gui, I came from the future, I know the dangers that are lurking. First, I need to kill a person!"

　　...

A moment later, Long Qing Tian died by Fang Yuan's hands.

In his last life, this Long Qing Tian went into a weakened land and used the jade sky Gu, poisoning the blessed land and forming a loophole, causing great damage to the blessed land, and also causing Fang Yuan a lot of trouble.

This time, Fang Yuan struck immediately after rebirth. Before Long Qing Tian entered that weakened area, he used the heavenly power to restrict him and easily killed him.

"Young man, I am starting to believe you. You killed a dangerous threat prematurely. Sigh, the three kings modified the blessed land, my control over this land is not strong anymore. You could sense this danger and have the Spring Autumn Cicada, you really came from the future..." Land spirit exclaimed.

Fang Yuan sighed, land spirit was old and dying, it was like a dying old man, it could not compare to a young land spirit.

For example, it could not even detect the fixed star Gu on Fang Yuan's arm.

Fang Yuan did not waste time with the land spirit, he worked quickly, taking Long Qing Tian's Gu worms and devoured his aperture.

In his previous life, because of the jade sky Gu poison, Fang Yuan could not take the battle loot after killing Long Qing Tian. But this time, he acted early and Long Qing Tian could not use his Gu, thus Fang Yuan had no restrictions.

After looting Long Qing Tian, Fang Yuan gained several useful things.

Other than the aperture, his greatest loot was jade sky Gu.

This Gu was like a dark green bamboo stem, palm-sized and hollow in the middle, it gave off a smooth texture when held in one's hands, like a piece of jade.

Rank five jade sky Gu originated from the immemorial era, it was extremely rare now. It had an extremely strong poison and there was barely any ways to deal with it, it could easily poison a person to death, causing them to fade into a green light.

This Gu had great use, Fang Yuan kept it carefully.

"Bai Gui, quickly transfer me to this place."

The next moment, Fang Yuan appeared in front of the demonic enslavement path master, Zhang San San.

Zhang San San had not even reacted before Fang Yuan attacked, ending his life.

Fang Yuan killed and plundered the aperture, it was the same thing again, causing the beast strength placenta Gu's aptitude to rise again.

Zhang San San was a rank four Gu Master, but had a rank five slavery Gu. Fang Yuan's greatest motive for killing him was this Gu.

With another flash, Fang Yuan appeared in front of killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu.

"Eh? Little beast king! How did you..." Chou Jiu saw Fang Yuan and was taken aback, his expression extremely shocked.

Fang Yuan's expression was plain as he used the rank five slavery Gu.

The slavery Gu exploded into a yellow light, landing on Chou Jiu.

Chou Jiu shouted: "F*ck! Rank five slavery Gu! You can kill me but not humiliate me, you want to enslave me, you are dreaming..."

He did not know that in the previous life, he begged Fang Yuan to use slavery Gu.

With the land spirit to suppress him, Chou Jiu could not use Gu worms, the slavery Gu was easily planted on him.

But to control a rank five Gu Master, it was not so easy, it was a contest of souls.

Chou Jiu resisted with all his strength, Fang Yuan's soul trembled as he entered a stalemate.

Chou Jiu sneered, his forehead full of sweat: "Little beast king, you are too naive. For an enslavement path Gu master, the soul's foundation is most important, the higher the better. It is not easy to control wild beasts, not to mention men. Man is the spirit of all beings, you want to control me who is a rank higher, it is wishful thinking, hehe... ahhh!"

Chou Jiu screamed in pain, as his smug laughter was terminated by Fang Yuan's slap.

With this interference, the contest of souls tilted towards Fang Yuan's advantage, as the yellow light merged into his body.

As long as it is fully merged, Chou Jiu would become Fang Yuan's most loyal slave!

Chapter 401: Battle begins once more

Chou Jiu was shocked, quickly concentrating his mind and pushing his soul, meditating resist this yellow light.

This yellow light was supported by Fang Yuan's soul power, but he was young and had weaker foundations in his soul compared to this hundred year old monster Chou Jiu. To enslave Chou Jiu, it would not be an easy task.

But why would Fang Yuan not see this coming, he had his ways.

Piak piak piak, bam bam bam.

"Stop, you dare to hit me!"

"Kick my face again and I'll fight it out with you..."

"F*cker, still kicking, I'll kill you!!"

"Stop hitting , stop hitting me."

"No, no more..."

Fang Yuan hit Chou Jiu until he rolled around, Chou Jiu could not use Gu worms but Fang Yuan had his strength path Gu worms available.

Comparing strength, Chou Jiu was not Fang Yuan's match. Quickly, Chou Jiu's face was bruised, and his distraction meant that the yellow light fused into his body more deeply.

"Hold on, I have to block it, once it fuses completely, I will be his slave, I will have no way out!" Chou Jiu squeezed into a ball as he allowed Fang Yuan to hit him, the strong sense of danger causing his hair to stand.

Just a tiny bit of light left, near his forehead unable to fuse properly.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, suddenly saying: "Zeng Ah Niu, you don't want revenge? Chen Jiu betrayed you and is living well with Shang Yan Fei."

"You, how did you know?!" Chou Jiu was taken by surprise, the light quickly entering his body with this chance.

Chou Jiu's expression instantly changed, kneeling before Fang Yuan.

"This subordinate greets master!"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

Success!

This rank five slavery Gu should be used on a rank five Gu Master to express its true worth.

Till now, Mo Wu Tian and Xiao Mang had not arrived yet. Tie Mu Bai, Wu Gui, Ku Mo and Wu Lan Shan were all killed by Fang Yuan, the final choice was Wang Xiao the owner of Wu mountain and killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu.

But how could Wu mountain compare to the door of life and death? The door of life and death was a forbidden land on the same level as the river of time!

Enslaving Chou Jiu meant getting the clue to the door of life and death. Moreover, Chou Jiu is one of the four great doctors of southern border, his influence even spread to the righteous path, he was definitely better than Mo Wu Tian.

The only flaw was that enslaving Chou Jiu placed a great burden on Fang Yuan's soul, it was a problem for his upcoming Immortal Gu refinement.

"Chou Jiu, back then did you use the poison vow Gu with Doctor Su Shou, swearing to love each other for eternity, never abandoning each other?" Fang Yuan looked at the killer ghost doctor, asking a question.

"There is indeed such a matter, but master, how did you know?" Chou Jiu kneeled on the ground and answered with a bruised face, feeling confused.

"Hmph, since you used the poison vow Gu, do you know how Doctor Su Shou lifted its restrictions?" Fang Yuan squinted his eyes.

"Poison vow Gu is mountain pledge sea oath Gu's replacement, Chen Jiu does not have the ability to negate it. She took a great risk for that gigolo Shang Yan Fei, letting the poison vow kill her. Without a host, the poison vow's strength vanished. She then used healing techniques to resurrect herself, getting free of the poison vow!"

Chou Jiu said this with a furious expression. He loved his senior sister greatly, but she betrayed him for a gigolo, even ignoring the dangers to her life and broke the poison vow.

Fang Yuan heard this and was even more furious than him, lifting his leg and kicking Chou Jiu away.

"You lying piece of shit!"

He remembered that in his previous life, Chou Jiu said this:

"We took an oath in front of the blessed land's sea, to protect and stand by each other."

"But who could have thought her heart had already changed and actually broke the oath we took at that time and injured me, defecting with that thief!"

What oath, it was the motherf*cking poison vow Gu!

This Chou Jiu only spoke of less important matters, making important information unclear and concealing himself. If he had said poison vow Gu back then, Fang Yuan reckons: He would not have been so unaware, not knowing that there was a person in Shang clan city that could break free from poison vow Gu, and thus he would've been careful of Bai Ning Bing.

"But I should've guessed it, when Chou Jiu talked about Shang Yan Fei's appearance, he said that he was only slightly better looking. Saying such shameless words like it was natural, it was no surprise that he would not mention the Gu."

Fang Yuan looked at Chou Jiu with contempt.

Saying he loved her, but used the poison vow Gu to restrict her, it showed how sinister and inferior his inner heart was. Such a person speaking with exaggerated truths was nothing strange.

Fang Yuan was also suspicious of how Bai Ning Bing broke free from the poison vow, even in his previous life Bai Ning Bing did not say the reason. Now Fang Yuan knew, it was Doctor Su Shou who helped her break free of it.

"Alright, let the past be past. Chou Jiu, go to King Xin Inheritance and get me undefeated hundred battles Gu." Fang Yuan collected his thoughts and instructed.

"This subordinate will do all that he can!" Chou Jiu answered.

Chou Jiu was a healing Gu Master, he was not a refinement path master like Feng Tian Yu, it was impossible to ask him to assist Fang Yuan in refining second aperture Gu. But it was extremely easy for him to get the undefeated hundred battles Gu.

This is because the blessed land was weakening, not long later, Gu worms would be usable, Chou Jiu just needed to charge ahead and he would obtain undefeated hundred battles Gu.

At this point, Fang Yuan's slaughter ended.

He returned to the hall and continue refining Gu.

Compared to his previous life, he saved a lot of time after rebirth. Without the Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure it was much easier.

Back then he only spent an hour a day, refining Gu like a maniac, forcing his own limits. But now he could sleep six hours, slowly and steadily, refining Gu with perfect sequence.

Days continued to pass, and the blessed land was getting weaker. But the immortal essence expenditure was much less than last time. Fang Yuan had his experience from the last time, he took less detours this time, many steps were completed in one try, and the land spirit was extremely amazed.

Three kings inheritance's weird state attracted everyone's attention.

As time went on, Che clan, Zuo clan moved out, and Xiao Mang and Mo Wu Tian also appeared on San Cha mountain.

Finally, October 24th came again.

"Master, this subordinate has succeeded!" Chou Jiu kneeled on the ground, holding up a Gu, handing it to Fang Yuan.

This Gu had a bland appearance, like a grey stone disc, it was none other than undefeated hundred battles Gu.

In his previous life, Feng Tian Yu who Fang Yuan enslaved obtained King Xin Inheritance and had several hundred hairy men as followers. Now, Chou Jiu was not a refinement path master, he broke through by force, only getting the undefeated hundred battles Gu, not a single hairy men followed him.

But the hairy men were good at Gu refinement, they could not battle. The hairy men's line of defense was as good as nothing, Fang Yuan did not mind it.

After keeping undefeated hundred battles Gu, Fang Yuan gave instructions before sending Chou Jiu away. This process was done in the dark, Bai Ning Bing did not learn of it.

Fang Yuan returned to the bronze hall, and Bai Ning Bing had already arrived.

Behind her, there were a hundred thousand dog beasts, either resting or playing around.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Bai Ning Bing, hand your Gu worms to the land spirit."

"What?" Bai Ning Bing was shocked: "Aren't I commanding these dogs?"

"The land spirit can use Gu worms, its manipulation is better than yours." Fang Yuan explained.

Land spirit appeared, slightly worried: "Young man, I have to refine Gu with you while controlling the immortal essence, if I have to expend effort controlling the dogs, I might not have the energy to do so."

Fang Yuan snickered, his expression extremely confident: "No worries, aren't you confident of my actions? Among the enemies I have my pawn pieces too. There are sufficient primeval stones here for you to manipulate the dogs."

"Is that so..." Ba Gui hesitated, but thinking of Fang Yuan's secret identity, he agreed in the end.

"As for you Bai Ning Bing, come with me. When I refine Gu, I need a trustworthy person to defend me." Fang Yuan patted Bai Ning Bing's shoulder, showing a kind and affectionate smile.

Bai Ning Bing snorted, her gaze shining secretly, as she said in a flat tone: "Up to you, as long as you don't die, whether the Gu refinement succeeds or not is none of my business."

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing entered the hall together.

Fang Yuan sat down as Bai Ning Bing acted as his guardian.

Fang Yuan shut his eyes, not doing anything.

"What are you waiting for? There is not much time." Bai Ning Bing endured for a while before breaking the silence.

"Ning Bing, stay calm, some things cannot be rushed." Fang Yuan smiled lightly, no anxiety at all as he spoke plainly.

Bai Ning Bing snorted, not speaking, her eyes squinting, thinking in her heart: "What is this Fang Yuan thinking of? He took away my commanding rights, is he suspicious of me? No, he arranged for me to be in the hall, he still trusts me! I have to continue enduring."

She thought of Tie Ruo Nan, feeling assured: "She is blocked by the dog groups outside now, without my assistance, she can only break through by force. Damn it, he did not let me control the dogs. Thankfully, we have a backup plan, Tie Bai Qi is already secretly on San Cha mountain."

A moment later, Fang Yuan was calm and resting, not doing anything.

This time, even the land spirit came to urge Fang Yuan to refine the Gu.

But Fang Yuan rejected him, not doing anything.

Land spirit was anxious, its tone became slightly angry, but Fang Yuan used his rebirth identity to convince it.

At this time, on San Cha mountain peak.

Blue, red light pillars were thin and weak, still shining on the mountain peak. King Quan inheritance's yellow pillar was gone.

The previous time, only red pillar was left, that was because Feng Tian Yu took King Xin Inheritance. But this time, Chou Jiu was not a refinement master, he could not break through the final round, thus two pillars were left.

"I wonder who took King Quan Inheritance!"

"Two left, us smallfry have no chance..."

"But it is really strange, none of the rank five Gu Masters in the inheritance came out, did something happen?"

"That's right, King Quan Inheritance was inherited, but why did the others not come out?"

"They are being retained inside the blessed land. This blessed land is facing destruction, soon the door will open, allowing us to enter and exit at will." A voice echoed.

"It is Lord Xiao Mang!" Someone cheered, recognising the person's identity.

Chapter 402: All is within my control

Extreme light Gu!

Heaven's will Gu!

Empty fist Gu!

Killer move — Immemorial Light Fist!!

Xiao Mang stood at the peak of San Cha mountain and used his killer move, causing the sky to dim.

Light rays formed into a giant hill-sized fist and pierced through the blessed land's barrier.

In an instant, the whole blessed land shook and an enormous hole formed forming a passage connecting the inside to the outside. Gu Masters could enter through it without any obstructions!

"Charge, everything in the blessed land is ours!"

"We need to hurry, or else we won't be able to seize anything."

"Unfortunately, the good stuff will be taken by those experts. It will be good if they leave just the soup for us."

"How nice would it be If I can luckily obtain King Xin and King Bao Inheritance!"

It was a scene of chaos; countless people cheered while rushing into the blessed land, causing the pressure on the blessed to greatly increase.

"This is it, hehehe, a bunch of idiots!" Xiao Mang laughed coldly inwardly and stepped into the blessed land.

The bronze hall also recovered from the tremors.

Land spirit transmitted its voice to Fang Yuan: "So you were waiting for this tremor to pass, it was really dangerous! If it was during the Gu refinement process, it would have caused a huge disturbance and the consequences would be too terrible to imagine. You are truly a Gu Immortal who has been reborn."

Fang Yuan smiled and transmitted a mental message: "I am not only a Gu Immortal, but also your future master. Ba Gui, you need to know I am the best candidate for refining the Immortal Gu. The more you cooperate with me, the higher our chance of refining the Immortal Gu. Now, I remember there will be two more tremors, we need to avoid them as much as possible. Alright, let's begin the Gu refinement!"

Fang Yuan threw the false second aperture Gu into the cauldron.

With the land spirit's cooperation, the bronze cauldron burned without any fire and the remaining bit of immortal essence started combusting!

Immortal essence combusted and formed into a blue smoke that gracefully rose and covered the false second aperture Gu.

The false Gu floated above the bronze cauldron and was turned into dazzling yellow light by this blue smoke.

Fang Yuan concentrated his attention in harmonizing the blue smoke and yellow light.

Previously, he refined the Gu together with Feng Tian Yu, now he was doing it alone and was thus slightly slower.

...

Mo Wu Tian arrived at the edge of the dense fog by himself.

His deep and mysterious purple eyes were enchanting and wild. Through his purple eyes, the fog seemed to be invisible and the sea of dog beasts showed themselves in his sight.

"Such a tight defensive formation, one man alone cannot charge through it, it seems I will need to borrow strength!"

He resolutely turned around and after a while found Hu Mei Er.

"Ah! Young master Wu Tian, you have actually advanced to rank five!" Hu Mei Er was shocked at Mo Wu Tian's cultivation progress.

Mo Wu Tian talked of the immortal treasure and was able to immediately incite the desire in Hu Mei Er who expressed her full support.

However, when they were on their way, they found that the news about the immortal treasure had already spread.

The two inquired about the details and learned the news was released by the killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu. Right now, he had already gathered a huge group of demonic Gu Masters and was heading towards the bronze hall.

Mo Wu Tian furrowed his brows. Most of the demonic path Gu Masters had already gone with Chou Jiu, and thus he was only able to gather a few people.

Moreover, talking of influence, he was no match for Chou Jiu.

Mo Wu Tian was after all a newcomer while Chou Jiu was an old veteran who had roamed around Southern Border for many years and was also one of the four great doctors. Most of the people would have favors to ask of him and he had some influence even in the righteous path.

With no choice, Mo Wu Tian could only join with Chou Jiu's group.

"With little brother Mo Wu Tian's help, these mere dog beasts are of no worry to us!" Chou Jiu welcomed Mo Wu Tian enthusiastically.

Mo Wu Tian's brows furrowed deeply as he was used as a target board for Chou Jiu. But nevermind, if he endured this and helped out, they would be able to get to the main hall quicker.

The huge crowd of demonic Gu Masters looked majestic, but they did not immediately charge towards the main hall but instead remained there.

"Sir Chou Jiu, time doesn't wait for anyone, why are we not charging in towards the hall?" Mo Wu Tian's brows had furrowed into a knot as he urged.

Chou Jiu said with a chuckled: "More people means bigger strength, there are still many of our people that have not joined us. We need to absorb their strength to become even stronger. When we charge at that time, the pressure and danger each person faces will be much less."

Mo Wu Tian urged again but Chou Jiu just chuckled and replied politely, not yielding the least bit.

Mo Wu Tian started to feel anxious, he tried several more times but Chou Jiu remained firm.

"This old fool does not know the value of time!" Mo Wu Tian repressed his anger and immediately contacted Hu Mei Er, Li Xian and others to agitate and incite everyone, making them even more impatient.

Chou Jiu had no way to deal with it since he could not directly go against everyone's intent, and could only lead a group of demonic Gu Masters to arrive at the edge of the fog.

Mo Wu Tian observed for a while and again made the strategy to divide the crowd in three groups, and so on.

Chou Jiu, however, said it was not a good idea and that the fog was too dense to understand the actual situation. As a doctor, he had his morals as a healer, he could not bear to see everyone risking themselves and delivering themselves to death.

Mo Wu Tian stomped his feet in anger and went to contact everyone and incite them with the allure of the immortal treasure.

The demonic Gu Masters' mood was agitated, Chou Jiu also took advantage of the situation to push the responsibility for this matter to Mo Wu Tian and chose the people who would charge forward. However, he put a condition that only those who were willing could go forward and they could not be forced.

The demonic crowd readily agreed and moved towards the three paths according to Mo Wu Tian's arrangement.

"Not good, someone is attacking from outside!" When the refinement was going on, the land spirit's voice suddenly arrived.

"No need to worry, I have already anticipated this situation, go take charge of the battle outside, I will stabilize the Gu refinement for the moment and wait for you to rotate with me." Fang Yuan's expression was calm.

The land spirit divided most of its concentration in commanding the dog beasts according to Fang Yuan's instructions and beat back the demonic crowd just like in previous life.

Mo Wu Tian was unresigned and again formed the second assault group, but they still met with great losses and returned defeatedly.

Chou Jiu came forward at this moment: "Everyone knows my rule, I take one life for every life I save. Right now, I will treat everyone first and hope you all can fulfill the promise later."

Finished speaking, he started healing everyone.

The demonic crowd was moved to tears. Chou Jiu's influence increased rapidly and even more people left Mo Wu Tian to side with Chou Jiu.

Chou Jiu patted Mo Wu Tian's shoulder and said in a kind voice: "Brother Wu Tian, do you see it now? I advised you earlier to not take the risk. Now, so many of our comrades have lost their lives, it makes me so sad."

His voice was quite loud which caused Mo Wu Tian's eye to twitch and his anger reached an extreme level.

"This old sinister fool! If I was successful in breaking through these beasts, it would be his contribution; and now that I failed, he is avoiding all the responsibility! Hmph, I did underestimate these beasts. I had thought the formation was a weak one, and had never thought that there was a Gu Master controlling them from behind. Such a fast adaptation speed and method, this person is definitely someone with deep attainment in enslavement path. Damn it, this is really hateful!"

Mo Wu Tian gritted his teeth but could do nothing.

In the previous life, he was able to use force and threat to make the demonic Gu Masters throw their lives. However, with rank five Chou Jiu here now, he was not able to be so unrestrained.

"Let's wait. Righteous path Gu Masters will also soon gather together and we can discuss it with them. After all, we only have one life, in case we charge through and let the righteous path get the benefits, it would be really bad." Chou Jiu spoke his plan.

"Lord killer ghost doctor is right."

"Lord killer ghost doctor is indeed benevolent and cherishes the lives of us small characters."

"Doctors have their healer morals, Lord killer ghost doctor is after all a senior of our demonic path..."

Mo Wu Tian gritted his teeth till they made cracking sounds, he really wished he could kill this old bastard.

Like this, the time was delayed for a good while until the righteous path Gu Masters gathered under the lead of Xiao Mang.

They charged through several times but also returned in defeat. Xiao Mang was getting anxious while thinking of the unopened King Bao Inheritance and again used his killer move.

Extreme light Gu!

My will Gu!

Bright spear Gu!

Killer move — My Glorious Spear!!

A 1.8m long and 0.6m thick spear of light landed on the mound.

An intense explosion occurred with shockwaves blowing away everything. After the dazzling light dispersed, the fog that covered the mound also dispersed.

The bronze hall and the majestic dog beasts were revealed before everyone's eyes in their full glory.

Righteous and demonic crowd felt their hearts thumping in excitement but also turned cold at the scene. The immortal treasure was in front of them but how could they charge through such an enormous dog beast formation.

It could only be done if the righteous and demonic allied.

Those with experience all thought of this.

Xiao Mang looked at the demonic path's direction and Mo Wu Tian also glanced at the righteous path.

It was clear they needed to ally, but they had to see which side would compromise first.

Time passed by minutes and seconds...

Chou Jiu calmly watched the dog beasts while Xiao Mang's expression was solemn as he closed his eyes to recuperate. He was the young master of the grand Xiao clan, a famous figure among the righteous path, how could he lower his head towards the demonic path first? If words spread later, his reputation would have a great hit.

"The second tremor has gone, Ba Gui, my secret chess piece has showed its use and for a short time, they won't attack. Let's continue the refinement!" Fang Yuan summoned the land spirit.

While the righteous and demonic path were in a stalemate, Fang Yuan once again resumed the refinement.

At this moment, the blue smoke and the yellow light had finally blended with each other.

The blue smoke turned into beads of grass that floated in the air and started growing. The yellow light turned into flowers that fluttered and fell into the grass.

Fang Yuan took out a dagger and cut his artery, bleeding out his own essence blood.

Large amounts of essence blood infused into smoke. The blue smoke and yellow light immediately let out sizzling sounds and turned into a red cloud, like a wave of blood sea.

The blood surged and turned into a sphere that floated in the air without spreading.

After a round of evolution, the smoke sphere settled down and formed a field with abundant red wheat growing in it.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air when he saw this.

He had lost a lot of blood which caused his face to pale. He immediately used a Gu to heal his wound.

"Wild grass grow wildly, the qi of blood like the sea. Three hundred years as spring, five hundred years as autumn..." He took out a lifespan Gu.

This was a three hundred years lifespan Gu which looked like roots with rough texture, like a snake that was coiled into a circle.

Fang Yuan threw it into the smoke in blood field, the cloud of smoke immediate started raging like boiling water.

In previous life, this strange change had nearly caused Fang Yuan to fail. Now, however, Fang Yuan had was mentally prepared and easily controlled the situation. Under his control, the cloud of smoke gradually settled down.

However, right at this time, the land spirit suddenly warned: "Not good, those Gu Masters have started attacking together! There might not be time to refine Gu."

"No need to worry, everything is under my control." Fang Yuan coldly smiled and took out the second lifespan Gu.

Chapter 403: Bai Ning Bing, have you acted enough?

"Killlllll..."

"Charge through!"

"Kill these goddamn dogs!"

Shouting, screaming, shrieking, cursing, dog barking, all these sounds merged into one, causing the ground to tremble.

The attack had just begun for ten minutes, but the mound was already overflowing with blood and corpses.

"Sir Chou Jiu, we are slow, with this kind of pace, when will we ever get into the bronze hall!" Mo Wu Tian urged.

Chou Jiu snickered: "The dog groups are huge, is it that easy to get through? It is better that we are slow, the righteous path will take on more pressure for us, we can benefit from the chaos better."

Chou Jiu was already Fang Yuan's slave, his greatest wish is to continue stalling for time.

Earlier, the righteous and demonic factions were at a stalemate, but this Mo Wu Tian had to ruin it by finding Xiao Mang to cooperate. Chou Jiu could not stop him, he could only go with the flow.

After starting the assault, he tried his best to slow them down.

They had planned to attack from two directions, but because of killer ghost doctor's manipulation, it caused the righteous faction to be further in the advancement, thus taking more hits. Meanwhile, the demonic path had less losses, but the assault's momentum was slowly, they were in danger of being surrounded.

"Chou Jiu, what are you thinking of! You are too muddled, we have to charge with vigor, how can we move so slowly? You are old and confused, can't you see? Our group is already in deep trouble, once our movement stops, we will be surrounded, we will be in greater danger than the righteous path!" Mo Wu Tian was stomping his feet in anger, shouting.

Chou Jiu stared with his eyes wide open, shouting back: "Mo Wu Tian, you junior, why are you screaming for nothing, what do you know? Doing it your way, how many people did we lose earlier! Later when we compete with the righteous faction for the immortal treasure, they will be our enemy, we have to weaken them!"

Saying so, Chou Jiu's tone changed, consoling softly: "Oh young man, it is not wise to charge ahead recklessly."

Because of what happened earlier, the majority of the demonic Gu Masters supported Chou Jiu and objected to Mo Wu Tian.

Mo Wu Tian's heart was furious, as he raised his head and screamed: "Old fool Chou Jiu, we have different opinions! You all can wait here and die, I am going to get my immortal treasure!"

Saying so, he moved ahead and charged towards the bronze hall.

Hu Mei Er, Li Xian and the others felt that Mo Wu Tian was right, they wanted to go ahead but their strength was insufficient, they could only go with the crowd.

"Youngsters are so rash." Chou Jiu sighed, then laughed: "Look, after being psyched by me, he is taking on the pressure for us. We will steadily move ahead, using the road that he paved for us, perfect!"

Everyone laughed, praising Chou Jiu's brilliance.

Countless dogs formed into a wave, as thousands of Gu Masters resisted them.

Blood flowed and broken limbs flew. All sorts of Gu worms competed, like the dance of fire and ice, lightning exploded and soil was overturned, green vines grew endlessly.

Yi Chong's body was covered in blue fish scales, black fins growing on his back with a light blue spiral wave around him. He seemed to have become a fearsome shark in the sea, charging ahead fearlessly.

Yi Huo turned into the god of fire, charging ahead as he slaughtered, everywhere he went, there was blazing flames and crying dogs.

Yan Jun used the phantom path Gu worm, turning into a hollow shadow as he evaded attacks again and again, safe and sound.

Li Xian used his rank five Gu and concealed his body while people were not noticing.

Kong Ri Tian turning into a rain of petals, floating in the sky.

The experts displayed all their abilities, getting close to the bronze hall. Among them, two were at the frontlines, and were the most prominent.

It was none other than Xiao Mang and Mo Wu Tian.

But good times did not last, Ba Huang and Ying Ming, the two dog emperors appeared, blocking their advancement like last time.

"It is time." At the frontlines, Tie Ruo Nan was bathed in blood as she stopped her footsteps, resting as she breathed heavily.

Tie clan's four old-timers were guarding by her side, other than that, there was Tie Bai Qi.

"We are a few thousand steps from the bronze hall, there are many dogs here, it is up to you, Lord Tie Bai Qi." Tie Ruo Nan said.

"Hehehe, I have been watching the whole time, my hands are itching already!" Tie Bai Qi took off his hat, showing off the third eye on his forehead.

Pew!

He activated his Gu worm, pushing the space before him with both hands, forming a black hole.

The black hole continued to spin, as numerous white apes jumped out.

The white ape army gushed out, forming into a strong formation as it charged towards the bronze hall.

"Young master, go ahead. I will block them here." TIe Bai Qi's tone was confident and powerful.

"We'll be counting on you, the Immortal Gu is most important, for the clan, we have to arrest Fang Yuan alive!" Tie Ruo Nan gritted her teeth, waving her hand and bringing the Tie clan four old-timers and starting their invasion.

With the white ape army to cover for them and sacrifice, Tie Ruo Nan successfully made it into the hall.

Fang Yuan was still refining Gu, he could not do anything else!

Land spirit wanted to strike, but Fang Yuan stopped it: "Ba Gui, don't force yourself! You have to control the dog groups while manipulating the immortal essence to assist me in refining Gu, how can you be further distracted? Bai Ning Bing, it will be up to you now, go block her!"

Bai Ning Bing snorted coldly, squinting her eyes as he blocked Tie Ruo Nan, engaging in fierce combat.

In the space before Fang Yuan, cloud smoke was moving violently.

In his previous life, he had already used third watch Gu by this time. But now, without Feng Tian Yu's help, Fang Yuan's progress was extremely slow, he had just thrown in the five hundred year lifespan Gu.

Without the refinement master Feng Tian Yu, Fang Yuan felt difficulty controlling the cloud smoke.

The cloud smoke reacted violently, causing Fang Yuan to almost fail several times, but he managed to salvage it every time.

Behind him, as Tie and Bai fought, Tie clan's four old-timers joined in.

Bai Ning Bing could not rival them, as she fell into a disadvantage, shouting: "Fang Zheng, I can't hold them back anymore, how long more do you need!"

The cloud smoke had finally absorbed the lifespan Gu, turning into the blood fields, golden wheat, filled with crops. It was the 'five hundred years as autumn' scene.

Fang Yuan's voice was nervous: "Hang in there, I need a lot of time!"

"If I die, you will not live too..." Bai Ning Bing cursed continuously.

Several moves later, Bai Ning Bing gasped roughly: "I can't continue! Fang Yuan, I am going to self-destruct!"

"Your aptitude has already returned to a hundred percent?" Fang Yuan was startled.

"What do you think!" Bai Ning Bing cursed.

The cloud smoke was slowly maturing, dissipating. From a water tank's size, it shrunk to a basin's size.

"Try to hold on, unless you can't control it anymore, don't..." Fang Yuan shouted.

"It is too late." Bai Ning Bing sighed deeply.

Crack crack...

Frost quickly gathered, as the cold aura spread everywhere in the main hall and the temperature decrease rapidly.

"What Gu is this?" Tie Ruo Nan's cry of surprise also reached Fang Yuan's ears.

Fang Yuan turned his head with difficulty to look and saw the main hall already becoming a world of ice and snow. Bai Ning Bing was floating high up in the air, her whole body turning into ice crystal, similar to the situation when she had self-destructed back at Qing Mao mountain.

The cold wind blustered and glacier rose, crushing towards Tie Ruo Nan with vast and majestic force.

"Is this the legendary Northern Dark Ice Soul physique?" Tie Ruo Nan cried out in surprise. But it was already too late, she was sealed within the ice like an insect in an amber.

The ice continued spreading towards Fang Yuan.

"Bai Ning Bing? Bai Ning Bing!" Fang Yuan worriedly shouted, but there was no response from Bai Ning Bing.

Her body had almost become one with ice and her whole face had started turning indistinct. Her crystal like eyes no longer shone and had thoroughly dimmed.

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan cursed, standing up and sending the Yang Gu towards Bai Ning Bing.

But halfway, the Yang Gu made a u-turn, and returned to Fang Yuan's right hand.

At the same time, the cloud smoke turned into a Gu worm, landing on Fang Yuan's left hand.

This Gu was like a peanut shell, golden and dazzling, the markings on the surface resembles bright red blood traces.

Earlier, the fake second aperture Gu could only live for a week, and was not stable. But this new Gu could survive for forty years!

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan raised his head and laughed, using liquid metal Gu and blocking the frost.

Then he said to Bai Ning Bing: "Bai Ning Bing, have you acted enough?"

The frost came to a stop.

Fang Yuan laughed again, saying: "Did you have a good time cooperating with Tie clan?"

This time, Bai Ning Bing could not longer act, she turned back into flesh body and stared at Fang Yuan with a shocked and solemn suspicion: "How did you!"

"In Shang clan city, you purposely lost to Yan Tu, getting Doctor Su Shou's help to remove the poison vow, and then secretly contacted Tie Ruo Nan. On San Cha mountain, you plotted together with the four old-timers... all these, did you think I was ignorant?" Fang Yuan played with the two Gu in his hands as he said.

Bai Ning Bing landed on the ground with a dazed expression, stunned beyond words.

"How did Fang Yuan find out all these? I was extremely secretive. This means, he was always watching coldly at my performance! Wait, I succeeded in planting the fixed star Gu though..."

"Fang Yuan, you demon, so what if you found out! You can't escape today, there is nowhere to run!" Tie Ruo Nan saw that the matter was exposed and quickly broke out of the ice, as the four old-timers joined her.

Fang Yuan chuckled, raising his left arm: "You mean the fixed star Gu? What if I chop off my arm?"

Tie clan's four old-timers frowned deeply.

Once Fang Yuan chopped off his arm, even if they used their killer move, they would only get his arm.

According to their understanding of Fang Yuan, sacrificing his left forearm was nothing to this cruel and wicked person.

"Hahaha!" Tie Ruo Nan suddenly laughed.

She pointed at Fang Yuan, shouting: "Fang Yuan, stop trying to deceive us! So what if you saw through our scheme? The dog group outside the hall cannot block the two factions. Soon, Xiao Mang, Chou Jiu, Mo Wu Tian, Yi Huo, Yi Chong and the others would charge in, can you defend the Immortal Gu?"

"You are a frenzied lunatic, killing so many Gu Masters and plundering their apertures to refine Gu. These crimes are unforgivable, Bai Ning Bing is the best witness! As long as we announce it to the world, you will be a wanted criminal everywhere. More importantly, your Immortal Gu is not done refining yet!"

"Do you still have a chance of succeeding? Impossible! You have no time left, not long later, this hall will be overrun by people, where can you run to? Try flying out? Hehe, you only way out now is to surrender to our Tie clan, and contribute that half-done Immortal Gu to us, as well as surrender the old clan leader's Gu worms, and enter the Demon Suppression Tower for reform, that's the only way you can keep your life."

Chapter 404: Refining Immortal Gu again!

Tie Ruo Nan took a step forward and looked with a gaze that was sharp as a knife: "Fang Yuan, you are a smart man, you should be clear of your situation!"

"I am indeed clear of my situation." Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil: "And I am even more clear of your situation."

His lips revealed a trace of cold smile: "Immortal Gu refinement has indeed not finished, but this has let me preserve more portions of immortal essence, enough for me to kill you all!"

However, right at this time, Ba Gui appeared and spoke with a tearful expression: "No use, it is no use. There will be too much loss in immortal essence to kill them and the remaining amount won't be able to support the Gu refinement. Furthermore, it is late now, there are too many holes in the blessed land and it will completely collapse and disperse into smoke not long later."

Its biggest obsession was to complete the refinement of second aperture Gu, it did not even care about its own destruction.

Right now, Fang Yuan had only refined to this stage and the crucial step still remained which was also the most difficult step; but the situation no longer allowed him to continue.

"Young man, you made a grave mistake in your calculations, our Immortal Gu refinement is a failure!" The land spirit howled in grief.

"Refining Immortal Gu? Never expected it to be so lively here." Yan Jun calmly stepped into the main hall.

In the previous life, he had been obstructed by Feng Tian Yu, but now with no obstructions, he walked freely into the bronze hall.

"Heheh, Fang Yuan, you are not the blessed land's master, thus the land spirit will not completely obey your commands. Since young clan leader Yan Jun has arrived, the others also won't be far. Today, your loss is certain." Tie Ruo Nan had some fear towards the land spirit and could only continue to engage in psychological battle.

"No, there is still hope, the Gu refinement can't be considered a failure." Fang Yuan suddenly smiled.

He moved his gaze towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing's heart tightened; if Fang Yuan used Yang Gu to force her to fight to the death, what course of path should she take?

However, Fang Yuan's gaze moved past Bai Ning Bing and turned towards the land spirit Ba Gui.

This aged Ba Gui was looking awful right now after crying, appearing extremely broken-hearted.

"Ba Gui, do you still want to refine second aperture Gu or not?" Fang Yuan transmitted his voice.

"Could, could it be that you have some way?" Ba Gui suddenly felt a trace of hope: "That's right, you are a reborn Gu Immortal, and with your previous life's experience, you should have expected this situation right!"

"No, the situation is beyond my expectations. The current me is only a mortal and I am unable to make a difference." Fang Yuan said frankly, "Ba Gui, I have failed you, the Gu refinement this time is indeed a failure."

The land spirit started wailing even louder.

However, Fang Yuan immediately changed the topic: "But this failure is only temporary, we can still have hope."

The land spirit's crying softened as it asked: "What do you mean?"

"After you die, I will be the only person who knows the recipe. The half-finished second aperture Gu is also with me, so Ba Gui, you must protect me."

"Of course I have to protect you! You are the only person who satisfied the requirements of the blessed land and are also a reborn Gu Immortal, there is a huge chance of the refinement of the second aperture Gu succeeding in the future even if it is a failure this time." The land spirit answered as a matter of fact.

"Good. it is is great that you have this understanding. However, you can only protect me for a period but not forever. Not long later, you will die. With the remaining immortal essence, we also cannot completely root out all the enemies in the blessed land. Even if you transport me to the outside world, there are many groups of Gu Masters on San Cha mountain." The corner of Fang Yuan's lips curled into a sinister smile.

Since the rebirth this time, everything was going smoothly. As he inched closer to success, he could not help but feel a trace of excitement.

"Then how do you want me to protect you?" The land spirit asked.

Fang Yuan chuckled and said profoundly: "Ba Gui, do you remember the third section of the second chapter of the \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?"

The land spirit was dazed as it guessed Fang Yuan's meaning, it said with hesitation: "You are saying... no, that won't work, there are two conditions that are not fulfilled. First of all, you need the light of glory of the immemorial era."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed satisfiedly at this, he raised his hand and pointed to the top of the bronze hall and shouted, "Look, the light is here!"

From the moment he stood up, he had inwardly asked the land spirit to share its vision, thus the situation outside was very clear to him.

Afterward, the talk with the Tie clansmen and others were only delaying the time and waiting for a good opportunity.

This was already the third time Fang Yuan had used Spring Autumn Cicada and by accumulating his experience, he had an even deeper understanding of rebirth.

There was indeed a butterfly effect to the aftermath of rebirth that could cause some things to change completely. However, there was also historical inertia; many great events that occurred were conflicts that accumulated over time, they only lacked a trigger point. Even without the original trigger, a new one would always appear. This was not something a person alone could influence and change easily.

Outside the main hall.

Xiao Mang was getting impatient fighting with Ying Ming and flew to the sky.

Rank four, gather light Gu.

Rank five, extreme light Gu.

Rank five, river under the sun Gu.

Killer move — Torrential Light Stream!

The river of light rolled and crashed as it poured down towards the blessed land.

The light was blinding, and the waves were fierce, it turned the entire battlefield white, and everyone closed their eyes, unable to resist such a strong light.

"Not good!" Tie Ruo Nan and others were in the main hall, Tie Bai Qi tried to stop it when he saw this, but the light river's formation was already complete and he could only reduce its impact by a little.

The grand light river was like a waterfall, crashing heavily on the bronze hall.

The roof of the hall was immediately broken through, and the light waterfall flew towards Fang Yuan.

"The light of glory of the immemorial era!" The land spirit cried out in shock.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly and poured his primeval essence into rank four bone wings Gu and rank five liquid metal Gu.

A pair of long and wide black wings spread out from his back, while the liquid metal covered his whole body like paint, spreading towards the black wings and dying his whole body with dazzling golden light.

"He, what is he doing?"

"Fang Yuan!"

In Tie Ruo Nan, Bai Ning Bing and the others' astonished gazes, Fang Yuan flapped his wings and flew directly towards the river of light!

Bam!

There was loud buzzing in his ears and the formidable impact forced Fang Yuan backwards.

However, he had killed many rank five Gu Masters before and obtained many movement Gu like golden aurora Gu and so on. Right now, he activated them all and flew against the flow of the waterfall, flying higher and higher.

When he flew out of the bronze hall, it immediately attracted countless gasps and doubts.

"What is that thing?"

"It is flashing with golden light and looks like a large bird!"

"No, that is a person, a warrior that has been soaked in molten gold!"

There was only a vast sea of whiteness in Fang Yuan's sight. His primeval essence was depleting rapidly by activating so many movement Gu and defensive Gu.

"Time and tide wait for no man, land spirit help me, divine travel Gu!"

Immortal Gu divine travel landed on his palm.

"Jade sky Gu!"

A ray of green light shot out from his aperture and landed on his hand, turning into a jade-green colored bamboo that was hollow in the middle.

"What in the world is he trying to do? He actually faced the killer move head-on and flew up!" Tie Ruo Nan stared with wide-opened eyes, expressing her shock.

"Did little beast king give up, and is trying to end his life?" Yan Jun's jaws were wide open as he looked up in a daze.

"Something's up, I understand him! Everything Fang Yuan does has extremely deep meaning! No matter what, we can't let him have his way, we must disrupt this!" Bai Ning Bing's tone was hurried and for some reason, the bad feeling in her heart continued to become stronger.

Tie Ruo Nan nodded and agreed with Bai Ning Bing's words.

"Four old-timers!" She shouted.

"Understood!" The four old-timers immediately moved separately towards east, south, west and north directions; they kneeled on the ground and held their right wrist with their left hand, their right hands were spread out in a claw form and faced each other.

Killer move — Infinite search and lock!

Almost at the same time, Fang Yuan's left arm shone with an eerie-blue light; one could vaguely see the fixed star Gu on it.

This Gu was a star fragment of the immemorial era, it was like an eight-sided diamond and was crystal clear!

At the same time, all around Fang Yuan, space tore apart and four chains appeared, moving like pythons.

"Finally reacting at this point? Hmph, too late!" Fang Yuan gave a cold smile.

Divine travel Gu suddenly flew and pierced into his left arm, swallowing the fixed star Gu.

The four old timers coughed out blood as they lost the connection with the fixed star Gu.

The four chains moving beside Fang Yuan also lost their target and flew about carelessly before they were destroyed by the river of light.

After the divine travel Gu ate fixed star Gu, it went into the hollow jade sky Gu and rapidly formed a cocoon.

"Huh? There is a strange person flying directly towards my killer move?!" Xiao Mang was indescribably shocked. Others often did not have enough time to dodge his killer move but now there was actually a fool who was facing it head-on!

"Who is this guy? What is he trying to do?" Yi Huo, Yi Chong and the others stared at the sky with stupefied looks.

"Wait a second, this scene, where did I see it before!" Li Xian frowned deeply, a ray of light flashed in his astute mind.

"How could this be, he seems to be... refining Gu?" Feng Tian Yu looked up for a while and after seeing somewhat clearly he immediately became shocked.

"He is actually refining Gu using the killer move, his courage knows no bounds!" Mo Wu Tian's eyes shot out purple light that extended two inches into the air.

That's right, Fang Yuan was refining Gu.

This was Fang Yuan's plan.

When he enslaved killer ghost doctor, it was certain the second aperture Gu's refinement would fail.

Because at the last step of merging with divine travel Gu, Fang Yuan was not able to accomplish it by just himself. Previously, he had the help of refinement path grandmaster Feng Tian Yu and the assistance of the land spirit, before he was able to barely finish it.

Now, he did not have Feng Tian Yu's help, thus this step was destined to fail!

However, after rebirth, Fang Yuan had never truly thought of refining second aperture Gu.

He deceived the land spirit and intentionally delayed time to create such a special situation to convince the land spirit and refine this Gu.

Similar to the second aperture Gu, this Gu was also an Immortal Gu whose recipe was recorded in chapter two section three of \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>!

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> was the first classic of the Gu world!

It appeared to be a story when one first read it but it actually held profound messages, recording the secrets of the ancient times and all kinds of Gu. Some Gu were directly described like wisdom Gu, strength Gu and so on. While some Gu were hidden, their descriptions were very vague, requiring the readers to dig through it and study carefully.

Chapter 405: Spreading my wings and flying away today, becoming an immortal and whipping the phoenix on another day! (Double Chapter)

The light of glory of the immemorial era shone on the cocoon.

Absorbing the glory of the immemorial era, the cocoon was undergoing a mystical change.

Fang Yuan's body was shining in golden brilliance, swimming up against the flow of the torrential light stream. Facing the strong killer move of a rank five Gu Master, liquid metal Gu's defense was starting to become useless.

The golden protection was washed away by the light eventually.

Especially the bone wings, it slowly revealed its original black color after being washed by the torrential light stream.

In the grand waterfall of light, a lone body was flying with great difficulty while facing great pressure.

Such a mystical sight naturally attracted many Gu Master's attention.

The battlefield slowly turned silent.

Land spirit assisted Fang Yuan fully, after the dogs lost their master, they scattered. All the Gu Masters stood on the spot, raising their heads and watching.

In their hearts, they had one question — "This scenario, I have obviously not seen it before, yet why do I find it so familiar?"

"I remember, I remember now!" Suddenly, someone shouted: "This scene was recorded in the legends of Ren Zu, that's why it is so familiar!"

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, the number one classic in the world, spread throughout the world widely, no one was unfamiliar with it.

Getting such a reminder, many people realized at once.

"That's right, this was recorded in Ren Zu's second chapter, third section."

"I remember now, Verdant Great Sun flapped his wings and bathed in the light of glory in order to refine fixed immortal travel Gu, flying towards the sun."

People recalled, laughing immediately.

"What is this person doing? Copying Verdant Great Sun, and disregarding his life?"

"Haha, don't tell me he is thinking of refining fixed immortal travel Gu?"

"How is that possible! He has divine travel Gu?"

Of course Fang Yuan had it!

But divine travel Gu was not enough, it was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> —

Verdant Great Sun was afraid that divine travel Gu would send him to dangerous places while he was drunk. Divine travel Gu was ashamed because of this, thus directing him: "Go up into the sky, and in the azure heaven among the nine heavens, there is a bamboo forest. Inside the bamboo forest, pluck a jade bamboo that is jade sky in color. Next, go to blue heaven and during the night time, collect the eight-sided diamonds inside the star fragments. Next, when it is dawn, fly into the sky and use the light of glory of the rising sun to turn me into fixed immortal travel Gu. Once I become that Gu, I will no longer send you to random places when you are drunk."

Thus, Fang Yuan needed the a jade sky colored jade bamboo from azure heaven, and an eight-sided diamond star fragment from blue heaven.

And also, the light of glory of the immemorial era.

Did he have these?

Not at first.

But after rebirth, he killed Long Qing Tian and obtained jade sky Gu.

This Gu was rank five and originated from the immemorial era. It was like a dark green bamboo stem, palm size and hollow in the middle, giving off a texture of jade on the surface.

This was the azure heaven's jade bamboo!

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> described all sorts of Gu. Immortal Gu were described as they were, like wisdom Gu and strength Gu. Mortal Gu were written more obscurely, the readers needed to look into them and researched carefully.

But the jade sky bamboo was not enough, he needed the eight-sided diamond star fragment.

Did he have it?

Of course not, but Bai Ning Bing planted it on him!

Indeed, the fixed star Gu.

This Gu was a star fragment from the immemorial era, looking like a diamond with eight sides, it was planted on Fang Yuan's left forearm, giving off starlight, able to project a half-transparent eerie blue light from his arm.

So now he had the jade sky bamboo and the eight-sided diamond star fragment, but to refine fixed immortal travel Gu, Fang Yuan needed one final condition — that is what the land spirit mentioned — the light of glory of the immemorial era.

Did Fang Yuan have this?

From start to end, he had never obtained it.

But Xiao Mang had it.

Xiao Mang controlled an extreme light Gu, this Gu was obtained by robbing graves, it was an incomplete Gu. It could only be used three times every month to unleash the light of glory. Once it exceeded three times, it would self-detonate.

And torrential light stream was a killer move that, in some aspects, replicated the light of glory.

Divine travel Gu, jade sky Gu, fixed star Gu, as well as the light of the immemorial era, all the conditions were fulfilled!

When Fang Yuan rebirthed and realized this, he discarded the second aperture Gu in his heart, changing his objective to refining the fixed immortal travel Gu.

But it was impossible to convince the land spirit.

The land spirit's obsession was to refine second aperture Gu.

Thus, Bai Ning Bing, Tie Ruo Nan, and the righteous demonic factions became Fang Yuan's tools!

He calculated meticulously in his heart, controlling the flow of events as he swayed them in his favor, causing this result. When the land spirit realized that no matter what, the second aperture Gu would not be refined successfully, it would change its goal to protecting Fang Yuan, as that is the only way hope remains.

The cocoon absorbed the sunlight, trembling slightly as the aura of an Immortal Gu leaked out uncontrollably.

Everyone was flabbergasted.

"Such an aura, how is this possible?!" Tie Ruo Nan, Bai Ning Bing and the others were staring with their eyes popping out.

"He is refining Gu, he is really refining an Immortal Gu?! Who is he? Is he the reincarnation of Verdant Great Sun?" Yi Huo, Yi Chong, and the others were staring with their jaws dropping.

"Fixed immortal travel! Is he really refining fixed immortal travel Gu? To think that I, Feng Tian Yu, would get the see the birth of an Immortal Gu!" This refinement master kneeled on the ground emotionally, tears overflowing on his face.

In the blessed land, the few remaining hairy men all kneeled down.

This moment, they were idolizing this person refining an Immortal Gu!

Unbelievable.

An event of the immemorial era was unfolding before them...

An unimaginable grandness and beauty caused many Gu Masters' bodies to shook. Was it excitement, fear, or both?

At once, Fang Yuan's figure was the center of everyone's attention.

No matter how glaring the torrential light stream was, everyone's eyes were wide open, staring without blinking.

The Immortal Gu's aura became more intense, but at this crucial moment, something happened.

"Trying to use my power to refine an Immortal Gu? Hmph!" Xiao Mang was no fool, after realizing this, he immediately stopped his killer move.

The torrential light stream ended!

Everyone gasped loudly.

"NOOOO!" Feng Tian Yu screamed, his heart pained as he showed grief and despair.

In his vision, the torrential light stream was like a cut ribbon, flowing down weakly, with just three breath's time, the Gu Master in the light waterfall would be freed. Such a short time was not enough to birth an Immortal Gu.

But why would Fang Yuan not anticipate this?

Third watch Gu! Third watch Gu!

He activated two third watch Gu targeting the cocoon.

At once, time accelerated by nine times, as the Immortal Gu's aura surged!

"He used two time path Gu worms to accelerate time?" Feng Tian Yu got up like he was jolted with lightning, his eyes glowing as his face turned red, there was still hope?

But immediately, his red face turned pale, as Feng Tian Yu plopped on the ground with a dejected expression, crying: "It is useless, the acceleration is only a temporary measure, if the Immortal Gu is created too quickly, it will not be able to stabilize its aura, and will be destroyed through self-detonation..."

But was Fang Yuan ignorant about this?

He took out a Gu worm.

This Gu had an plain appearance, like a grey stone disc.

In his previous life, he obtained it from Feng Tian Yu, this time, he got it from killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu.

What Gu?

Undefeated hundred battles!

Undefeated hundred battles Gu!, rank five expenditure Gu, once used, it allowed a Gu Master's refinement to succeed for sure!

The next moment, Feng Tian Yu was stunned, grabbing his head and screaming in great joy: "How can this be!"

Because he felt the Immortal Gu's aura stabilizing like a miracle!

The cocoon broke open, and a green butterfly flew out — fixed immortal travel Gu!

"It truly is an Immortal Gu!"

"Beautiful beyond words..."

"Who in the world is he, he actually refined an Immortal Gu?!"

At once, everyone's hearts were pounding, regardless of whether they were aware or unaware of the circumstances, they were speechless and shocked to their limits.

Xiao Mang was stupefied, Mo Wu Tian was in a daze.

"Is this the re-enactment of a legend?"

"What era am I living in?!"

Fang Yuan flew out of the light waterfall, as fixed immortal travel Gu flew around him. Each time it flapped its wings, green light flickered like pollen, it was a beautiful sight.

Of course, Fang Yuan paid a huge price.

A rank five killer move was not a joke, liquid metal Gu died, golden aurora Gu and the others were greatly damaged. The black wings on his back were torn and tattered.

As the liquid metal faded, Fang Yuan's identity was revealed.

At once, a commotion burst out.

"Who is he?" Mo Wu Tian's pupils shrunk.

"It, it's him, little beast king!" Hu Mei Er and Li Xian were shocked.

"It's him!" Yi Huo's eyes were popping out.

"It is actually him?!" Jiao Huang and Meng Tu looked at each other, trembling, feeling each other's shock, after-fear, and joy. They had the guts to assassinate such a strong foe? A man who can refine an Immortal Gu?!

"Fang Yuan..." Bai Ning Bing, Tie Ruo Nan and the others who knew the situation witnessed this miracle with their own eyes, watching like a still statue.

Hundreds of thousands of years ago, during the immemorial era, Verdant Great Sun flapped his wings, refining an fixed immortal travel Gu.

But now, Fang Yuan was doing the same, using his mortal body to accomplish such a grand feat under everyone's observation.

Once this matter spread, his name would be renowned throughout the continent, shocking the whole southern border.

"You really succeeded in refining fixed immortal travel Gu, incredible! As expected of a future Gu Immortal." Fang Yuan could hear land spirit's praise and sigh.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Fixed immortal travel Gu can allow a Gu Master to roam the world, going anywhere he wanted. But it is still an Immortal Gu, your help is needed, to activate it using immortal essence."

Ba Gui: "Of course. There is still some immortal essence left in the cauldron, recall in your mind where you want to go, you should choose a safe place. Remember, the image in your head has to be the same as the real place, there cannot be too big of a difference."

"I understand that."

Ba Gui sighed, speaking wholeheartedly: "Using the fixed immortal travel would allow you to escape this predicament, but without immortal essence, the blessed land will be destroyed immediately. Death is a relief for me. I just wish you would succeed in refining second aperture Gu in the future, and do not waste this opportunity. Before we part, do you have anything to say to me?"

Fang Yuan opened his mouth, but no words came out.

He moved his tattered black wings, flying in the sky and looking around.

The torn bronze hall, the mound battlefield overflowing with blood, and the ruined Gu Immortal blessed land...

Goodbye, Bai Ning Bing.

Goodbye, Tie Ruo Nan.

Goodbye, Southern Border.

The land spirit did not know that Fang Yuan was about to take a an even greater risk. But life was a gamble, if one did not gamble when they had the chance, when would they succeed?

If man did not have aspirations as grand as heaven, they would be letting down their eight feet body! [1]

Thinking like this, Fang Yuan felt great ambition and aspiration, his heart boiling with anticipation. Standing before everyone, he felt an urge and expressed it as a poem.

The people present heard him recite —

Since ancient times land immortal pass with the wind, today three kings return to eternal slumber.

Who would not experience failure? Verdant Sun died regretfully. Start over again and proclaim oneself as King.

The carp swims up the heavenly waterfall, travelling alone in the desolate lands and defying heaven.

Spreading my wings and flying away today, becoming an immortal and whipping the phoenix on another day!

As he said so, Fang Yuan laughed loudly.

Everyone was speechless.

Only the land spirit shouted: "Grand aspirations, I will send you on your journey!"

Immortal essence entered the fixed immortal travel Gu, and jade light flashed, as Fang Yuan vanished from the air.

Only his clothes were left, floating in the air like a kite with its strings cut.

"He vanished!"

"He used the fixed immortal travel Gu, I wonder where he went."

"Ah! Why is heaven and earth shaking?"

Everyone was stunned.

At this time, intense winds blew as mountains broke, the world was collapsing. Loopholes after loopholes were formed, connecting to the outside world.

"Damn it, escape quickly."

"The blessed land is collapsing, the winds of assimilation is coming!"

"If we do not escape now, we will die, I do not want to die!"

The experts were frightened and shocked, frantically escaping as San Cha mountain went into chaos once again.

...

Central Continent, Tian Ti mountain.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, on Dang Hun mountain, the battle for Hu Immortal blessed land was reaching its end.

"Fang Zheng, hang in there, victory is within reach!" Lord Sky Crane encouraged.

The skin on Fang Zheng's arms and legs were torn, as blood flowed down.

He surpassed Ying Sheng Ji, Xiao Qi Xing, his body was numb from pain, and his brain was unable to think, there was only Dang Hun mountain left in his mind.

Being the first to ascend, he only had one thought left in his mind.

"I am the great Feng Jin Huang, how can I lose here? I have never lost since I was born, this time is no exception! Come out, dream wings!"

Feng Jin Huang shouted, and a beautiful pair of wings grew from her shoulders.

This pair of wings was extremely elegant and beautiful, all sorts of lights shone on it, it was dazzling and alluring, with just one flap, Feng Jin Huang ascended easily.

"What?"

"This is..."

"The legendary Immortal Gu — Dream Wings!"

The nine Gu Immortals were shocked.

Most Immortal Gu could only be used with immortal essence. But dreams wings were different, it used the Gu Master's spirit and soul instead.

Feng Jin Huang was only a mortal, activating the dream wings forcefully would cause severe damage to her soul, amnesia at best, becoming retarded at worst.

But Feng Jin Huang was competitive, she wanted victory, willing to pay any price!

Under Fang Zheng, stunned gaze, she overtook him, taking back her head.

The dream wings were folded back as Feng Jin Huang stood at the side of the cliff, breathing heavily, she felt a strong dizziness from the depths of her soul, almost causing her to faint.

She reached her limits.

Forcefully activating an Immortal Gu, it was not easy for Feng Jin Huang to reach this step.

"I actually lost!" Fang Zheng stared with wide opened eyes, dejected and upset.

Feng Jin Huang's arms were already at the edge of the peak, she was one step away!

"I, I am about... to win!"

At this moment, Feng Jin Huang forced herself to raise her head, using the last bit of strength she had.

Her eyes were glowing like amber, her beautiful appearance and her snow-white long neck, was shining like jade in the blessed land's pink light.

She was like a young phoenix, expanding its wings for the first time.

Brilliant and glorious!

At once, even Gu Immortals were dazed.

Fang Zheng raised his head to look at her, as Hu Immortal land spirit stared at her in a daze, everyone was waiting for Feng Jin Huang's victory.

Feng Jin Huang did not let everyone down, she bit her lips, placing her arms at the edge of the cliff.

Next, she used her remaining strength to drag her body up as well. But at this moment!

Swoosh!

Jade light flashed, and a man appeared on the mountain peak.

This man was completely naked, his left forearm had a hole as blood flowed out of it. His youthful body, was strong and muscular, giving off the aura of a veteran expert who had undergone countless battles.

"Brother?!" Fang Zheng was shocked, slipping and falling down the cliff.

The ten Gu Immortals were shocked. Who, who is this naked man?!

Feng Jin Huang raised her snow-white neck, looking at Fang Yuan from his feet, stunned and watching with her eyes wide open like a statue.

Fang Yuan's body was muscular, the giant monster on his lower body entered Feng Jin Huang's vision without any doubt.

"I really came here? Tsk, fixed immortal travel Gu has such a weakness, it cannot transport clothes along with me. But thankfully, I placed my Gu worms inside my aperture, and brought them along.

Fang Yuan looked around, realizing his situation.

"Eh? Isn't this person below me Feng Jin Huang?"

It seems \<\<Biography of Feng Jin Huang\>\> gave an accurate time. He was a step before her, this competition did not ban Immortal Gu worms, according to the rules, he was Hu Immortal blessed land's owner!

"I succeeded, all my risks paid off. So what if I failed to refine second aperture Gu? Now I have something better, the entire Hu Immortal blessed land, and fixed immortal travel Gu! Hahahahaha..." Fang Yuan laughed crazily in his heart.

"Unfortunately, she has the Immortal Gu dream wings, I can't kill her yet." Fang Yuan looked at Feng Jin Huang regretfully, before raising his right foot.

Under the ten Gu Immortal's supervision, his right foot landed on Feng Jin Huang's face, as a jade-like feeling could be felt on his feet.

"Scram." Fang Yuan pushed, and kicked the weak and dazed Feng Jin Huang down.

Feng Jin Huang was already out of strength, how could she resist Fang Yuan's kick, she immediately descended.

Fang Yuan turned around, facing the land spirit.

"Little Hu Immortal, aren't you calling me you master?"

"Ma... master..." The little girl stared at Fang Yuan, shocked.

After she reacted, she used her small tender hands to cover her large crystal clear eyes.

Next, she lowered her head, her face red with shame, as she stomped her foot, shaking her head, saying meekly: "Master, aren't you shameful, you are so old already, quickly wear some clothes!"

[1] Your life is nothing but a waste if you can't achieve anything great.